{
  "exercises": [
    {
      "id": "f7c5fc89-8221-420f-a61a-f949089339b3",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5a9941d8-52c2-4fe3-af8b-9557eaf79538",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8a4108bc-e433-480a-a964-4467c9fac26b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0648\u0627\u0639\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4b85634a-59c9-476c-b312-4ea19112b64c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643 \u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0647\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c4ccdb1e-cab4-479e-907c-ec5e47c2b532",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u0648\u0645 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6e82efb9-f115-4a3f-b3d7-9c09fd76c9f9",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u0648\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0635\u0645\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c87e4c90-1340-4802-9d9b-78bf14936b4e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u0648\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0639\u0629\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1d626bb7-ca55-41a7-a24b-c9504c5cb61a",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a \u0648\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0647\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ce1c494d-2342-450c-9deb-285a4f581c9f",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062f \u064a\u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0647\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7782fde1-6397-4e4d-89fa-4b0a279d7b30",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062f \u064a\u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a \u0648\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0647\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c4e33e04-9099-4411-8f0e-d5a6d46fdaa1",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u062c\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062c\u0645\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "903bfc0a-066d-4d3a-87ba-4f28a7fd0ae3",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2c965e08-32a4-447d-bde6-313d107c6e1b",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "52ad34ab-1aea-466e-bc18-6993ea9fbb04",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7a61789e-7959-467b-878c-4bade42c9c8f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "05a74f82-84ef-4944-b266-2159c66b2b17",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b0885c59-e1bf-484f-b9b3-29963617bb38",
      "question": "\u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u062f\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4c25e9a1-42c6-427e-9fbc-df3bc615841a",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5678d333-c623-4636-9c48-4ab32ffdfb29",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0641\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "faf18ec1-266e-47e3-824e-714ef5d74d53",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4b1366e1-fa72-4fec-b09f-ec29700dd0aa",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e0aec2f2-26b8-4d5b-a989-c0bfd87867a3",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b96bdfcf-44e4-4557-9762-1bf3d884296e",
      "question": "\u0627\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f513aa1b-fba3-49d6-bfa7-6605cbe1ee01",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0639\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "76383f23-27b9-4300-b591-d8ab13b2ef9e",
      "question": "\u0627\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dfd5cb3f-29bc-4d8a-8b6c-e9a9904717a7",
      "question": "\u0627\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "feb5ff31-be79-4a6f-9d93-27d5f78ffda8",
      "question": "\u0627\u0634 \u0647\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "88d8f12c-9ee4-4eac-8e27-f6844a637d9b",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3f0b73c0-5767-4e94-acdf-59af90be11f6",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e13f423e-7c12-4173-9e5a-ff450865bb25",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3bc63edd-8b24-440f-939f-d9edef16a095",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u063a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d60a7310-07ba-4b53-9cd1-6314d06d0bbf",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "24ec1b39-2569-4274-9235-fb45adcbcbb1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0646\u0642\u0648\u062f \u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0631\u0627\u0621\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4b325b2e-0619-4f85-95cf-7bae7136cd70",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0641\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6da2c303-a1a7-4f16-89cc-3ccfa615b481",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0641\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "62ddf8f4-524f-40d9-9983-6eaa86a005d4",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0637\u0627\u0644\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "05ad2b72-31a7-4242-a5dc-8e5e0e6e698a",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0637\u0627\u0644\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0641\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "33fce108-8e9c-4ca0-a4a4-d459d0566ce7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4aaccfe3-4d20-4ea7-9eb8-dc868c019ee7",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "aaa5f69c-6964-49b4-94a1-d99091152ee7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0636\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a33f97cb-dc13-4dbd-913c-9dd6578c002c",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c6936187-374d-44bb-b7fb-58cc4d278256",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0632\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6557e65c-4146-4196-a5a1-586d15ace8fa",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0646\u0636\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b49274d4-3e3c-4d66-af08-de0678dc32c7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u062a\u0646\u0636\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "940a677c-8139-4301-8711-76cfc7fdd423",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6702e4f5-f4e1-400d-9a94-d0690cf353aa",
      "question": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cb3875b9-79f5-4c73-adff-7de9cd485710",
      "question": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u0627\u0635\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e2643a7f-3814-4c77-b53b-1e28d7a1f32c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0641\u0644\u0627\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0644\u064a\u0628\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1d50f597-9a5d-4e04-ac9a-ba214c5cb720",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0641\u0644\u0627\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9222f92e-5217-4597-8067-bc53993d9d22",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0641\u0644\u0627\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2d3288e9-a35d-464e-a137-6048ffe4a9a6",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u063a\u0646\u064a \u0644\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2424da2d-3db2-4c67-a54d-bac035f0e823",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u063a\u0646\u064a \u0644\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "601c18bc-cd21-4c93-9f74-9bf24092f7e8",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u063a\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "22f76427-b793-4d0c-97a9-04ffe570e627",
      "question": "\u064a\u064f\u0639\u062a\u0628\u0631 \u0623\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0645\u063a\u0646\u064a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0648\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0637\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c8b620aa-a93b-466c-9bac-4c7ec9a45bf6",
      "question": "\u064a\u064f\u0639\u062a\u0628\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0645\u063a\u0646\u064a\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0648\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0645\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c3ecf367-d082-41fb-b347-4aac9990aec7",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b47df471-4836-43d2-8b5a-c234bec729f0",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0631\u0642\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a949cb6a-5a19-40ac-92e0-be143c25ae74",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0647\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0627\u0646\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062c\u0645\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d1b3c513-92a8-47fc-b7be-d48656f9c119",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0647\u0645 \u0645\u062c\u0645\u0648\u0639\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0627\u0646\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "be4b7f0e-8b49-48cf-bd84-95118dd60eb6",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0627\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u064a\u0645\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3a495899-3213-440a-a9c6-6e2a1ff16736",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0627\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u064a\u0645\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e332df9e-21c9-4022-9858-56fad948ffa8",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0627\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u064a\u0645\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b25895af-e5dd-4766-9c5e-80902e4f23a7",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0918dea6-14b5-4b2b-85b9-e2c3348c6a20",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2a8ce45c-ca5c-4d5b-b4e4-61eefab1b5d4",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u062a\u0642\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0636\u0648\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a28c4f10-a39e-4606-b4d0-671a375ab7d8",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0639\u062a\u0642\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0647 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0636\u0648\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7a2cda7b-741c-4f49-98fe-98a3070d756f",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u062a\u0642\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0636\u0648\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u062f\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b8869142-c92a-4e4e-b705-d3387a64275a",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062b\u0642 \u0628\u0646\u0641\u0633\u0643 \u0648\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0645\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0641\u0639\u0644\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ae1277d6-6a6e-4e81-8326-98599e8aa3be",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062b\u0642 \u0628\u0646\u0641\u0633\u0643 \u0648\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0641\u0639\u0644\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7b470174-c8e4-42f1-9bea-5374c4c2bc15",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062b\u0642 \u0628\u0646\u0641\u0633\u0643 \u0648\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0645\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0641\u0639\u0644\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a932c393-2152-4a5f-8dbf-87e139b7c8b8",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u062a \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5052d96e-a0b7-4ed7-b618-0699e3b70093",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u062a \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9a65dc39-d79f-49d9-9826-747929354839",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b0f9e9f0-37e2-467f-b89e-45f255cc26ba",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4ae3ee16-8982-40c0-a6de-c034dcbe843f",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0627\u062f\u0631\u064b\u0627 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0627\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "07378735-11ef-4ae7-872d-f33555ae1d22",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0642\u0627\u062f\u0631\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "096468cf-316e-4ca3-9742-91b44718b1ce",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u063a\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dfa89712-b46f-4754-9d0c-61fef5f9c399",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u063a\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "da6a59aa-4ba1-48d5-995a-2b7406deabd3",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0648\u0631\u0628\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "df4af371-cd14-48c9-8789-40676762f1e1",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u063a\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d4abee13-d38d-4db6-8b42-87ff26b87359",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0647\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0634\u063a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0636\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "aa00cf74-df10-4bfa-9915-ad09bd597409",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0636\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0634\u063a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0647\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "af1c8058-bad8-4f72-b11f-b30aa50acf41",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0647\u0627\u0632\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "239b3bed-e611-4331-afef-f671cda07ece",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0647\u0627\u0632\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0631\u0643\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1bc7769e-a0a1-41e3-881a-b6f4d8d6c5a3",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4e6887d6-8fea-4eab-9b44-fb2c84b2216c",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3d015f2e-076e-4151-8a89-70d0f839ad82",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0648\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ba01a00e-fade-464f-865b-d9c9b3660d2a",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0648\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e787c2d4-8f20-4412-9655-dc7d39039e84",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0648\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6afdf062-e7ba-4bd8-a5eb-596fd1643b11",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6fa8cd05-9b7f-4f4e-a72a-904520d75445",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0644\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u0643\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "45f9afcf-0e9a-4923-a873-79b722065f14",
      "question": "\u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641\u060c \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5771b0dc-b7f6-4ce0-a08c-a84c2bc14c6f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641\u060c \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8dae7852-39e9-48f2-aba1-af8a5e85200b",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u062c\u0639\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0631\u062f\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6ff0a4f7-8e77-48ee-84a9-1736d2801039",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u062c\u0639\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c0f01cc9-8464-4474-8850-cdf5feec55a2",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u062c\u0639\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u0645\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e1d3083a-1061-48d8-818f-969336c09751",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0643\u0645\u0627 \u064a\u0646\u0628\u063a\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9dda8d47-cf6d-46b2-a761-0c0291173a52",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0644\u064a\u0633 \u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0646\u0628\u063a\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0645\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "67a84383-33ff-4adf-b6c2-846313df8064",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0644\u064a\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0645\u0627 \u064a\u0646\u0628\u063a\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1480ee5a-10d3-43e5-a67a-68cf7fd38a05",
      "question": "\u0642\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "045037d3-c918-40d2-81bb-c22afd3a96ba",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9f2ac41c-f4ad-4850-9a9c-52e3a3573bcd",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0636\u0631\u0648\u0631\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fd9f6ba1-3849-43ad-8c9c-86d095e94fa4",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0636\u0631\u0648\u0631\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b6899609-4e41-4bcf-b87b-f1d82ebf2266",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0636\u0631\u0648\u0631\u064a \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fc24da61-b351-4d3b-8c96-5ea36f5cdd78",
      "question": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "63f298b1-2403-48d5-b97e-3339c108049e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9390e9e5-4a8c-4ac1-afc6-12d0864fb721",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e6912bd3-121b-4958-b0b8-1b992676fd6b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "12868d16-4fe1-4476-ad1a-ba44f048aa8b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5ed551d4-accf-46dd-ae4a-df78e2377abe",
      "question": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "beca6df3-75e3-4a7f-b2cf-b3d9f404a798",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ebc9de4a-5b5c-4ef3-b98a-79f4f97ba346",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0f971e44-c1f0-4cf9-944a-35e4406c56cc",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "83135127-c438-4864-bf44-80c3f6a76355",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7679137c-d224-4c40-92a7-a57df36d6866",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f2ce7f95-dfca-48c7-becb-7f347925cad8",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0633\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ae2abe80-d129-4028-84c8-79b0544e91a3",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ab6b2d68-3783-4ddf-8499-751f7d7242f6",
      "question": "\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0647\u0627\u062a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "080ce7a0-0901-4ee7-ad58-5eed90e1cf4f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a194a149-5d9c-45df-9efe-80f571c7bed8",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0644\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0642\u062a \u0644\u0627\u062d\u0642",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "13ca5d84-6cb9-4726-9aec-a8c9b84916cb",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0643 \u0641\u064a \u0648\u0642\u062a \u0644\u0627\u062d\u0642",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u064a\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ec99b1d7-a9bb-42d9-8f59-6f675ace2b1c",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0644\u0643 \u0641\u064a \u0648\u0642\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627\u062d\u0642",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6157bead-6cbd-42bf-85fe-dc355b938efb",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4c8ed226-2739-432b-b2ed-1e80d55090dc",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9c90d283-06ef-4683-b746-13ea89e16e86",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6c885a0f-711c-469f-aed6-8dc17622366b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0627\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "76ae5e6f-74ee-49e3-844f-5764354996c6",
      "question": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0648\u0627\u0633\u0637\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u0631\u0648\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f209da71-5aae-448e-87e4-7cfe77a799c2",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0648\u0627\u0633\u0637\u0629 \u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6d862cae-5bf4-41d5-abb8-d87e73544933",
      "question": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0648\u0627\u0633\u0637\u0629 \u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5cb018d0-5594-467a-a65e-0638d5ce8552",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0645 \u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0644\u062d\u062c\u0632",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "40ab5bc9-a834-46e1-a5cb-36877df6174d",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0645 \u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u062d\u062c\u0632",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ab1d78ec-c048-41e2-a824-55130a997e2d",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u0644\u0644\u062d\u062c\u0632",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f93a4230-e5ae-43f4-ae27-6cb1fcba7e23",
      "question": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1db48394-5844-408c-a2b2-770620adb864",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "acdc9b75-4a31-412a-8f7b-003ba0bc55f8",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u0623\u0645 \u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4179761f-701f-4521-bdfc-4ce78312bf11",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u0623\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "be77870e-7bba-41d6-b988-ee9f3f121614",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "76551945-e564-46f5-a24e-1c64cb16db41",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d8e7833f-37d4-4809-86b3-eb86ac7baea4",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0627 \u0633\u0647\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0633\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "45bb272a-db7e-4d1e-842b-34c1cb6efc61",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631 \u0644\u064a\u0633\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0647\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0628\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8b935b0d-5504-4a82-b38c-e641452996d5",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f \u0628\u0631\u0624\u064a\u062a\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9d87e551-9aaa-4ea1-b654-658783e544df",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0627 \u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f \u0628\u0631\u0624\u064a\u062a\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7c6ce35b-8b2f-41a8-a758-8d00e98c1124",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0631\u0624\u064a\u062a\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2a0576e4-ee1e-4dee-b97b-3fc0afd65f6b",
      "question": "\u0641\u0627\u060c \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0646\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "436b972c-3f34-482f-8f53-adb9e797a4b0",
      "question": "\u0641\u0627\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0646\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062d\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "21ca882e-04be-4b27-b929-1d66cfa83a52",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645 \u0645\u0627 \u0623\u0642\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a793e404-0fda-4488-8d87-d65cdf94d660",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0642\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f763e6ad-0f41-4cb8-9927-d08e73d5bfd4",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645 \u0645\u0627 \u0623\u0642\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2ba2c231-5ab6-4981-941c-7e06872e3df3",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0647\u0645 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0636\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "95401a50-463d-4f1e-83bb-429d5506cf1b",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0636\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0647\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "91b77d63-a8f5-4383-90a8-ab659a75651a",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0641\u0647\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u064a\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0627\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c9b45ea8-b29b-4b13-b027-6bea97250407",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0641\u0647\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u064a\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0627\u062a \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u063a\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1c25ffef-7018-4831-9fd8-125e18b118af",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0641\u0647\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u064a\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0627\u062a \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0ca76401-b303-484d-88da-cac9c5d795e3",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0639\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "223534d6-1b5b-4979-be9b-1cb1f8c01dfc",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628 \u0634\u0639\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0647\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9e4dd3ef-db4b-4e16-8015-866b7666d448",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u063a\u062a\u0647\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0645\u062a\u0646\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "401dcbef-953e-4bc3-b274-7ec7e1bad2df",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u0644\u063a\u062a\u0647\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5a124aa7-d344-44ef-902b-29de7c613320",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u062d\u062a\u0631\u0645 \u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0631\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4d95dbeb-cf99-46d8-b1f9-0be8b86d31ae",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u062d\u062a\u0631\u0645 \u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fdf9ff89-59ac-4d57-8377-a155390ec3cd",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u062d\u062a\u0631\u0645 \u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0631\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "63b4f160-4849-4747-a128-448b3982b551",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "75b3bdd4-d972-4f2e-9fc4-d56a077fd855",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "aa87167a-85b3-4ba0-a4f6-54248e4b03c3",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0627\u0635\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7b965d46-12f6-4273-9eee-3730341d7aaf",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u0627\u0635\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7ea94a02-d86c-4464-babf-855a8e05cdd2",
      "question": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0635\u064a\u0627\u0646\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b9e8e101-b5ce-489a-85af-4c473a573fff",
      "question": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0635\u064a\u0627\u0646\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0631\u0646\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "677d66d8-6b7b-455e-a91b-6fd825b95c89",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u0633\u064a\u0626 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2232df60-0d0b-48f2-921e-bdcb4e0e902b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u0633\u064a\u0626 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6f78cccb-7561-48f6-a82a-e41b331d615d",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u0633\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "70309ab0-cb81-47d9-b05f-2f85409ea13b",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "29d8d0c3-5d7d-47a0-a9a9-7cd42e8b2376",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0647\u062a\u0645\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a0986c63-dea7-4050-944e-e519af5dd3cb",
      "question": "\u0633\u0645\u0639\u062a \u0639\u0646\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a44656f9-c7bb-4ff7-98e8-3b605f50d73f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0646\u0647 \u0633\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0645\u0639\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0869cc35-e9a2-4261-80c8-6c3735b39dc6",
      "question": "\u0633\u0645\u0639\u062a \u0639\u0646\u0647 \u0633\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bf1e04f7-9074-463f-87c2-a440d1318ffd",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ab535f16-f172-4f7f-9fc4-60b6424ed998",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8e9c0e24-d316-4f3f-971f-f10b73727ffb",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0633\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0dc366be-8928-420a-b0a5-610f363adb34",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0633\u062a \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fe7d9935-6e0e-4d46-8f7a-b1c037a60e79",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642\u0629 \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0635\u0631\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5b8b12ae-2423-4bc7-8c7f-566b29e112c8",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u062a\u0635\u0631\u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0f6de3b2-c1e5-4a8b-976d-b26fe152f1fa",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f19127e7-cb2a-4a20-adf3-d68c3b927a9e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "de804531-a46a-4252-9f21-a604c295cfe8",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f55e409e-7193-4a1f-903c-733cff86c927",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648 \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5b4cb7ca-1c01-4bec-b866-80f94cc850c1",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6169db60-f929-4052-8d4c-3a11c947a841",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a9c48588-9c32-49ee-9ef0-3f0a0ff9a5fb",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5bd064a6-3af9-46a1-b985-95442f57b178",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0645\u0641\u064a\u062f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0108f613-584d-4948-9cc5-061fb3c17147",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0645\u0641\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c337cb1c-f711-4160-b61e-2b3b6562883b",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0642 \u0645\u062c\u0647\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c6678703-f2c1-413e-9089-33da2fe1115c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0642 \u0645\u062c\u0647\u062f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "224ec5d6-9b4f-4ea0-a4c7-ae72ebf96d84",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648 \u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u062a\u0627\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9dbc207d-1707-4136-b4ed-b45155ef48a9",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648 \u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0634\u062a\u0627\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2b6ae93c-384e-456a-9bb2-9432fac7ad1a",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5694b8f0-0eed-4f00-866e-a3f7b5144189",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4d9a0ccf-2b76-475a-80ca-0198670551cc",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0637\u0627\u0644\u0628 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623\u0647\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9d87e564-0c97-4ed8-bf00-10d28325654a",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0637\u0627\u0644\u0628 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b51f1fc0-a671-443e-9d26-7dc77c30857c",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631 \u0630\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cd0d06f2-679c-4230-a692-35f659250e10",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0630\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "eaaba666-5244-4775-88ff-000cef6c2fbb",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0630\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0638\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bc2b9c2e-64fd-46ca-97e8-175d3fb2c3f6",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0632\u0639\u0627\u062c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9c1aaa44-b7ff-4551-bb81-82756e33f1c3",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0632\u0639\u0627\u062c",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e8fb340f-88c1-47f2-8a2a-d961095448ed",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0639\u0637\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0639\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0cd9f304-07e1-463a-945a-58e32e1e0ded",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0639\u0637\u0627\u0626\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "612d0f49-0839-41f3-9adc-140e11371436",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0625\u0639\u0637\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "aebe3c92-d531-44db-b652-77419050924c",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0634\u0631\u062d \u0644\u064a \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a2a8fe9b-4db3-4d80-82ea-4b5d84e30d33",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0634\u0631\u062d \u0644\u064a \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "740cd778-56ff-4a53-92fe-4ea34a110bca",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0628\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062e\u0644\u0627\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3b9b1488-7de7-4635-95e8-f3348f04fcc5",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062e\u0644\u0627\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0628\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0632\u0639\u0627\u062c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "72fbbd76-4db3-4d6d-a210-983e7a5a45f1",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u062e\u0644\u0627\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0628\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2775f309-38b7-433b-b790-dc041069aebb",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0627\u062a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1fa118e0-66c8-4fe3-a230-472c321d93d6",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0627\u062a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a85e813b-1650-4da0-87d5-f8aca2ef003a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0627\u062a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a73c52b1-36a1-45c1-b233-f960bf3541be",
      "question": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0639\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d2d86fe4-717d-4dc5-9e5f-d06de7dd7f11",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "67f2368c-6a8b-40d4-9754-b2f1963027ce",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0632\u0641 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062a\u0627\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dd667e2b-5263-41ca-89a7-a14efcd6bdf7",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062a\u0627\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0632\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "720d76c7-7dc9-4328-b863-5633db5bd710",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0632\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062a\u0627\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3b699eef-f351-4523-800a-7a52cd691702",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0647\u062a\u0645 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0645\u062c\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u063a\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0645\u062c\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5df41b00-1afc-471e-b8cf-1e756e373a9e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0647\u062a\u0645 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0645\u062c\u0629 \u0648\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0644\u063a\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0645\u062c\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5a68b091-0f82-4942-8c40-0130d6609bab",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0645\u062c\u0629 \u0648\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0644\u063a\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0645\u062c\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0647\u062a\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5fee381f-5a68-4af2-8fe2-3201bfe8941a",
      "question": "\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u0645\u0646\u0630 \u0641\u062a\u0631\u0629 \u0637\u0648\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u0642",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ebc1d13d-5493-4e2f-9029-3817ab2c000d",
      "question": "\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u062a\u0631\u0629 \u0637\u0648\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646\u0630",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0623\u062a\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8e1b5af8-8ed5-4b17-9858-dce182749150",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e333f9c6-235d-421c-aade-ad8a6aceaa2d",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c60b4d90-996c-409c-ad81-87a62f8dbf38",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "38becbf1-4712-4f70-aee9-4ba74296965a",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ac1e6547-4819-4f7c-8e09-b32b91f0639f",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0645\u0627\u0631\u0633\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0624\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f17bc204-8b1a-44e2-80a4-c1ad105251fb",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0645\u0627\u0631\u0633\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b6c8b3e5-3e6d-4a54-a28e-ad2fbca3372b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c \u0643\u0631\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "417255ca-0b7c-4413-94cb-276b038cf835",
      "question": "\u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0631\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fbf2f4e3-7427-4246-8d80-1bafec6a4c21",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0633\u0645\u0639 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "aa31ff2b-3aab-4f2e-977d-6c08adc86e0b",
      "question": "\u0644\u0645 \u0623\u0633\u0645\u0639 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0643\u0631\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "542bc51f-01ed-4947-bb5c-0c417e9f4746",
      "question": "\u0644\u0645 \u0623\u0633\u0645\u0639 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a4f603a8-0f06-4907-8577-d542a3bd089d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0631 \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0631\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "839760cb-6b17-4d4f-bfc9-569f2eab8c9d",
      "question": "\u0643\u0631\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "14a37393-021a-4373-a6d3-6d6e149cb700",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "73a5c1e2-7628-494f-8cba-96407fcaf16f",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0624\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "53bf5a08-7b15-43cb-af97-a29603cbd406",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627 \u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "72505115-f9fa-4d57-a7f9-2e9ad7b62f86",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "23a16a3e-e7a9-46b8-9ba7-eee5f6fd5656",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0639\u0646\u0627\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0630\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1a94559f-f492-4b5a-8608-e63de34dbc44",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0639\u0646\u0627\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c3c01bc0-57bc-4d01-bf17-cebcd28d4ad4",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0639\u0646\u0627\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5318c06a-8620-4abe-a714-441473338393",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f2ea282d-ce25-4ee1-92dc-7bf4719e5e54",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "26b9e59f-8c29-4fb3-be71-0af3686dfc92",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bc28861d-6189-4989-90ab-3f0f7090eaaf",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0644\u063a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7a6ae69b-9008-46bb-ab83-3f4f33304267",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0633\u0628\u0627\u0646\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ba69e40c-3fbb-4020-9436-f6923e316b5b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e47dca5a-297d-4854-a98b-e333c730ff80",
      "question": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "df0d357b-f42f-43f0-bc09-df676d64f6af",
      "question": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e6b1b10f-3021-4a21-9a4a-d33c236e53cc",
      "question": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u0628\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "88aa6891-1d0a-4023-8e9b-900723250ebd",
      "question": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6b65af29-2000-49e4-a1c9-39a429ede0d7",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "44573568-44b1-4876-8827-81cd9f56ef70",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b3988772-5b95-4c99-b91e-fc3bbb078c6f",
      "question": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u064a\u0636\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0633\u0628\u0627\u0646\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d636c0f8-1a23-49ef-a85e-e6f31bd022f0",
      "question": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0633\u0628\u0627\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0636\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0622\u0633\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "86106da7-7f16-43bc-b8cc-262a7495c540",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4f9ffb20-de24-4a98-bdbc-c023f480dc81",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0633\u064a\u0631 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0f730b75-54ff-43be-aeb8-812d3cea468d",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u062d\u0631\u0643 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u062d\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0639\u0637\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fae59967-5f65-47b4-9ab2-2708b93e1d27",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u062d\u0631\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0639\u0637\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "68ec3b16-a07e-4b54-8133-b32ba1b29d25",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u062d\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0639\u0637\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u062d\u0631\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8855554a-866f-4604-be79-19f2cde682e4",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0635\u0641\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0631\u0646\u062a \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f2556ddf-7abe-4fc5-a070-59e51fedb78f",
      "question": "\u0627\u0642\u0631\u0623 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0635",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "02bdfdb0-caa0-4176-98ce-bb2df16feefc",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0635 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0642\u0631\u0623",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "948e097b-304e-406e-b540-3d331a1512e5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u0644\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "513baec2-aa49-4822-8b7d-da979800094a",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u0644\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "658e88d9-bd39-4cca-9a4a-ded5542280c6",
      "question": "\u0633\u0627\u0631\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u062d\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4d0d8cf2-f9c9-4afd-a74a-74d8f3408fac",
      "question": "\u0633\u0627\u0631\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u0646\u062d\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9f341784-6c7e-4baa-bc2c-4084b901f1ab",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0628\u0636\u0639 \u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0642",
      "correct_answer": "\u0636\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4b8c42a7-946c-4dad-8478-aba00d2c8c5c",
      "question": "\u0636\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0628\u0636\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0642",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0644\u0641\u0632\u064a\u0648\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1fd79693-4fc3-4a2a-bccb-f2a6604c278b",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0636\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0641\u062a\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u0637\u0648\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "17211823-15fc-480e-925f-5e2b16f0b339",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643 \u0644\u0641\u062a\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u0637\u0648\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0636\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "98a2d2c2-c152-4626-85d8-12d3a3d25741",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0636\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643 \u0644\u0641\u062a\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0637\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0645\u0631\u064a\u062d\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a69c1d2d-35dc-4b49-a024-b0eb21ca76c8",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0636\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0627\u062f\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a7f9ea89-be46-494c-805b-50beb4b490ae",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0636\u0644 \u0647\u0627\u062f\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e4a0b43d-214b-45d3-9f80-a02b85484517",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0636\u0644 \u0647\u0627\u062f\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9031ec1a-694c-4238-bf3d-d69a6a063edf",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "86bb105d-37e4-4c9a-86d1-2235f49e6546",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "76be179a-5b6f-490d-aed0-f3665992d71e",
      "question": "\u0623\u0639\u0637\u0646\u064a \u0645\u0627\u0621\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2ee7429c-50e7-4bfe-a945-6f42396b3779",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0627\u0621\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0639\u0637\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c9a94318-57a7-46db-89a3-76c4e0fb94a6",
      "question": "\u0623\u0639\u0637\u0646\u064a \u0645\u0627\u0621\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4f900f85-fea8-49e2-971a-362484603171",
      "question": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1c87bb16-f6c5-4269-83a0-10632ea530a5",
      "question": "\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0644\u064a \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0643\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "72a4a25e-6d75-4b1c-80a1-ab3ad8301cf1",
      "question": "\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u062a\u0641\u0643\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0c692f1e-422a-462b-a37f-861379e30e93",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0b0fa8fe-ae35-421b-9083-ba47f1ef90d5",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0644\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bb245013-04c9-46b5-9fe6-5ec613382f8b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "05dc048c-1055-4cb1-bd04-95aa768667ee",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0643\u0644 \u0645\u0627 \u062a\u0641\u0643\u0631 \u0628\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "332864f0-9d29-476c-97a8-3a464e7de9b5",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0643\u0644 \u0645\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0643\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ef5b90c0-6f1c-4374-a6f6-9f0d1c0fff07",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a8b2e517-b1f5-4543-b83b-4d073841c773",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2996ce74-6c92-4bb9-b8f2-a73257f3217d",
      "question": "\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0634\u0643\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8661c0c4-d214-4301-b1ee-4da36cc1aba6",
      "question": "\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0634\u0643\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "11d0595d-2d4b-4331-9fd9-145c18f904e8",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0634\u0643\u0644 \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "eb4349a5-d90f-4f59-89b1-0f00b259770c",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0648\u0636\u0648\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8cf8ca64-23a0-4143-adaf-4ba226117e09",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0648\u0636\u0648\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "59b983a8-d330-4684-8518-d6138c0e77f3",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0648\u0636\u0648\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "097f9758-1635-41b9-8b4e-d0b3ea6504a6",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ec18fff7-fda3-4c22-9273-3b1cb6408145",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4b6534d3-51d6-4c40-9e75-421815f5dd92",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d2a52ce4-7ca3-4b74-b2e2-841b4a7425d8",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u064a \u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f2232848-5cc5-49cf-8ec0-4d6786b7e126",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u063a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "baaea14a-3101-4c05-bd13-899ac933c7b7",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "557ced1a-84b0-4dea-92db-e786f85847f5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u0636\u0631\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0164ed97-8e6f-41a2-b1f2-a1bab95e0b6d",
      "question": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8fce2dbe-57d2-49d2-bc0a-caf12cf8c36f",
      "question": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "af1ff483-f2f9-40aa-996f-03eb167c16d2",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0631\u062d \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "882db295-79ea-4626-ade6-294d90824c20",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0634\u0631\u062d \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6d03fa3b-aa23-40ea-8da9-82c7699efbb6",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0631\u062c\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "206e3e1d-798d-4144-8753-51f6363cce31",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0631\u062c\u0627\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d1576014-04c1-4c39-aa1d-0613effac8c4",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0631\u062c\u0627\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "120a6a8d-7dee-49bd-b443-1ca38988eee4",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0120f7bd-a67b-4592-be08-058b507480f1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3a178544-bfec-4cbd-941a-127f8035e93b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d810a6da-92f2-4ebd-b5ae-ce09ed1bc2f4",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c04c4e3f-0f16-4192-b48f-9ee8ba88a5e9",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1e41c9e5-cfb1-4dc7-8c09-57d095216027",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642 \u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0624\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b6471756-3e40-41e1-bd67-4592b3f8a3cf",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b3cb3aa6-6c5e-4e3a-9d58-403969ef1bcb",
      "question": "\u0625\u064a\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "166fd7f4-5636-43db-831d-a4ab9305f3a9",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "72c8de6a-0092-4156-a1c6-4b8550f6ca0d",
      "question": "\u0625\u064a\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cba6dcf6-2156-49d6-959d-8b95ba0d8ef8",
      "question": "\u0625\u064a\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1a628bc0-312f-495c-8461-67aa85c42aac",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d205d829-a592-4ef2-8439-89fb79300915",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0634\u0631\u062d\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1fe7c2b3-e43a-4514-a7c0-9a3e7c1523d3",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0634\u0631\u062d\u0647 \u0644\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f6a68c2e-5938-4c47-a40f-ced66febbdf3",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0645\u062a\u0627\u062d \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5ba29cb6-d886-4497-9d88-55644a1f6d2d",
      "question": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623\u0647\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fa2225c1-5d0d-46b0-96cb-b9ab37aeb209",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0646\u0636\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0cfefa82-ea25-412c-aa7a-11cab42e07dc",
      "question": "\u062d\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0646\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0628\u062d\u062b",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fcc87524-327f-49fd-8ba0-f37f7905210a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0628\u062d\u062b \u0639\u0646\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u062e\u0646\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "107e65a1-43d4-412f-85a8-be7aed77a258",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u062d\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u0635\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "eff55821-35c5-4c30-8b63-b02df1c1b554",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u062d\u062f \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "913b4f9a-1a85-4799-be99-be5f51ba4ec0",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "532e4c9a-31bd-4e06-83f7-c340a7d3964f",
      "question": "\u062d\u062f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "201bc063-e59a-4e5c-a758-5112c8c17023",
      "question": "\u062d\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u064a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "29674e6f-257e-45d1-9d9f-d8aba8ce816f",
      "question": "\u062d\u062f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c4bc5305-6a4a-46b6-904e-03effb3a49a4",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f \u0641\u0642\u0637",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0627\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1de82720-a9ef-4574-be6c-c019d7953732",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0642\u0637",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ef84ac14-6a59-4df4-8ee4-34360f893bf8",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u062a\u0627\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bf540a30-2add-468f-a243-cfa5beb82fa0",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0e719f5b-2ac1-41aa-8acb-57e806e0173e",
      "question": "\u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0630\u0647\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "974832de-8e8d-4332-8849-51162509b7aa",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d1d1a43f-dd41-4ea1-b5a3-e1e684c17d9a",
      "question": "\u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e4c5e858-e858-4694-9097-073caa2e9698",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b28f2a81-b1e1-440b-83b2-cea704d84143",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "efaf8dbf-28e2-4057-a205-ca180623b60b",
      "question": "\u0646\u062d\u0646 \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0635\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e8ead551-d61a-4ab2-9f04-dab046a3e4cd",
      "question": "\u0646\u062d\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0635\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0641\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d2171589-b990-4ee8-9a04-7ef0ec0c8f98",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u0648\u0627\u064a\u0627\u062a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0637\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b69eeaad-7016-4cfc-9e62-a42ebb2ebbab",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u0648\u0627\u064a\u0627\u062a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d308f895-84d9-404a-a2b2-7e4cf3199de0",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0647\u0648\u0627\u064a\u0627\u062a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0641\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0637\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1a45e53b-8560-45eb-86d3-a0606828cf8a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0633\u064a\u062a \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0638\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "715f46d9-b10d-4148-a96a-d1c4f3103089",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0646\u0633\u064a\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "59e37fe0-4413-4079-bca2-f0c0c4eb1201",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0631\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e79dbe6d-9f9f-4caa-a9bd-6141a3b616ac",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0631\u0649 \u0623\u064a \u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dd66f122-fa87-4521-9c04-247758b35159",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u064a \u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0631\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0268f77a-7c4b-4d05-b3f7-46f1332c122e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "77881060-6953-45a5-818d-4163a7bcd582",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "36fd33c3-63a4-4eef-8b8f-8e57ce0a276a",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0641\u0639\u0644\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f1b18dd2-1890-4f02-bee3-927938c2239d",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0641\u0639\u0644\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0644\u062a\u0632\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0b952cf4-6237-4a08-81de-95c00d57eede",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0637\u0644\u0628\u062a\u0647\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6ebd5dd4-8bef-452f-bd53-865f74181b39",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0637\u0644\u0628\u062a\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "97532d06-35e9-4e45-83ac-35e4b1ebd28c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u0628\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "da333997-e135-42ea-83f5-468e58390a79",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u0628\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3292c3fb-2719-4c4b-99bb-3b397acb5349",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u0628\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "75278dc1-3c53-4a97-94a8-99f465b88197",
      "question": "\u064a\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0647\u060c \u0645\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "39b36f2b-dd62-4b18-b32d-a0dc6664735d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0647\u060c \u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0631\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a5728901-1f8f-46aa-a3fc-8702e74fcfd0",
      "question": "\u064a\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0647\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0631\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9951bef9-6c65-4ce4-b914-d9fb9c97242a",
      "question": "\u064a\u0627 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a\u060c \u0647\u064a\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c87706b2-1703-48d2-bbaa-966bae68f20b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a\u060c \u0647\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "391608d8-4ae3-4c78-b420-f973cddc8d1e",
      "question": "\u064a\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629!",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "970f11c1-038c-4a41-a999-35a4dddb8b7a",
      "question": "\u064a\u0627 \u0644\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629!",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d2e73a8d-6226-4e88-bd7d-dbd1100bf3e5",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4d266f4d-c429-428a-adac-d02bc27855e9",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "45b35bee-3149-48ed-af8b-0a30078f9ede",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0623\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0631\u0633\u0627\u0644\u0629 \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0630\u0627\u0647\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "10d3b1fe-ff4c-403c-82dc-f1e9d35b6bae",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0630\u0627\u0647\u0628 \u0644\u0623\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0631\u0633\u0627\u0644\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1fddf43a-0a5f-48cf-9a8e-615fff9a8024",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u0642\u0648\u0645 \u0628\u0630\u0644\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062c\u0644\u064a\u060c \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fe15298f-1dcf-47a3-be61-8a1045e08de8",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u062c\u0644\u064a\u060c \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0623\u0642\u0648\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "798c3985-3b82-4ffd-8ac8-8e5e2534ea54",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u0642\u0648\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u062c\u0644\u064a\u060c \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "807fe3fe-9010-4a9d-b09f-df0c9b629da8",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0622\u0643\u0644 \u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0623\u062a\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a21b316b-d685-410d-b52f-d8feafc6c7e1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u060c \u0644\u0627 \u0622\u0643\u0644 \u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f78c01f7-4c58-4c1c-9f94-a210888ab16b",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u060c \u0644\u0627 \u0622\u0643\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u0628\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3f0486e6-1694-4d57-b580-a693e7f4d6ca",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062e\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a \u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e2b15aa7-74af-41d7-a1e5-c55db42100d5",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062e\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a \u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u062f\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "70146f54-934a-4c07-965f-caa841dee59b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062e\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3cf2404c-7fb1-4dc6-b891-9407ea723443",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642\u064a \u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d6ad2092-1337-433f-9e9f-c4ae4486028b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u064a \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u0644\u064a\u0644\u0627\u064b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "05e4c286-f63d-4072-8cd2-57558df8243e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0623\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c94d6981-9672-42df-8292-e2bd3c708439",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0623\u064a \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "63783f19-ffeb-411d-8c23-3689cc8738fb",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u062a\u062c\u0646\u0628\u0648\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0648\u0627\u0646\u0627\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7782a995-6c30-492e-b641-a10ad8fa37ed",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0648\u0627\u0646\u0627\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062a\u062c\u0646\u0628\u0648\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "37f3a425-1557-4269-811b-83478663e657",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646 \u064a\u062a\u062c\u0646\u0628\u0648\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0648\u0627\u0646\u0627\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u062d\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d0d99bad-6a03-4955-a111-5c863070a11a",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "32163d17-b2fe-43f7-ae77-02c9105d8c4f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642 \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a84ca763-d965-4bd2-b761-911678641652",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9f25d846-f35b-4b9a-ac45-6ae59e403d9e",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0647\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2e115027-cbc0-4bde-a6ea-f9e7c6cc589c",
      "question": "\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u0627\u0635\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f53469ba-5949-4114-b68c-9a3844d1482b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e6fbae4d-4674-4498-85ee-c1191e56787f",
      "question": "\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e8839639-c4fd-4fb0-b756-f3973985a6ff",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c75a1b19-5876-4b23-a099-83e97ff58df3",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "daf1e88f-2727-42e7-9523-46bab15a4a97",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "25eeda37-3244-46b4-8560-1326ad67d83b",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062e\u0648\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0a026569-c266-407e-9877-b81d53276bb2",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062e\u0648\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dfe03ae6-32a0-4df8-8c97-ec5d82fe2730",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621 \u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u0648\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4bd71f79-5de5-45c8-bdb5-1ab2070cd1c9",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u0648\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a4e54000-59d3-4119-bf4e-e3d87262a2be",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u0648\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4447920c-5dec-4b0c-a70a-043a79f4fb50",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0644\u063a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d642e7ba-5056-4b3f-b53c-ed3625011f16",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0637\u0644\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fa916044-fa75-4828-ba9f-d8e53bb8b5b7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0637\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ea201d47-f39a-46e4-910a-6a3935556ddb",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0639\u0637\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7db137b5-bb33-4527-a9c2-0fd3a9721504",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0625\u0639\u0637\u0627\u0626\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2ade2f85-f80e-4073-9fc0-80401754538b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0625\u0639\u0637\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "17568eda-f9f6-443b-b026-bf853589cb22",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "05da2723-ed58-4988-bae8-465889486fcd",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fecb87a3-1af6-4b1c-bec7-36f22f105002",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "85b5adbc-7284-423b-9b53-4e94f4c5a3b2",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6fb802f4-a14a-4051-8c17-7155d707d7c7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f56ce19b-b26e-468b-bdd5-1d2b38c6990a",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0639\u0645\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0629 \u0644\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d7626aef-91a0-4d2c-9d1b-dcc3f69722b8",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0639\u0645\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0f067a9a-95cb-4302-9603-65e62cfd561e",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0629 \u0644\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0639\u0645\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6652a507-fbd8-4e86-a9d2-7fcc8737f03e",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "17db4064-c63e-4248-8c1a-9fbba469a70a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0648\u0627\u0639\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4e98b52f-f992-4843-9ae8-82ff54a201fb",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9b8a95a6-b389-4fb7-ac1e-087bf05213a0",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "09789663-aedc-4dc0-a022-c50adcd969fb",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "16cf3b0e-6eb2-4113-a4e8-522143b954dc",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0642\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062e\u0648\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e226615a-0b6a-425e-b63d-44946ed05a05",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0642\u0633 \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "58bc6c0c-cbd4-45b8-aafd-875800e19a28",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "80751424-2d8f-4f04-94c8-5f90084dbd9a",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0631\u062f\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "02d37635-fe6f-49f2-a9dd-07eeaaaf9015",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0648\u0631\u0628\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "39f76b55-9b11-4f1c-8e3a-688929dafbab",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0648\u0631\u0628\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7566862a-bfdf-473a-8d2b-f14810973de3",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0628\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "28643eb8-971c-42c2-8938-da4b655e5f9e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0628\u0629 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ef32f195-bc64-4b9c-b8d9-204dee167c04",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0644\u0645\u0633\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0646\u0647\u0627 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0639\u0629\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e26ebb58-b87a-42c8-8a70-42fea95fa7b2",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0639\u0629\u060c \u0625\u0646\u0647\u0627 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0644\u0645\u0633\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0639\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bda5f8d0-3f67-4616-99b2-223345c87f3a",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0644\u0645\u0633\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0639\u0629\u060c \u0625\u0646\u0647\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "528be5df-6e2b-4391-8a57-a6ef617dcd68",
      "question": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u064a\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u063a\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "18a4567a-9814-4d2a-b425-94bc4eac5b3b",
      "question": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u063a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u064a\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623\u0647\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2512f543-135a-4e13-93ba-1f448d75c720",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631 \u0627\u062d\u062a\u064a\u0627\u0637\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7dcbaf03-6c77-4e25-ac17-fae0d354b81b",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u062d\u062a\u064a\u0627\u0637\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0627\u062f\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2fb8d8a5-0e17-41a0-b71a-be4a1066d919",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062c\u0639\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u062a\u0633\u064a\u0631 \u0628\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0633\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "30fa2a83-e9ba-4342-8d13-f5b71a6cf66c",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ec0e3076-244b-46d6-a042-f9486ab8eb30",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e353ad27-3dee-4545-bbea-f2a30db6eccc",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u062a\u0639\u0648\u062f\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6c5a7fbf-0b56-4124-a766-04aa2496ce7b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u062d\u0628\u0648\u0646\u0643 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e21830b7-7f4d-4da2-9a62-8cc50516aacb",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0623\u0646\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u062d\u0628\u0648\u0646\u0643 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f9ead455-d761-41fd-b416-be313e1a9aa3",
      "question": "\u0643\u0646\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u063a\u0648\u0644\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c8d002df-4851-4380-917e-eec9e97820cd",
      "question": "\u0643\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0634\u063a\u0648\u0644\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2b1fc0a2-80aa-41b6-80f4-c0498e2264f4",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646\u0647\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ec8d93eb-b56d-40e9-bf9b-0637d295bab8",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0645\u0646\u0647\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d0aff126-c119-49c3-9e91-182c80393709",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9fd25f28-6232-49fc-979b-03c71352bc30",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c2ccb1f2-003d-46a7-870e-d38bc012dae2",
      "question": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0630\u0647\u0628\u0648\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0628\u062d\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "114b1a5b-034b-4c72-8634-da5c212927a4",
      "question": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0630\u0647\u0628\u0648\u0627 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u062d\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cfbe5e80-8334-4b3b-9d3b-79d268ebe72f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0630\u0647\u0628\u0648\u0627 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u062d\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "27e5c39f-1ab8-4ef0-9214-c0aae887987e",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3096de46-dcc1-4628-9e0a-62cbf6787497",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7ecf4d5c-d24b-42cf-8266-1f2eb1f93b69",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u062e\u0646\u0629 \u0623\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "068deeef-f21b-4fdb-aab8-0163599b80ef",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u062e\u0646\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "24f618dc-9b22-4c21-b38b-7bf430ec3783",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0645\u0634\u0647\u0648\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0642\u0647\u0648\u062a\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u0628\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f250d757-5095-43d4-ad1a-8c9b68d72ef5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0645\u0634\u0647\u0648\u0631 \u0628\u0642\u0647\u0648\u062a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0635\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a39c6307-7a74-4c3a-9bed-5eafeec9e285",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0645\u0634\u0647\u0648\u0631 \u0628\u0642\u0647\u0648\u062a\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d27d43a4-e638-4c58-ac28-eecb6bf7d05f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e7199ae7-2c6c-4727-81a4-c10aaa75a59e",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "827c9b2e-60b8-48f7-9fa7-706ec1f420a4",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0644\u064a\u0628\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4df41c37-ea2b-41fb-a3c8-506af24994b2",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0644\u064a\u0628\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "958d0fb5-47c1-4b44-950e-908fa69c9f26",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0644\u064a\u0628\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fbbc263d-5b1f-4a7d-81eb-0c31078a47e5",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u062f\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6d4b0353-72fa-4879-90ab-05c0dc9c554c",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0648\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "77cb7e1e-7d1d-44f2-b429-cefc9685ad46",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062a\u0631\u0643 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d4ade86c-d60a-447c-ba8a-fb3808588cba",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0631\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f40bac4d-6fc3-4e88-bcc8-271c51b8baa7",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0631\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8a46eba0-10c0-4667-a251-f10d2773d850",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0631\u0643 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0642\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0634\u0643\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a065b7e1-6412-4f7b-a862-b4fc5e1875ee",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0631\u0643 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0642\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1615dbc6-5b0d-4b18-886b-37fe0bc5d4f6",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0631\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0642\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8a4f0af2-50b3-4275-99d8-c9b1d4caed45",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u062a\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0628\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "56665fbf-a357-4db6-8b9f-f268e671aab9",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6be7d2ee-cbbc-4e1a-8268-1aadf08d5b61",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0644\u0648\u0645\u0627\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f24c2205-c409-481e-a608-57ac98fe9e67",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "acf1b0f4-0fc1-4d63-8f9e-3821de78d5cc",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fd2d6ecb-ceb9-46a0-8085-fe634b03d34d",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u0636\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5128b5e0-0fff-44f1-84e3-b6acf8bfc303",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u0636\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b866c834-6757-4128-9a22-e532a0e19002",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1660542e-485a-4736-be8b-a588982eef55",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ef08b494-7305-49e2-90c2-3e68d89458f5",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u062f\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6cd39648-cb78-48ae-b37c-08d0c9b7db88",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0648\u0628 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0645\u0646\u0627\u0633\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "055783d8-6aa0-4840-915a-785914537008",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0648\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0645\u0646\u0627\u0633\u0628 \u0644\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2ea15367-9f6e-46ec-969c-8a843ab0020e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641 \u0648\u0645\u0646\u0627\u0633\u0628 \u0644\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0648\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7183a9cb-83d4-490a-bb07-10d98e5b2054",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0645\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0636\u0648\u0621 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a04f04bb-f0fc-4736-82fc-ffa13ad83a2a",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0645\u0633 \u062a\u0634\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0636\u0648\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "93816919-20a5-401c-b33d-1326f6459a63",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0634\u0639 \u0628\u0636\u0648\u0621 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0645\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0631\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0feab3a7-1f5a-4ae7-905f-ca6949349542",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0628\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "866773d4-b522-497a-ad4c-c26a9e945588",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0628\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "994af954-2183-4b99-b624-f3a5fc08b0a5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0648\u062c\u0628\u0629 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0634\u0627\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9b03ee5e-b52d-408f-8d17-d72b63e58bba",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0634\u0627\u0621 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0648\u062c\u0628\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d2271d8c-0ba9-4719-b7a4-d7d5d039ad5b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0627\u0646\u062a \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7f50ebfa-e55d-4d4b-844d-f77937a6d53e",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631 \u0643\u0627\u0646\u062a \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0639\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f89c2c0d-ea43-4163-bbe3-2295ed8f8000",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0646\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "900287f7-2231-4cd5-b5af-59968546f370",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0646\u0627\u0645\u062c\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "61d6dd26-6189-41f4-b9d6-9ad3619bae9c",
      "question": "\u0634\u0648 \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0631\u0623\u062a\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fc8b03ec-9a8c-4b03-8028-cbc5405f75d8",
      "question": "\u0634\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0642\u0631\u0623\u062a\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6fa0e6b9-80a7-469e-a23a-e5e11b32d61a",
      "question": "\u0634\u0648 \u0628\u062a\u062d\u0628 \u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u063a\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb172ace-d17e-4893-8b8a-34004dc3ca61",
      "question": "\u0634\u0648 \u0628\u062a\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3eed3367-5aee-42e4-bd74-328d1f82bf03",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9fbc3081-729a-4695-ada0-0d9612564232",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0643\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3177106b-967d-4edd-8bd2-738efdfb58d9",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u0648\u0642\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0646\u062d\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2071638b-3d44-48a6-b765-ba25f8e42c28",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0645\u0646\u062d\u0646\u064a \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u0648\u0642\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "43522e6d-e844-47ba-9950-3baac1fd84c3",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0642\u0637",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0623\u0634\u062a\u0631\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7b63537c-706a-4a8e-87d8-3550cc31f182",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0642\u0637 \u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9abba795-018e-467b-9a7f-05583bc607f1",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0636\u064a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0643\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c518aee0-5a2b-4dfb-8a05-81be8dbf3baf",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0636\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9b599d97-f10f-4149-af04-ede3c087aa4f",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0639\u0643\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "07bcbd35-1f64-4ef4-b8d2-103fd96eab5e",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0639\u0643\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6e2e70a4-fb17-4dae-ba0f-8a50fd04f3e9",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0639\u0643\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "459054d8-7bd8-43fc-ac18-a38524eb3000",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0633\u0643\u0631 \u0628\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0643\u0631 \u0623\u0628\u064a\u0636\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ea908871-e5d6-4afa-ba6d-57bcfb4a19cc",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0628\u064a\u0636\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb9b83db-051e-48c7-af84-a28b75e5bf14",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f940f0d2-d9eb-4957-9a5b-401a515c60eb",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0623\u062a\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d074572a-82cb-41ae-be17-e81111fb66b4",
      "question": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u0635\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ddaf607e-6a19-462d-80b2-62cff32904c6",
      "question": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0635\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6496c7ee-0259-4275-b0f7-e8f8c4694bfa",
      "question": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0635\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "95cff326-8619-4db6-943a-03ec331141c1",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ebb83fc1-cefd-462a-b659-fc58a147bb1c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0647\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f2e982f7-964e-448c-906e-f5be3df38494",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2c0cbe30-97c9-4df2-919f-e859c566b746",
      "question": "\u0646\u062d\u0646 \u0646\u0642\u0628\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "037d1da6-2c8b-4261-95d0-a2a5d9bdfd69",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0642\u0628\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u062d\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d9ca89e6-c6f5-43d5-8886-7258083e7171",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "049aa71b-ec5a-48b0-a0af-209ddf84381f",
      "question": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d7467c89-6e7a-45e2-92ea-882a42057485",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dc2dfb5f-a637-4c00-a6aa-53d01450ea97",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5ce46d62-b658-42ca-8bed-db113e419c42",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ca1fa722-7837-4e26-924d-ceb2a1a48b63",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0645\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4baf0e81-d839-4cb7-8824-158296c2f4f9",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u062a\u0634\u0645\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "42a06fc5-0f26-4b4c-a9d4-65d5703b0fd9",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0648\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u0641\u0644\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "37bd0ab5-c7bf-430e-8a90-4da86ce1048d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "47b24d66-941b-4a79-891d-d967d679ec20",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "403c47ef-faac-4ec3-96b2-517b45c5a838",
      "question": "\u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u062f\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b13ec9bb-9b3b-4861-a9b4-1d4fe0f2b70c",
      "question": "\u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c \u0642\u062f\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5da9d673-5f0b-4b28-8e5a-a54adbcdf4ac",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0642\u0644\u064a\u0644\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0631\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f4388a21-8583-44ab-adac-430bbb701647",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0644\u064a\u0644\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "162c06b6-b422-4ad7-a66a-93dd5f6f037f",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0644\u064a\u0644\u0627\u064b",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8e3c2162-7ac0-4fc2-b5a5-91ea16ad971b",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0643\u0647\u0629 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "037c330b-baf7-42f3-b7cd-39b6be75b822",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0643\u0647\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "58acdb70-47c2-45a7-98f0-98639c2693e2",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0643\u0647\u0629 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "91f8edee-380e-4356-8dea-21867bc44598",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7be3176d-e699-4bd2-838e-f5a2c4fffa48",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "79e1a26b-533c-4e52-902b-14303e517283",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d217588c-edaf-4aaa-94bb-22569f8558fb",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a\u0632\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7759a923-b084-4eee-af16-8be4a542dee1",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a\u0632\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646\u0639\u0634\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d8a9c393-1db0-4209-820a-77ec55b17c25",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u064a \u0646\u0648\u0639 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "74c07034-ae00-45cc-8f48-1804342bbd3e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0648\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0f447bfe-652c-427e-8ab0-98cb7780ac59",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "60bc50b2-27c7-477d-acc4-33b58b764569",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0631\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "01d69650-bf6a-4f30-8bb4-137056b45f15",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c84d6fdb-9051-498c-9d7c-7063a9c1abf3",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0635\u062d\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "22f67a17-d49e-4bbb-894d-b35112f11d78",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0635\u062d\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "56894edd-50d3-4119-8dde-31fd95153e94",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6b803424-6640-4d15-9933-1fbc874cb2aa",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0a74b058-e365-42dd-bb8f-7ad7a2d97836",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0634\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0648\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "33631635-3e38-4497-983f-123119f20adc",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u064a\u0634\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "635a8b79-a7c2-4806-85a2-2ff6028ed339",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u064a\u0634\u0645\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "99b831c7-dbff-422a-8459-b46539814d45",
      "question": "\u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u062f\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7bfec21d-ea05-47db-9c6d-63120455b43f",
      "question": "\u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u062f\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3a2994c7-7378-403d-b43e-39b44a929942",
      "question": "\u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c \u0642\u062f\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b83b9c91-b50a-40be-905c-19b03c5de0b7",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u064a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0627 \u0642\u0648\u0627\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0641\u0627\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cd8cbe6d-7946-4f3a-b2f5-d0e8b309637b",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0641\u0627\u0644 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0648\u0627\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "53306c7a-59b1-448c-aa7f-b135493576c9",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0647\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0645\u0646\u0627\u0633\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "252da6f9-51cd-4510-a3db-75f5ea348014",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0647\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fcc5af4e-d8fd-4d58-af6c-19bb44c84e1c",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0648\u0633\u0627\u0626\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u0627\u0632\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fe6dcade-dd16-4a92-8e66-4d8cf7f79246",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0633\u0627\u0626\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0627\u0632\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c53d3377-793c-4f3e-b0d7-c01244887b5f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c \u0645\u0647\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9c139dba-891c-4505-859c-daff28ccbff2",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0647\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0631\u0643\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a0c3163f-90d0-4018-a251-a21e53de203b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u0648\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0643\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "692873d8-3e60-4253-a149-c8af76c431c5",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u0648\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0643\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e4bcac24-b8f4-4f81-bda6-d2b7cb497720",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0631 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2d8e2cd9-072a-4c06-b409-5f8133723dc2",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u064a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0631 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0631\u0627\u0621\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3bfa730b-b1ce-4445-93a0-725035e7608e",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0631 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0637\u0627\u0644\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "82edf743-cefc-44c5-86c8-a20b6d66ce85",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0642\u0637",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "be3be402-c14e-4592-9398-7109fcbae700",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f\u0629 \u0641\u0642\u0637",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f41780cc-5d48-4682-abec-53576e12c352",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u064a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0623\u0628\u0642\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "10937206-211f-46b6-aa7e-b22ebee4e069",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u064a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a3a7e2a0-223c-4b6c-ae75-0260cfe1cdfa",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d048f1ac-b4ad-40b9-8bd2-4e04245fdf48",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647\u0627 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f9e61104-fbdf-46b1-9314-4c7b0f556653",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062c\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "497db2e3-66e7-40ac-bbb9-1f096ec528ee",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "111ee23e-f133-41ba-912b-4310633e70f2",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "057a0527-b2e7-4361-9163-c9cfe098763a",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f418000e-7454-4ce2-afcc-a51b33b7836c",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d38a9672-61d4-45a5-812e-dba31571ec87",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0647\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2dc39f07-fed6-458a-85e3-12c01b3cc1de",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062d\u0628\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0bda1565-34a7-491c-a41b-c2993c5d9d55",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062d\u0628\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "23154b81-c5a7-497c-96ce-fd4eee653413",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643\u061f - \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2ea7ba78-b3a2-4bc7-9f8e-855121e3055b",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f - \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u0634\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "85d6b01e-e291-403b-aa10-3be29ff035bc",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u062e\u064a\u0631\u061f - \u0646\u0639\u0645\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4abcf597-f338-4fcb-b7d8-6fb846fbc830",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0628\u062e\u064a\u0631\u061f - \u0646\u0639\u0645\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ef09e8bb-1014-44cc-bc6a-c899f64eff90",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f - \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ee680aa8-231f-43a5-9e7e-3d882424242c",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u0643\u061f - \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0647\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "914f8244-9bf0-48ad-bb64-e18f3f87a62f",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0637\u0641\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0647\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c08f85c3-e693-485f-9eb6-4359a0df284c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0637\u0641\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0c4ed56d-ad19-4a12-b0d4-eb1bf39e4fae",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0621\u061f - \u0646\u0639\u0645\u060c \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ff425280-1572-46b7-a525-f563d21935cf",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0643\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f - \u0646\u0639\u0645\u060c \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0621\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ebe73c78-2191-45e6-bed5-8dbcb905f449",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0643\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0621\u061f - \u0646\u0639\u0645\u060c \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5749da48-3392-4326-88f4-baf629d250f6",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0632\u0627\u0626\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0646\u062d\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fe64cfec-c0c4-4324-bb3e-f35401a5e661",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0632\u0627\u0626\u0631 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d1edd33b-7c17-44a2-8a17-2c8403668e0e",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0632\u0627\u0626\u0631 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a1d7a6ec-d642-421e-a662-ee0504ca125c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0648\u0641\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0635\u0639\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c3e91997-8a79-4ee2-adcd-4259dfb4662b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0644\u064a \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0648\u0641\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f7bc4fb1-45ff-420a-a08d-2bbfe1776e41",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0646 \u0644\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9c738b43-719e-46d8-977a-6ebe7943de86",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0646 \u0644\u0643 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8fb89590-4f6a-4c17-a3e8-34653d8db864",
      "question": "\u0644\u0645 \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u064a \u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7b177fee-b082-4298-8e42-e158f422fca7",
      "question": "\u0644\u0645 \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0644\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0648\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fdf36069-89c3-4339-9906-85c302a93ce1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0644\u064a \u0623\u064a \u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2e4cf44e-e7ab-4fc1-86b3-2ef576d61526",
      "question": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u062f\u062e\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6de73c34-3508-412c-b351-42f846479703",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062f\u062e\u0648\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "db755432-eaf5-4681-a61b-2ef65d181a8a",
      "question": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0628\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "051f27ef-f9ec-4642-bedc-8351d4ee5a78",
      "question": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0634\u0631\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627\u062d\u0642",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9abc8ad5-55b0-4ab6-a01b-647de2aefaf1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0d22ca16-dfa1-4f47-b5b1-16e8a39653cd",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "07a0ab79-8569-429e-8c67-0f9778d8df9f",
      "question": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062c\u0644\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1b2f9f0b-e699-42d5-9d13-3de60046aaf2",
      "question": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "25891671-1251-43c7-84b7-68f1cbdb2363",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4fc391ca-7008-4084-aafc-a5d2aa28a5bb",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7a99c2f5-3a4c-4e15-89a3-89a795369d9e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0648\u062c\u0647\u0646\u064a \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "96c6755c-5c75-4e9b-843f-af8506547374",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0648\u062c\u0647\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2909b51e-9102-40cb-89e3-1eb3e7cae246",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0632\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "70f2386b-5855-4317-904c-f6a02d8bca07",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e9978282-8f73-4c2c-807e-06a0c6ae5d82",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0647\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ef5b47b7-8005-4b70-98cc-10807b37e4b1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646\u0630",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "847d0c3e-21cd-4383-b0dd-6007295ea4d1",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7988f5ca-e8c7-41ce-a1e8-43fe652c418f",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0630\u0627\u0647\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0635\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8aff7b3f-bc35-4442-97b7-a2647b662a8d",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0630\u0627\u0647\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u062d\u0635\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "628b4c02-f9e7-4557-9c0f-29412d4f2ba1",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2096d693-b462-4a39-b884-7833a2050519",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0632\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6dd4e702-683b-4422-b92a-e30645c17eba",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ffd73a9d-ed03-40f3-8513-d3272c01d720",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0631\u0627\u0621\u062a\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f639a722-68a1-4447-8ec7-02a3ddfe3b06",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0631\u0627\u0621\u062a\u0647\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0642\u0637",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6d1a5da3-a3bb-4f99-81ad-904e00daf807",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a \u0644\u0648\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u0628\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9d4a4c3a-67bc-407e-a0b4-fda2155855b9",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0644\u0644\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0642\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e28a6873-3889-46c5-81e5-3aba4e062f48",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0644\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0642\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d163c13f-cc7e-4b95-b9f4-6194b0ba5ba6",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0642\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "068f60cf-831c-487d-99ec-2c0db2b2a24c",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cabb7608-91c3-429c-9e72-e05dd8d5a4f8",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2906d6ac-0a02-4033-a27d-14742014977b",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c5c5cd7b-3fc1-44db-ad9e-7f47273ae6ae",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a208f33f-cbae-447c-a978-aaa883e2dca2",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a2f5898f-2ee0-47c6-be00-a846eebec753",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2e10b67a-5a3d-4efc-8c38-2cababdd308c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0645\u062a \u0628\u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u064a \u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u0645\u0624\u062e\u0631\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u0641\u0644\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "833b6442-cfc3-4b23-ab32-86ef0b9d05b6",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0642\u0645\u062a \u0628\u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u064a \u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0624\u062e\u0631\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "409e8a9f-b338-44f4-a77c-ffddc72f7103",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0648\u062f \u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u062a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8b1e09c1-b529-4e97-8e78-6147cbdd0132",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u062a\u0648\u062f \u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u062a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e17e888a-b9aa-44ab-ac0f-4154bded4106",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u062a\u0648\u062f \u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u062a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f64e1aac-862e-4a35-896e-7b944f2358df",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0641\u0631 \u0648\u0627\u0633\u062a\u0643\u0634\u0627\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6b05befc-e9ea-4925-b5ac-0d7be44d4f13",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0641\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u0633\u062a\u0643\u0634\u0627\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bba36744-7dce-44a5-b7f2-42e4b391c7ef",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0641\u0631 \u0648\u0627\u0633\u062a\u0643\u0634\u0627\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5d09551d-66a7-4e18-941d-13b875eeae9f",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u0642\u0645\u062a \u0628\u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u062a\u0647\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2cc63be9-619b-4d4a-9928-4247d327d3d0",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u062a\u0647\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0645\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "299608c7-7f6f-4ba5-864d-8aee9dd1357d",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u062d\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0635\u0631 \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "494c89a4-cd49-40e0-8371-20e12865047d",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u062d\u064a\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ceb9463b-1208-4bad-9476-31fc072a1cf3",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0632\u0648\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0624\u062e\u0631\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "31ee7ddc-06bf-40cb-974d-174c7e10cd9a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0632\u0648\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f0ce5f48-31fd-4686-ae61-85ef7029730b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0627\u0636",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0646\u062f\u0648\u0642",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c4eaad40-44f1-4add-a948-b740d80693df",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0646\u062f\u0648\u0642 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0636",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "04a9321b-bb38-41fd-ba50-4cb7ea42e2c4",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0644\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a\u061f - \u0622\u0633\u0641\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0627\u0636",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1e82b347-fcca-47a1-a687-2e51351c33f3",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0644\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0644\u064a\u061f - \u0622\u0633\u0641\u060c \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0636",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4b8a2936-da0b-4aa2-9e58-d45e5ddfc733",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0644\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0644\u064a\u061f - \u0622\u0633\u0641\u060c \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0641\u0627\u0636",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0a8af975-cc8b-4949-9b59-4eb0bfc88518",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "09294dca-96d5-4979-af35-e9aeb39b9009",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ae359f20-a1a0-426d-924e-04b0ce82f496",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0641\u062d\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0644\u0648\u0645\u0627\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "65bc6f70-cf9c-4e1e-b68d-e7af6081c4d4",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cd21a3b2-5b19-46f9-9982-de161e2bd7b7",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e5e57fa1-e5f5-481b-9f38-68e39c6e4b82",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c4e8ba6e-d885-4d28-bdde-973665e95b62",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "22d86418-30c5-43c4-8c79-57370298a4a9",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u0628\u0642\u0649 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u062d\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1ad10b3d-528a-4e9d-bcf6-f5bd53329d1f",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u0628\u0642\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0627\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7a87c7fd-2277-44ce-8956-25e25364774c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0623\u0628\u0642\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0627\u062a\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "689e5403-94c2-47f0-932b-84ce74dec41a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0646\u062c\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0622\u0633\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e4c528a5-13d1-47e1-b192-703df58955f7",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0644\u062d\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u062c\u0627\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3f9c0df3-e164-4583-9b2a-9924b78a564c",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0646\u062c\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0635\u0645\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5f17d38d-cb2e-4c58-be8c-98eb1ea5735f",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0646\u062a\u0638\u0627\u0631 \u0644\u062d\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f23fb270-691c-4e19-bef7-b61d1cec9b88",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0627\u0646\u062a\u0638\u0627\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2285d7c4-8cbc-4603-885c-b3fbf106c0b6",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u062a\u0630\u0647\u0628\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "566fe0c1-4875-47f4-a826-38ea876ef151",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0633\u062a\u064a\u0642\u0638 \u0639\u0627\u062f\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f4a87baa-af70-4fbe-9cd4-4904652aae60",
      "question": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u064a\u0642\u0638 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u062f\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d61d0702-cf1e-4b52-b831-6c5a752b8380",
      "question": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5de1df21-8660-427c-bb9f-9899ad36b410",
      "question": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "37b9c0e3-ace4-4f73-ab62-f6887ac68f53",
      "question": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0e7cfc85-b6fd-4c5a-946d-96a6b52a347f",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062d\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0637\u0648\u0627\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b02137cf-43f0-40d6-a1f0-5a3c70cca0d2",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062d\u0644 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0637\u0648\u0627\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0640",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3c1feea8-1865-4e4a-aaf0-8b25f0999be4",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062d\u0644 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d \u0637\u0648\u0627\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2430ecb8-bc79-4802-91bd-64a549195048",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9b942cfa-aa84-4f35-ba7d-9d72b4db393c",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u062a\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "06e07e19-efa6-40d4-b22d-e79bccbf7afb",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d \u062d\u062a\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3105735e-dfd4-4ee9-928d-e11045a517e8",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0644\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cf12b789-232d-4e8d-893e-c162431ea8aa",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0644\u0628 \u0644\u064a \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0634\u0631\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "27e0c4a8-5a14-40aa-892c-145a234973b4",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062c\u0644\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0635\u0628\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a21e6ff3-cc6d-41e1-b5d2-0171c792c1e4",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062c\u0644\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "27c0e1fd-b8bb-4834-aa9e-c9c9b2780e4c",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062c\u0644\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "72e4a828-b134-40d2-8456-2d165eb9a87f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062c\u0644\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c30cd762-4017-4ca7-b64e-8fe9de66bd66",
      "question": "\u062c\u0644\u0628\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u063a\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1095d4bc-5f39-4c68-a418-95d2f6a3dafc",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0639\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0644\u0628\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "25e10674-d0c0-43bc-b874-36bd6399b7b7",
      "question": "\u062c\u0644\u0628\u062a \u0645\u0639\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "64acecca-c3d2-45f3-8b4b-237742c52d10",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1a531482-b938-442e-b861-f999f7843fea",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3e4fffc2-3dc2-4706-b343-19158b7cad84",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0642\u0648\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062c\u0645\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5ab89b00-7b4c-4fa6-bb27-13f3559939b3",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0642\u0648\u0645 \u0628\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0143d431-66f4-4e55-a36b-61ac31cb21bd",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0644\u062a\u0632\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "352710dc-7557-48cf-a687-29b27105a236",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0644\u062a\u0632\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "65b6c0bc-23ed-4797-8d34-a8e49eea5585",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "35314e59-77f1-4ddc-9583-2f32ecd7c238",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4a991c8e-6d04-46f4-ad29-209aea4914e7",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0648\u0644\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0623\u062a\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4d7e72cd-7ea4-4ef6-aca8-bca1c89ff0b7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0623\u062a\u064a \u0623\u0648\u0644\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3acfd6e0-a7c7-4c83-8afd-654fde0bab64",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062f\u0627\u0621 \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "164f49f3-5264-413a-b171-3b2b736211c5",
      "question": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062f\u0627\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "62f862e6-4296-4ae7-8ec8-039929322de9",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0646\u062f\u0642 \u064a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1329c6d4-a793-44fa-ae9a-a4217e973436",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0646\u062f\u0642 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0628\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "10f001ca-bd18-4718-9524-5e8c75859901",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0646\u062f\u0642 \u064a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fdfb5c0a-e18f-4e73-a408-0f024c5eb03c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0638\u0647\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ee0d713d-4975-489f-aafb-cf92ee721ae5",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0638\u0647\u0631 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a65ed3a5-0e17-47b9-8a01-f4716184ff53",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0638\u0647\u0631 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "975de28e-bce7-4a9f-be6a-961afdae182d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062b\u0644\u0627\u062b \u063a\u0631\u0641 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u0648\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "26b5d23c-b668-449b-885d-066b61fa8fc0",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0627 \u062b\u0644\u0627\u062b \u063a\u0631\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a611304e-dc28-43ad-af59-cbb08d01f46a",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0627 \u062b\u0644\u0627\u062b \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u063a\u0631\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "964fd8e6-c762-4e0f-b5b3-0925abbef9a6",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0623\u0642\u064a\u0645 \u0641\u064a\u0647\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0634\u0643\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4183f251-9d37-43ed-860c-434ea4cbf5f0",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u0633\u0623\u0642\u064a\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0647\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d7855cb0-3abc-48e7-99cc-58ad4b89e937",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0645\u0631\u064a\u062d\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "28d02b7a-704b-4d84-9102-e0a9ee9ef847",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0645\u0631\u064a\u062d\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "37279e85-c115-46a0-988f-7ee2605e62d9",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0646\u0638\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7db7b241-9548-45d6-a11f-18f744150121",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0646\u0638\u064a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "500d3b77-d096-434a-af54-ecf638011a6e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4f36cd51-54e4-4096-afd1-d0494e493bda",
      "question": "\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0627\u0642\u062a\u0631\u0627\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "23aa36e3-ba0d-4491-b257-e3a90545d695",
      "question": "\u064a\u0646 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0627\u062d\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f5cb9c1e-f108-4ae4-ae0f-491d00e2edf7",
      "question": "\u064a\u0646 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0627\u062d\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0c33d684-6c74-4c43-ae4b-338539cc5809",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0630\u0647\u0628\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f9fbe982-d282-4d9c-b3bb-a101a0024bf5",
      "question": "\u064a\u0646 \u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0630\u0647\u0628\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5b110372-d88b-4341-91bb-7945dfee6062",
      "question": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0631\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4cc28054-c502-4247-98f0-9436400ff291",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "539e8275-a567-4679-9e26-1e1aea92a5b5",
      "question": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "28ddb321-0a74-48f8-910e-139c527860ee",
      "question": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0628\u062f\u0623",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "df923431-31d8-42f5-ad41-64b1b4f55160",
      "question": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b32da7df-c17a-44ba-a8b1-6c083668ce45",
      "question": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dce04b55-52d9-47fd-8bd5-e80ae8dab145",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0632\u064a\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b8fa973d-2de4-4fee-966f-77b796dfcd73",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0632\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "452f0f5a-63cb-4e9a-923d-fef4db20ba5d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0631\u0633\u0627\u0644\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "00e0f592-8075-4c04-ad1a-a14d534e9754",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d3c5ed7f-94cd-448e-ab76-fa48d7e2f184",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "09546b19-3097-47c8-855e-1e7c435f325e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u062e\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e9a2313b-3c0a-436d-ba0e-76a6852b3651",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ea66158e-cf6d-4b17-bf84-a57b15223ba5",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0630\u0647\u0627\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "26c51909-1edd-40b6-b8dd-59f9abc204c2",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u0647\u0627\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "92e5d0d1-5620-4752-b458-58cb357b382c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u0647\u0627\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e09ce156-2892-4f77-9525-8811d3d010d7",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0636",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7cbbd981-88fa-46a2-ad99-89eba7da7ec0",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0634\u063a\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6f7eac29-3e2d-432c-ae7c-dde399cf4be0",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u063a\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d74e467d-b0eb-4495-80be-14868ee4fbb4",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0645\u0634\u063a\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9921f960-65e0-4538-8a6f-ace6c6c9835c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "11727489-65cd-46e4-a7cd-3db5aed81585",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4cc31b8d-b00a-4403-a353-8fbc1bdf36f4",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0638\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3528118a-0fb1-4806-8987-07a357696fa5",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0646\u0638\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a\u0632\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2396524b-e286-4f13-a75f-8d0920c9b2d8",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f90859ea-cc6a-4c44-8b4d-4f06af80033d",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3c074d5f-ef0d-4891-9947-d53fcf2cecc7",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bcb06846-871b-4a68-9408-3eb24484dd95",
      "question": "\u0635\u0628\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "772b9fe7-273d-4efc-8bb3-993290568dcd",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0635\u0628\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "33bd216b-3cd0-4ff3-b3f7-9d16afb8f4ac",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u064a\u0642\u0638 \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0643\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0632\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c0442273-8e3d-4efe-b8c9-bf53fd28ceda",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0633\u062a\u064a\u0642\u0638 \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0643\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0628\u062f\u0623",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "772e9601-9740-46ee-96cc-94c363268a57",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u064a\u0642\u0638 \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0643\u0631\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0637\u0627\u0644\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "829ee9d0-0c1b-42d5-a6a8-502f608c7705",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0645\u0636\u064a \u0648\u0642\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0631\u0627\u0621\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "abfead86-a7b7-4035-bca8-0e29b4066410",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0645\u0636\u064a \u0648\u0642\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0631\u0627\u0621\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "de41d4ec-fafe-484f-8e52-cdcbcb5c9b26",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0645\u0636\u064a \u0648\u0642\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0631\u0627\u0621\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a56eadb7-57fb-4af2-9e10-9468c47e651c",
      "question": "\u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "17f1f978-2324-4710-8897-9937b63f9c6e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "926d164d-ce0d-4d85-bfd3-c73ae84bde67",
      "question": "\u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6016e2ba-9c11-47be-83b3-417550e1b1b6",
      "question": "\u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0627 \u062a\u062a\u0645\u0646\u0627\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "95302c9a-7ed9-4acf-8d1d-69e261a97d23",
      "question": "\u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062a\u0645\u0646\u0627\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0648\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8a6a6b3a-6619-469a-b231-8bb27573f0bb",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "040f9d86-d567-47c1-baba-44c0b55361bb",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "db4c5bf7-1552-4d43-bd4f-f8e9904e3fb0",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0627\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1a61c1f4-6914-4924-8eb1-056276156f43",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0627\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7cf5ae24-f719-4999-884d-a255db77408a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u0627\u062a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0635\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a832bd37-1d1f-4ce9-b713-bbed337923f4",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0647\u0627\u062a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f5f445be-6b4d-47be-90c0-24a740608cf9",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u0627\u062a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c1475a9f-6311-441b-81e3-642a34ecbac9",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0631\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0641\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1c887f55-aefa-47d8-a866-f69fe3b751dc",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0631\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f22db8c2-6af3-42f1-80d6-948c24f2ea2f",
      "question": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5fb008fc-eb9b-4ebd-b06b-a1646cc25dcc",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "eb584e2a-a18b-4733-a953-300f1e66685b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "238e5f71-3a72-4502-a468-cce9d2758b35",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dd4fa3d9-7b13-48fa-98e5-09917f18b43b",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a489c9b7-74a2-425a-b220-b0958728ba62",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "aa572085-3d52-48d9-b27f-71af741a2184",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "75998669-0eba-44cc-b554-0e9fd0ee40d0",
      "question": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "70a23f0a-229c-41c2-9d7d-6bf84bbf52ed",
      "question": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0635\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2f905307-2024-49a4-a802-5b0a4aa693da",
      "question": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u0646\u0635\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "221253ad-6daf-4640-a471-7e1de6478966",
      "question": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643 \u064a\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642\u064a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "98034de7-69b9-4ff8-97f5-878b463ab0a5",
      "question": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b4970114-f430-44b4-bebf-7093c4aa0488",
      "question": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0628\u064a\u0628\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "caea83c6-0bb0-4443-b82e-0d2dc61d44f9",
      "question": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643 \u064a\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0628\u064a\u0628\u064a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b1a2a8a6-5cc6-4a73-80da-41363902f339",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0628\u062e\u064a\u0631\u061f - \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ee9707b0-56c3-437b-af0d-308d3defc10c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0628\u062e\u064a\u0631\u061f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "-",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5caea768-20c7-4a6d-bed0-211110329fc9",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a\u061f - \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e574eb76-81c0-41ce-aab9-408f1b791bb7",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a\u061f - \u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u062a\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "01e1f1dd-6108-44c5-a434-7e9194ef162a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a\u061f - \u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "511fbe69-58d4-4886-92d7-3d40b05b0807",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f - \u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8e518224-040e-4c83-8f02-5bab0a60d7bb",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f - \u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0627\u064a\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "636287de-663f-4641-8d48-9f881516c1d9",
      "question": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ac56c398-5d03-4ea8-a7dd-4a23f1f717c4",
      "question": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633 \u064a\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642\u064a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fa0e0db0-96a2-4376-952a-afcc93be6742",
      "question": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6e1d7cb5-4bfa-43da-9dff-1133d4960c67",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b6a3fd95-c031-44bc-98a4-336dae01cde1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5971a98a-b477-49bf-bf86-4e8ec147e98e",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a9cdd8b9-5be6-4eb5-bad4-d32bf68df6fd",
      "question": "\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "27f83289-fbe0-4a3a-ba64-21e65b446f49",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "42e7437c-6fa2-44f5-a66e-5d5c4fa8b0e1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0639 \u0639\u0627\u0626\u0644\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c5d71035-6b49-46b2-a889-eb4a9313fc77",
      "question": "\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0645\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0626\u0644\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "996eed0f-2ad6-4dd4-9743-09790c6905ab",
      "question": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "45835551-a96d-41bf-9290-f855a309faea",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "523f5ed5-43a9-4dd8-9e77-ae683babccbe",
      "question": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0645\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "eaa235e3-8b64-4ad2-923a-ebfb6233f839",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0639 \u0645\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u062d\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "10b952c9-d88a-4120-8594-67f4823a0941",
      "question": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f4dddcc3-2cf0-40fe-bcf3-b06d452f1de6",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0634\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0622\u0633\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7df82aca-b90a-4569-a9a5-ce8c6b32744d",
      "question": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0645\u062a\u0646\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d1ca5dd0-d1fa-4a43-972f-f4be01a4eace",
      "question": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u0631\u0648\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "15f09153-d03f-4a67-86f2-1641d95d4708",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u064a\u0634 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cbf8f469-1b8b-43e5-9eaa-5ceae5adb7d6",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u064a\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "44a82611-d976-40e0-9660-c4dd54c529ce",
      "question": "\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0627\u0635\u0645\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b387b49d-7456-4814-ace2-7eaa1e690b02",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u064a \u0639\u0627\u0635\u0645\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7aef05f7-e2d9-40ff-a015-d9d3c1ff35f3",
      "question": "\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629 \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062b\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2a83c9e9-e056-4eb7-ac15-f3ce825413d3",
      "question": "\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629 \u0648\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062b\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b83a5d79-cd9d-4385-96f0-231bad86d867",
      "question": "\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062b\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "10a326cb-8ef1-4367-8eef-7806f1a4cce9",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0639\u064a\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f028a584-2785-4883-b6b8-9fc878dd3d97",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u064a\u0634 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "578f9790-1ca3-417e-a571-8a570d2e23f4",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u0639\u0627\u0635\u0645\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "afbc2943-16d8-4602-b3f7-e2999052c8d0",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0627\u0635\u0645\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1a89caf3-0a61-4a9f-ac32-3eb9088e9157",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0635\u0645\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ba38161d-4ad8-455d-a26b-efe53e61f4b0",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0636\u0631\u064a\u0629 \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "48a89eea-d3d8-41e8-bb99-b24ac6236c70",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0636\u0631\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8b510a08-58b7-47fc-bb91-d734a8f01877",
      "question": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a0ffa344-7093-45c2-8fd2-4acc9215b977",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bf49fcbd-e67a-404d-87a0-562b8d5f0c7c",
      "question": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0644\u0648\u0645\u0627\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fcbab866-ea2b-44a3-8fc2-899739ab4e3b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5474371a-4518-4f19-9678-dfdadbefc9e7",
      "question": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a749ecc8-a168-4664-b3ae-5069f14f18d5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0625\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7bb6b733-0e24-4307-92db-8babcc21eed0",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0637\u0627\u0644\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7fab7179-c58c-41fb-b0c0-bfffa9642ff0",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0142b65f-856d-4a07-969e-ec7f774e94c9",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3d9d3d88-aaa5-41bc-9a93-4807251ab233",
      "question": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2af4a38a-6acf-4997-bb5e-af916a9f4189",
      "question": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634 \u0643\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "48c05ad5-1315-43c2-8c68-4058f7300413",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0641\u0633\u064a\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f5cb527c-63e6-4aed-b199-b880b49cc19c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a \u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ac5be64e-9f14-4416-aaf3-046169af60ca",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "77387d3d-4128-497d-b196-1bef728132f2",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a \u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8bfb234f-3fac-4364-9425-7f8b61ab019c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0639\u062a\u0645\u062f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7e6588a0-5ca0-4b58-9505-15c535d8b355",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u062a\u0645\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "809c46a3-8ad2-42d8-9df8-e22cc0f12cfa",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9b3fa0e3-7e13-43e2-bbdf-43d7fe5b1e44",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ee4ad3e5-2020-458e-a94b-90e2bd03b7dd",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d66cf2d9-9f80-412e-80d2-cae924d04bb8",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u0629 \u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4a2b4e1d-e552-488d-a172-5f7276b4b6d7",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u0629 \u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f05a8c49-87f2-4c92-a694-bf63b58479c6",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a30ad47e-863a-4561-be0d-626b0525a8ed",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0633\u0645\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a1a4e2b4-8ff5-4005-ba45-6a2f249294b1",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0645\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646\u0630",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2d3c599e-e780-4e70-b34c-a63cea9f92c6",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0633\u0645\u064a \u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "25e31f2b-0cdc-45ff-9966-500f939dc3a7",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ea7fff5d-a51c-40a3-9fdd-6224a0f7dc9d",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "08fd282c-9217-4300-a1f2-2ce1404888b4",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 \u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7307cac6-e73a-41f2-b0e2-fecd2a6efcee",
      "question": "\u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "06105089-f520-465d-b01b-b3a157e55e4c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1624d311-f10f-4959-9ae4-206a181674ca",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a1d32789-4715-485f-9526-f66022cbe330",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5dc77ebc-ef61-4f20-ae65-0e647f3cbf90",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641 \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0b124238-b7a5-4363-a75d-e372bd13467c",
      "question": "\u0643\u0645 \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e38ba846-4db7-435c-b5c1-fd7406929412",
      "question": "\u0643\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "73e86113-f869-4a87-8b74-6222b0bf2d4e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ee54e42a-71ef-44a8-a6ad-2439c45760e6",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "baa247a9-4153-4f4d-872c-0f809c62159a",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u0645\u0647\u0645\u0629 \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4ff1e553-ca96-4760-862a-4bde4f52f581",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u064a \u0645\u0647\u0645\u0629 \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621 \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "58f3ead2-24e8-4c45-9b7b-4a65cdf3e90e",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0647\u0645\u0629 \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621 \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ca72f1d6-06e4-4852-85c6-4d458fa59030",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u062f\u0645\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "024db548-8279-43d1-befd-147d65b8141b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u062f\u0645\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b39ce4b8-7753-40f1-b468-eaf44982ad40",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0642\u0644\u064a\u0644 \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0638\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0a5b968b-7278-40d9-9257-663fa4d155e2",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0638\u0627\u0645 \u062a\u0642\u0644\u064a\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fd66fee1-7b66-4a1c-b35d-a09251c05f2c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0638\u0627\u0645 \u062a\u0642\u0644\u064a\u0644 \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4e0014ba-1ec8-47ec-9c14-e09d5236f224",
      "question": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0627\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0648\u0645\u0627 \u0628\u0639\u062f \u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0632\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "91a3c013-cfa3-4def-beea-feb9b2103b67",
      "question": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0632\u064a\u062f \u064a\u0648\u0645\u0627 \u0628\u0639\u062f \u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0627\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7a38c537-1a7c-4684-8cff-7c05ebf47acd",
      "question": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0627\u0629 \u062a\u0632\u064a\u062f \u064a\u0648\u0645\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0639\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u0631\u0648\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "952975bd-bff9-4bb3-a0da-e495115b5239",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u0642\u0627\u0628\u0644\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "beb2dcef-866b-4944-bd3a-1431808b9ed4",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u0642\u0627\u0628\u0644\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u064a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "356df7ea-fce9-4665-938e-72f1d17240fa",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u0642\u0627\u0628\u0644\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u064a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "57666dc9-87be-4b53-8f24-a761d16bb5d7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0648\u0627\u0639\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "54156476-713b-4c6a-bc91-176151fea524",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631 \u0645\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "69610357-9193-4764-8bf0-3b0aa9aa334f",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631 \u0645\u0627 \u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "74d06e22-bd34-4ef2-b5af-413464e6ae70",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u0627\u0632\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ad50c8a8-112e-4b76-989c-ae1bb4ce61fa",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "33abc8e0-90f9-4ae2-beed-cd56ba2fb8a6",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062f\u062e\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f8bd58a8-45a8-4fa2-ae81-ad96d7f52377",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u062e\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "557e8c59-8cec-4e7e-9824-ac39f36e23eb",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u062e\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "93f80b45-1573-4d83-95f5-7cf278ac69d7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u062d\u062c\u0632 \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0627\u0626\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u0633\u0628\u0642\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0641\u0644\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4bbe30dc-d84c-4e97-94be-774d43043ee2",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u062d\u062c\u0632 \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0627\u0626\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0628\u0642\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7184a5e1-f9c3-46ee-bb1a-e9f1565c8c47",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u062d\u062c\u0632 \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0627\u0626\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u0633\u0628\u0642\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "114e4c03-0cd7-403d-9e5d-70ec6cb07133",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "86e69994-12ae-46be-8129-01d13e8fc28f",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u0631\u0648\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b0d01cca-ca51-4de6-ad30-6ebf5b4725d1",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0623\u062e\u0630\u0646\u064a \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "90345799-ac59-4d08-88c2-0e2ad2edf67e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0623\u062e\u0630\u0646\u064a \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6134cc0a-6fa5-4e84-89fd-cdbd4de2c203",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0623\u062e\u0630\u0646\u064a \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7f120042-18a2-46bd-ab96-fab9455737d0",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1ff0f48c-de76-4e84-95a5-21fbb7fd82c0",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "50a406f0-d5f3-4f01-bcc9-7e2e187e7501",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e9a8ffd7-de55-4417-a221-5cd33aa7ccc3",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0647\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0645\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "70df42da-0fb6-4b6e-b4fc-a68d8b9911be",
      "question": "\u0623\u0645\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0647\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9db2e8d4-c598-425b-9080-51a79841a957",
      "question": "\u0623\u0645\u064a \u0647\u064a \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0634\u062e\u0635 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2ae64773-ca28-4c71-92ed-db18bf4df4ae",
      "question": "\u0623\u0645\u064a \u0647\u064a \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u062e\u0635",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5fc6e3c9-1d29-432c-abc0-cb7d9769343c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u064a \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0634\u062e\u0635 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0645\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0641\u062d\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8ee02e46-1747-4708-adbd-eaf6f4019a6f",
      "question": "\u0623\u0645\u064a \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0645 \u0644\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0643\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "82ce8490-f0d7-434a-b8b4-dbad12f3379a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0645 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0645\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a1a85285-ce82-47f4-b098-f876fddcc559",
      "question": "\u0643\u0627\u0645 \u0623\u062e \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a238e92e-98ed-4188-8b67-9ec8b4db24f4",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062e \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0647\u0627\u062a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "10424f92-71a8-449d-babf-919d9d2958ad",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0627\u0639\u0629 \u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8438a411-5d42-4aa3-a765-fe224efbd591",
      "question": "\u0643\u0627\u0645 \u0633\u0627\u0639\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "db10e599-ee59-4cef-91eb-0c81c6fb7f34",
      "question": "\u0643\u0627\u0645 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623\u0647\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a36b3493-7d62-4c9c-8859-b544d2779a62",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062f\u0631\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a0cf9a4b-051a-44c5-9f5c-60380874860e",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0d549794-e5da-4759-a14f-e5a08c873679",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5a9aec6b-ca54-4700-bf65-4cc3479d6720",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u062f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d67576c7-af57-4915-8223-7a7afceeef7d",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u062f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b8e49285-7098-4b7a-9f5e-57414da1f229",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u063a\u062f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "23bd653d-5679-4d4b-b6c6-372fd4fc1035",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639\u064b\u0627 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "93e55116-4e3f-4a5f-915b-8fdf365360d5",
      "question": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0645\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "be03d61d-f8fb-47a7-9dbf-f6f76771d47f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0628\u062f\u0623",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9265af3a-47e1-4687-8be3-a028eb23dc9d",
      "question": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0645\u062a\u062d\u0627\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627\u062c\u062a\u064a\u0627\u0632",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "06dafc2a-c11c-4c14-bc09-71ca3b92152c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0627\u062c\u062a\u064a\u0627\u0632 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0645\u062a\u062d\u0627\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fa007a2d-990a-4547-a92e-a4190d35fb61",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "94936bc1-a10f-4302-8bb3-f3808c2191b6",
      "question": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0639\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c4249202-33bc-4eb4-af7d-fe9b087f5e02",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "56da21ab-7128-472e-ac9d-e580d4e537d8",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ea80b49d-4da8-4e73-abc1-5ce1004be65f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f1825362-a53a-41b0-bb9f-bdfd7bb14033",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 \u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0644\u0644\u0635\u0644\u0627\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d4a3cc5b-0135-438a-932c-736c9605a72f",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u0647\u0648 \u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0635\u0644\u0627\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8f7e4f0f-853e-4b2a-a4e5-fe3db5b30b13",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ed9a6152-effb-4ebf-a7df-5e0693822a89",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b2a3559a-4386-42c6-ba35-3b98d5daa1de",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0621\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "23e993ae-4fc3-46ae-9a3e-bc75783ff35b",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0645 \u0639\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u062f\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "07259458-1835-410e-98f4-d1bafd373e41",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0645 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0644\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4efaa61f-cb82-4a17-9872-c4fc798b3ce7",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0632\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "90e8f5aa-f6f7-4c4f-b628-576fa6c31a26",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "86090d44-4c3b-4e7b-9959-560f19135a33",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0635\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5f330345-2696-4033-8c15-e38af26fa152",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0635\u0631\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c0adaeee-c95f-4704-8d5d-6af8f66e2f9d",
      "question": "\u0645\u0635\u0631 \u0647\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5edcf066-cd09-4b83-b29f-84aebb9b661c",
      "question": "\u0645\u0635\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0648\u0644\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "05555227-9290-450b-a45e-c7033a9e4e45",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0647\u0627 \u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e \u0637\u0648\u064a\u0644 \u0648\u0639\u0631\u064a\u0642",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b0098593-dd81-4868-a4bc-1460a3596e45",
      "question": "\u0645\u0635\u0631 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0647\u0627 \u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0639\u0631\u064a\u0642",
      "correct_answer": "\u0637\u0648\u064a\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "75024a2b-be45-44f8-8fa2-84a557c9c9ea",
      "question": "\u0647\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "016c97ab-e703-4326-9e73-800128d6d3b4",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7365a020-6d97-41fd-9f4a-bacd11b8dbb5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629 \u0642\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0631\u0623\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c25b498d-b992-49bf-bdb3-1e1d89b3784f",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u0648\u0645\u062a\u0646\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3147e5ba-03ab-4b99-8a1a-000e8cda86b4",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629 \u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u0648\u0645\u062a\u0646\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0631\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "293800a7-89b3-4088-b44e-34cd0042a290",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0644\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6c4075b5-99ed-423f-a0f5-6733f6ebe271",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062c\u0644\u0628 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u062a\u0627\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0fa6115e-7305-4c92-840a-9d802ab8bb94",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062a\u062c\u0644\u0628 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1a2f64d8-b186-4650-8047-fed1d5b4fefa",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062a\u062c\u0644\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0639\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fbb3d3ba-0f36-488a-a2ad-11472a47d19a",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0643 \u0644\u062a\u062c\u0644\u0628 \u0644\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "31cda47a-9982-4b8c-9f84-51d21834f57f",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062c\u0644\u0628\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u062a\u0627\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cda54dd5-2e5b-482c-a513-eab4e78a94d0",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062c\u0644\u0628\u062a \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0627\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3a76eaeb-cfc0-4a30-aca5-9deba37b1903",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0644\u0628\u062a \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "897133b2-1c0c-4008-99de-93b57f0a268f",
      "question": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0636\u0627\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u0642",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "05e8597d-827c-48d2-8ccb-bd5ec9aebfbc",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0636\u0627\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u0642",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2646d72a-2be1-4be7-8ad3-a552dcf8af33",
      "question": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0637\u0648\u0631 \u0643\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ebf4b2a2-149e-4e8e-a2a5-1e60d34bb618",
      "question": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0644 \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0637\u0648\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "57cbf3bf-910f-4471-92d4-123dd972f365",
      "question": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0644\u0648\u0645\u0627\u062a \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0631\u0646\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3c0ee624-36ea-461a-ab11-fd57773d00f1",
      "question": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0631\u0646\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0644\u0648\u0645\u0627\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623\u0647\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7e04561d-d3c1-4eaa-9d2f-4e817b1e94cf",
      "question": "\u0643\u0645 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8098c50a-39a7-40ef-98f7-73940fffea92",
      "question": "\u0643\u0645 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "db731223-618e-4f8f-a397-d67abde198a8",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0639\u0642\u0648\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0639\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "11d183a5-ffc8-49e5-ab48-c0341e34815b",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0639\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0642\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e0d0306f-cac4-4b34-9fc2-e7ee5c35a509",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0639\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u062a\u063a\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dbb4b529-5986-4f30-9ec9-5c1233a4da86",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u062f \u064a\u062a\u063a\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0639\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0631\u0635\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7f674a0f-57d9-4858-ace5-cf70e2bfd80c",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0631\u0643\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "527a891d-68eb-47c4-8383-2e200903a19a",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0631\u0643\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "439e6ca2-68dc-4799-acb1-486efb882262",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0645\u0648\u0627\u0639\u064a\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0633\u0628\u0627\u0646\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a6dfd577-6a17-4a1f-beea-fb2c35f1a6aa",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0648\u0627\u0639\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4d08f63d-a80c-43b2-8083-939f1b3e7b8e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0648\u0627\u0639\u064a\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bb04d31c-8d85-44b5-adfd-37803ff9a932",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0632\u062f\u062d\u0645 \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2d34cd2c-7ef1-4068-9a2f-dc9c333ca05c",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u0645\u0632\u062f\u062d\u0645 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "40dd3997-0145-4310-937a-68af001bbc80",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0635\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fc74843f-dd81-4f25-b488-d9c51db67863",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0623\u062e\u0630",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0623\u062d\u0627\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f38d155e-c002-4c0e-b7a3-ee374efbcbde",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0623\u062e\u0630 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e6ee0338-2dc1-46f0-abc6-ab3e3f088408",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0623\u062e\u0630 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0628\u062d\u062b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "700f04f3-6cf8-479b-96d1-a6f1c376f333",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062a\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4899720d-6865-4aba-8343-6eb93a90a29f",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u0645\u062a\u0627\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062b\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7cc4955c-90a7-4c44-af1f-e3f1f313ec52",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0627\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4a26d1f1-6c42-494a-914a-0ac26478a72c",
      "question": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3da3daaa-d638-449d-b73f-7cc6a59ecc1a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3d8cb298-5eae-43e5-863b-79bbf189cc4a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5fb517d3-e263-44d1-80b9-62e18d33a344",
      "question": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6e72af76-d608-440e-aaca-420f05ea2ae9",
      "question": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0627\u0644\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u064a\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629 \u0643\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "75512c48-9767-48c1-861a-97eead827e25",
      "question": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0627\u0644\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0644 \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0631\u064a\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "19e614f2-a79a-4bfc-8081-930f0bb0acbe",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0627\u0644\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u064a\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629 \u0643\u0644 \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "570d7eeb-d8b5-4f0e-8692-5dd5a9019a25",
      "question": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "148e32e2-9580-42f5-bbb5-db574bcf4bdd",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3b4dcf65-438c-4c2f-a1b3-6b8aba3be67c",
      "question": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0627\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0627\u0644\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5a48486b-a6f7-427b-968c-8589b1437c06",
      "question": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0627\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f5d5af01-f7fe-4c06-a0d5-8abd6f8aadad",
      "question": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0627\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4a936c9c-47c7-455f-935a-a371e270c9a7",
      "question": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628\u0629 \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062d\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "48dcdb33-d595-4878-b602-72ba550868a5",
      "question": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062d\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9675c93a-26a5-4bbe-b966-8fd69dde1cdc",
      "question": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628\u0629 \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062d\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d6eb792c-0abf-4e77-8366-c6a66ecd94ae",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0632\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u062a\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "369bb755-07d3-4186-bfe9-fbe533752b7c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0627\u062a\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0632\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "02ed00be-2054-490d-9337-f5986f76b7a9",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0648\u0627\u0646 \u0645\u062a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9037a387-f2e1-4dea-955e-442ffa2f79da",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0648\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ffcaaa41-1899-471c-a9c2-70aca21dd605",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0648\u0627\u0646 \u0645\u062a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "76bed275-1e12-4dfb-80b3-0393f0e49a69",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0627\u062a\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0c5c5b86-d0c6-4cc3-b74e-eac16939acc4",
      "question": "\u0646\u0645\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0637\u0648\u0627\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8e1950aa-511a-4cf3-ae29-9ba747ffef94",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0637\u0648\u0627\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0645\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "83766b2a-108a-4205-98bc-a5d1d45f2941",
      "question": "\u0646\u0645\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cb90451c-f028-4495-945e-1c60df98296b",
      "question": "\u0646\u0645\u062a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "40bd21ad-ab8a-44d6-8285-6b1aeb7e52d4",
      "question": "\u0646\u0645\u062a \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0645\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dbd1902d-841e-499d-9c77-9e286e0937a0",
      "question": "\u0644\u0645 \u0623\u0646\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f\u064b\u0627\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6153bc30-849d-474b-a59d-e37e323e242b",
      "question": "\u0644\u0645 \u0623\u0646\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "986ea81b-732b-46a6-82de-cd6227a71f9d",
      "question": "\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0631\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e7bb2ca0-2d18-42e2-9c5e-56f650288cc9",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0644\u063a\u062f\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "93f273ce-7b90-429d-a5e6-754408c49aee",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0644\u0644\u063a\u062f\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "07ad156f-ff17-431e-bf7b-3821c782f7a3",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0648\u0627\u0643\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ec16b6f3-1da4-407f-9ef5-f659adeb9923",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0648\u0627\u0643\u0647 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0637\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d540f16c-404e-4b71-8300-88c78638257e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "18957770-bd26-4aec-a8b6-fddcaa731c24",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0645\u0646\u0627\u0633\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5418d204-d376-4d9c-aad0-f541175ed795",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u062c\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "640dc7b0-622e-487a-b853-ae18b477ef82",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0631\u062c\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f3441330-f75a-41f7-8a0a-39c0d604eaa1",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f0f8e6d2-86d6-49b4-8b89-dd2523b06af1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3972b879-6d25-43a8-b4ad-4532859602ad",
      "question": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0639\u0631\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f9c9a59e-4776-498e-bffd-ebbccc32ae8c",
      "question": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646 \u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4caf186c-0c04-4998-883e-b43bc9b3ecde",
      "question": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5d475a36-7918-4548-93b3-1480535da53f",
      "question": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646 \u0646\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u063a\u0648\u0644\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c94e2bf5-989b-417c-85d8-c4e822631f25",
      "question": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "74c3659b-895b-4d3e-890c-f01b2409c67d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "511cc3a5-0e15-446b-8a26-15642ce48774",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0639\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "47cdb16a-a851-4058-90a2-c432a9c277f4",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u064a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "96b3ccde-7154-4e86-8c5d-68b280991f17",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "273e0fb7-48d8-4486-9d70-bf02edd59439",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0633\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fbcab739-1072-4635-b0aa-f8d21b428d19",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u063a\u062f\u064a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a\u0632\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2ddfd816-366f-4b13-8746-6903b1bf68a6",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u062a\u063a\u062f\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a\u0632\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2cab9992-4720-4cbe-9dd0-c75dfe33a27e",
      "question": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0647\u0649",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ffa97553-3374-4e27-af99-51f9975344a1",
      "question": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0647\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a290d40e-fb6d-4148-9c2d-7d4f93da699c",
      "question": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3869e3af-8940-4d6f-9347-9d0fda571aac",
      "question": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ae9948d9-c447-43cf-a32d-860ca181249c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0639 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1d9c042a-aaec-4964-b5fd-8362df13c18d",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646 \u0643\u0646\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f\u064b\u0627\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u0631\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b0fc75f0-775d-41b1-95a8-86acd2e78ef2",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646 \u0643\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0633\u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1162ce71-ad63-4cb8-8adf-78abb32016ec",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0648\u0643\u0648\u0644\u0627\u062a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0646\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "102e9d06-2feb-409c-a6d7-5a634eee0ba1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0646\u062a \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0648\u0643\u0648\u0644\u0627\u062a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b4c3c716-f29c-4632-bb54-dd6d176c1d51",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646 \u0643\u0646\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0648\u0643\u0648\u0644\u0627\u062a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "046f5313-26cc-472f-a2d8-a69df17e9333",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u064a \u0623\u0633\u0626\u0644\u0629\u060c \u0641\u0644\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0637\u0631\u062d\u0647\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0631\u062f\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9a9229c5-06b3-43cd-ad95-575b4722a781",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u064a \u0623\u0633\u0626\u0644\u0629\u060c \u0641\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u062a\u0631\u062f\u062f \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0637\u0631\u062d\u0647\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e48a0e03-35fd-4719-b090-57a51f8e9515",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u062a\u0631\u062f\u062f \u0641\u064a \u0637\u0631\u062d\u0647\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u0626\u0644\u0629\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1d633edc-a187-4dd0-9da0-1cb99eb64050",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c3dbb607-1f19-484b-a926-deee039905be",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a116a600-a85e-4e10-81a0-50d4b6a33072",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0646\u0638\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b9f86f3e-9844-41eb-be22-4c38739f6838",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c084093c-535f-4422-b0b6-15adb5e0eff0",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a3272a07-1451-484e-967f-a2ea9036b55b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0646\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u0636\u0631\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cd28a209-aca7-4125-91b0-38bca64c39e5",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u0628\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fc167704-7704-4f0e-bc2d-4d7e42c023bf",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0624\u0644\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "230049bf-256c-498e-af2e-c309820877ef",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0624\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4c4516b2-bf0c-486d-94df-05b5c2be8e53",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0648\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "834469d1-39d1-4d48-b020-189a4ed9f859",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0648\u0639 \u0634\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0645\u0631\u064a\u062d\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "29d1e921-692a-4b60-b826-3b5c8ad69c4d",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0639\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "41e4fdcf-1dbf-4ee9-939a-304b34ce32af",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u062a\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0639\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "52598bc5-2e85-4f4a-aa18-4e412d1d66ca",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0648\u0639\u0627\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0648\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0cb547d4-ba36-42c5-a223-ed7c39a223fa",
      "question": "\u0628\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e16eed31-e78b-48de-a516-8357cad53957",
      "question": "\u0628\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0644\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0634\u0627\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "842ebaeb-7865-42e2-b01d-fa6b1a1c02f7",
      "question": "\u0628\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3a9c7295-5746-465c-9150-528eb9d68600",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0644\u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "917f986c-674f-4ac8-9a6e-54f3d7012d5c",
      "question": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0644\u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "304dcec1-7cf7-4415-803a-8e4e376f2116",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0642\u0631\u064a\u0628\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0623\u062e\u0631\u062c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a63b28ae-9b5c-47cb-9e51-7c908c9c8cd8",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u062e\u0631\u062c \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0631\u064a\u0628\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e2828dac-2847-44a1-a10f-a9e9c8d6512d",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u062e\u0631\u062c \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0631\u064a\u0628\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bbdef1f3-e997-469c-b0e0-c23c08e3e7b6",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0646\u062f\u0645\u0627 \u062a\u062e\u0631\u062c\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062e\u0628\u0631\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0627\u0647\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5848acb5-0b32-433e-9c9f-9e005289884f",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062e\u0628\u0631\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f\u0645\u0627 \u062a\u062e\u0631\u062c\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c71c0818-73a2-4a94-82ed-fe4297a0b2ba",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "43cfb368-6a2f-47a1-9865-b9d4e0524aa5",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "683c9f1b-21dc-488b-bc91-e2473c3940f8",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u062a\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9342f087-fe12-4502-a496-c9adf4ce3b69",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u062a\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c95e277e-aaa2-4ece-a5c0-61577bd3f12e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fdbd3543-dfcd-4a38-894f-c44f78ea5124",
      "question": "\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "27a1e70b-8a85-4e24-b265-f7dc4fadbf55",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0628\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "adb3834f-5a5c-4389-b181-1f0c50f34247",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0633\u064a\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0628\u0644\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "007142e8-7fdf-467e-8aba-d88b17d2e03a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u062c",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "45e006de-e7bd-4f76-a3d7-e7b9a0cab1b4",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u062c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0633\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7cd40e88-3426-484b-927f-4466e3010637",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u061f\u061f\u061f\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u062c",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "026a7924-89db-46a2-b15f-2a204580d7ca",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e30cdf7e-d374-455f-bf8c-857e498b96e4",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0632\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d43483a7-cb9e-4dcf-82d7-f52578078f38",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "223f020a-414d-4168-a703-4d3f23e861b0",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u062c \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fbea475f-c147-4dc5-a1e4-a061db7b2ead",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u062c \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a6fea985-fa37-4a2c-bc25-8298da186b11",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639\u060c \u0633\u0623\u0634\u062a\u0631\u064a \u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0645\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a710c24f-2a50-4b51-8e1d-1b7e278855d4",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0645\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639\u060c \u0633\u0623\u0634\u062a\u0631\u064a \u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f602d119-5c58-42b3-a39e-1f342437a016",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0645\u0627 \u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0623\u0634\u062a\u0631\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c488a39d-5bf0-4b89-8b7c-89858251d3f0",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "405dddf3-1ddd-401a-8ab3-69c88e17e842",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8b137026-9d47-455a-b2b6-3695376e7f00",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u063a\u062a\u0647\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "963ddd4a-8828-4049-ae06-34641219d1b0",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u062a\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0e7cedf6-3544-44b3-be76-d48312bdeb6b",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u0641\u0644\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d6e8dd76-606a-48c1-96d0-996621423203",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u0641\u0644\u0629 \u0633\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0a27ec64-df10-45ff-bde7-b4789c9c7b6c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3927b364-0c7d-4119-8d97-b2c9446a7d25",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0631\u0643\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "138a7869-5606-468c-b7fa-673b52ed70d8",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8b618dab-2a10-46d8-b6bf-5f8ae3cd667e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "34abe79a-7589-4c50-9b84-b8c6446860f1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0636\u0648\u0636\u0627\u0621!",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0644\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fcd75668-69f8-43b8-a8f3-3856bfe699ce",
      "question": "\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0636\u0648\u0636\u0627\u0621!",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "36177a49-0710-4dcf-9fb7-a235b38cd236",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a323a1df-967b-4ef2-9e5a-f076efe9cf1c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3f5ba6d2-11c8-4a9d-964b-67ebf911cde4",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062b \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0d07ea02-1a30-43e5-8317-4029d9e309ab",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062b",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6675d699-59f0-4d59-98a0-626f1ebdd7ea",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062b \u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "111a5a8a-7643-4bf2-84f8-457ed6644d4c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "03a3c6fc-3588-4c79-aa73-d6b589ec5d8e",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0639\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1d897a62-2742-487b-af2f-2b02ecec263f",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0639\u0646\u064a \u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "32748d2e-9df6-497b-babb-08829745439e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0639\u0646\u064a \u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "99054d4e-310d-488f-a0cd-73dff4c93681",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "df51b213-2bbb-4f76-bd28-deb4e643355f",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a4610104-f62f-47b1-8c2c-52c95f026925",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0633\u0628\u0629 \u0644\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2d126e2b-f6bd-48cd-8850-3404ae90f7c4",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646\u0647 \u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0633\u0628\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ae09f4ed-c1ac-41fe-ba94-e004482d78e1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0633\u0628\u0629 \u0644\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0646\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "03afa37a-b511-46a7-a653-7f72f28521bf",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "610b1152-bf58-4383-848a-f6852b06884e",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "43190010-98ed-46fa-8650-420c9124cf5c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2674868e-708b-47f2-8a60-db7da6547598",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ea41bf9a-d6ff-4a21-ac66-e4c81e6110b0",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0645\u062a\u0646\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "680f0dca-ffb8-4097-94f4-ab1b691eabab",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0645\u062a\u0646\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d212fc26-dc32-4cf3-9776-37dbed643140",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u0648\u0645\u062a\u0646\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2ac4b700-982f-4be0-9493-465b1ec5c2da",
      "question": "\u064a\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f26b30aa-c1f8-47a5-ae6d-0031520b64da",
      "question": "\u064a\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a9d604c5-b075-4753-808f-02cb8f11bf86",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u0628\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7cb9ecb9-5603-40e0-ae83-7593a45ea100",
      "question": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0644\u062a\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a9291f16-a1e3-4a46-9828-81d6f18ec322",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0627 \u0642\u0644\u062a\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f9e8e6c8-5eec-4252-b98d-7c34e9d3e8f3",
      "question": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634 \u0645\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0644\u062a\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8291cb6e-c04a-4fa9-9fc6-44521435c562",
      "question": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f51c8707-82cd-4c73-b9be-c54d4e27b2a4",
      "question": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "acbe9350-50d4-4faf-9ca0-53e63e5e78f3",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2699893b-a048-49c9-9ece-b376a3382965",
      "question": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "380e6477-e8de-46b8-86cb-fe1fc351428a",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "33537c0b-8a50-4d83-880a-e31445c23459",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cd79156e-8377-4f36-aefb-b6b708a503de",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "20d740c9-167b-4b9b-8232-b9eba6b800e0",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0641\u0644\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0645\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0629 \u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ec47fb39-8734-41f2-a9b0-c55d67c72f40",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0641\u0644\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0645\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "601cdbe8-e720-47e2-96ce-51dc2c296334",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0645\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0629 \u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0641\u0644\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "193b753d-16b2-4040-991a-c5eb069c1ddf",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0646\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b7f5d912-4424-4fde-bb6f-32ed9f6354da",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0646\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0635",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "abec6792-7959-4e39-877d-bd70399fdced",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643 \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0646\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7cb1892a-4c0a-4458-a279-fa5fd1336554",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0644\u0628\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "17212eb9-77a5-47ab-ba21-1a297d286ba0",
      "question": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "925e0a50-a924-4451-8879-e106c96bb204",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629!",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8ede00cf-7eb3-4581-807e-a8e4ce1a41f4",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0648\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5f9e51da-91d0-4bd0-b737-033b6283f798",
      "question": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0648\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8c7636ca-4487-46b4-9309-510fad0ac4bf",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fcc33c92-98d1-4743-8f19-439084f97f55",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c9d660cd-6027-4766-ba8c-10239077f325",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0639\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b70ced45-7362-474e-80c3-dc0d33e16a18",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0648\u0627\u0637\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "17c61bdc-8c2e-4d0a-9143-4656b13bfa8e",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649 \u0647\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0648\u0627\u0637\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u063a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "be763308-d9f6-4351-96b2-0761bb027069",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0632\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a76e73c9-a42b-40f9-85b2-a64f33fda87f",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0632\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "61f2e09c-ad96-414b-90ba-8eb0297f67d9",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u0632\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e1d684d5-e66d-4166-bd61-955c077c8056",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0645\u0627\u0639 \u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "845d1740-1d4b-4b91-b187-8b08d4ea0691",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0633\u0645\u0627\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8c522c19-e15f-425b-b382-6c3319201c34",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0639\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0468c11e-6edf-4554-a129-28299aef12e7",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dcccd0ec-6893-4870-82b2-13d1c2b53a6e",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5a468a01-6269-436d-88f2-8d92407a0d10",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0627\u0642\u062a\u0631\u0627\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "581ef9ef-29ff-4a18-9aa6-4761899504a3",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6f7b3286-bdb7-4571-86b5-7f5c291d683c",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0644\u0648\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0644\u0627\u0626\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u063a\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "40145da4-a294-4a8a-a8bf-94db09efbde7",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0644\u0648\u0643 \u063a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0644\u0627\u0626\u0645 \u063a\u064a\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6325bf61-232f-49e8-bf09-dba537a62ac8",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "baa7380b-4b0f-4abe-90b9-9d23376e4784",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "792b6fff-db1e-4d1e-8d15-fd76c2ec423e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0638\u0647\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3d878202-0bb6-45d2-87ff-50291b230659",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0638\u0647\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "40ac5c19-5e05-4a21-a559-ead568069177",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u062f\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0629 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u0637\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "68e783a8-414d-4d73-94e0-562de757a8a6",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u062f\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ebd10fb1-36f4-40ff-9fe2-a9be69a505e8",
      "question": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "491d4dfb-2415-431d-8880-52f82da75458",
      "question": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8d2b3314-78ed-4874-848f-c17e1124b8e0",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0648\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9ec9cd86-dab1-44f5-8431-394c3293af6a",
      "question": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dc9b6e0d-f346-48b0-9f2d-b890f21fde27",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d6d76ac9-89f2-45d8-b165-70b9f0a6f218",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u0639\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062b\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7e2d9831-190b-4926-98bc-e93c93e0ade1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u0639\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062b\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b0021485-c035-4d56-a2a9-9ebcf9d89d3e",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u0648\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ad8b8c04-ebb1-4955-add5-2ce6a6bf0ee8",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cbec221a-17ef-4f48-8115-56e08a9881bc",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "de047692-b084-40cc-bc98-01c750a30725",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d9a86927-385e-4af5-93a5-887db946d7fc",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0644\u0641\u0632\u064a\u0648\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c7da4f74-d373-4271-bc21-a7118b9e4366",
      "question": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0644\u0641\u0632\u064a\u0648\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0631\u0646\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "895927ef-ae56-4308-b318-aa9e80b77a4b",
      "question": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "18c394a4-2bc4-4ddf-8a03-6ce6cd3dc80b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0636\u0648\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u062d\u062c\u0632",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a0bcfd68-73ed-4ead-b743-381def17eb4e",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0632\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3eaa92a7-9fe2-4709-9188-cc7c0210b985",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0632\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4479813f-a76a-4f5c-9d44-e3d36eace4aa",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630 \u0632\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c5c4de1f-907c-42d4-bc8b-05e1f107bdfc",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0632\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d9b44e40-e3f9-4ca0-9d06-23f37be919da",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0632\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2b934a62-2413-4c95-9799-4daf8e7be00c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u0632\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0643\u0647\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4992a1f8-b3a7-4093-84dc-926a35f14dc1",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "021ede47-84f1-45f9-a827-0a9dd717ec57",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cbe2c5ba-a738-4ceb-a789-726e207374f7",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0982231c-eb70-4720-8599-8ae3cef29fed",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "785848c5-8fcb-4906-bc44-0f78c2626c21",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f\u064a\u0646 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0637\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u0648\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5a637630-3603-404d-b3e5-371d26184ef7",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f\u064a\u0646 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u0637\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b949c5e8-6cdf-4b4c-bf97-2ec9bc288109",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0637\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e1a8212f-249b-4d87-af5b-dae6614c3c71",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0633\u0628\u0629 \u0644\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f92024b6-a968-47ef-a505-d151367c8463",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0633\u0628\u0629 \u0644\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "68b558f4-f164-438e-b11e-9c1861d5aabf",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u0628\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0644\u0623\u062c\u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "174403f2-2a02-47c8-87fe-4092b5784f80",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0644\u0623\u062c\u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d6114108-3042-464f-8121-c3270eb2a5d2",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0645\u0647\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2cd8179e-cbb6-4b31-a58d-84e825946565",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0647\u0645 \u0644\u064a \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "24ea5080-9a7c-43e8-a308-cbb4b7df93a2",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0645\u0647\u0645 \u0644\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "14e92131-5cce-442e-b9cc-2566a9cec3c6",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0627\u0639\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f6a7d173-ffb0-4a03-9e68-7f572b404e15",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u0628\u0631 \u0639\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0627\u0639\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4e8c4da9-a8c0-4ae1-8689-922db53df9bc",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f230c257-5ca0-4e83-8224-5e13dd0b4964",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2f0a42f0-cabf-4190-9099-3ea22740a127",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "faaba88b-a9d1-4edc-bcad-a75266fe4938",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "18d230ed-6fd7-4edb-aa48-527a8b9ab382",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d57b1224-eb4b-484f-9116-66da00c66602",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "af841f7b-1e87-4517-94ca-248b78e5b3dd",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0648\u062d\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "659cb5d0-0d45-4888-bb9d-0cafd88879eb",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u0648\u062d\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f182f0fa-99b2-4f7f-996f-8d1352dcf670",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0645\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u063a\u0631\u0648\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "985a4a82-a726-4b1c-a0cb-9b3a40c51f50",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0645\u0633 \u063a\u0631\u0648\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e8fd37fd-48e0-43b9-990a-6c344b4fbddc",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u062a\u0627\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "22e03c35-3eab-4424-94d0-ce35892a1fc1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u062a\u0627\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "88573793-1348-4cdc-8b45-c24c3856b4e6",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0628\u064a\u0639\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bd08015f-75a7-46a4-b207-8781f2a3c1eb",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0628\u064a\u0639\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u062f\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e65ac863-5d21-4cc0-a9bd-5cd187e627e2",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0628\u064a\u0639\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "647503eb-3543-4648-91f1-0696823c62da",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0632\u0647\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b14c13f9-68fc-44cb-ae43-d886be8761bd",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0632\u0647\u0631 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "508aac8d-f588-4ed6-80e8-31b8213d21b5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0633\u0631\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b98c9214-9688-46b7-a90a-a12270514231",
      "question": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0633\u0631\u0639\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ee1330fa-66ee-4faf-8097-36f99a6089d5",
      "question": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0631\u0635",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7c582f66-6d86-4730-898d-8af4feac4102",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u062a\u0627\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "db078fbd-c1e5-4003-aabc-a1ffb0e2b998",
      "question": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "78f5835b-63c8-43d1-83e1-d94e6a36498d",
      "question": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0634\u064a\u0627\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u063a\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4ab4b8e5-2a1a-483d-86e0-6177de94da4e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0634\u064a\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u063a\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0644\u0645\u0633\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "15230205-a58f-4493-a4b9-0e18f7819551",
      "question": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0634\u064a\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u063a\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "05aae646-791e-4758-82e8-68d28ca4730f",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d868dfc4-7abf-4457-8130-548955a83aac",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d8e2e582-0cd4-42aa-9f3d-91fb47cbccb6",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f \u0628\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "68250f3f-16f6-4348-8613-832709ac56d0",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1d1553a8-d572-4edd-bdc3-9d5b2ac246f9",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "71cdc487-0eef-4917-80fc-45299b7d438e",
      "question": "\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u062a\u0623\u062a\u064a \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0631\u062d\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d9cfc97f-fdce-4efa-a039-536b0fae8e8a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u0633\u062a\u0623\u062a\u064a \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1a057275-1001-42b0-af44-59fa53776985",
      "question": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0647\u062a\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b4b8cf90-abb0-4e20-b50c-beeabc9ce842",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0647\u062a\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8c793ebb-1f2f-47a0-8cc6-6f576b93f0dc",
      "question": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647 \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u0644\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0647\u062a\u0645\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4b01333a-c629-4eae-a182-c2f47df377c3",
      "question": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647 \u0623\u0646\u0647\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0634\u0643\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0633\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0634\u0643\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1dfca1cb-142e-49c7-bf28-17228685cdca",
      "question": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647 \u0623\u0646\u0647\u0627 \u0644\u064a\u0633\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u0643\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6a37f41a-d385-410a-acae-181984e016cc",
      "question": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a\u0633\u062a \u0645\u0634\u0643\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0647\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e563c668-5e8e-40b6-b840-3a766d78c7ae",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u0633\u062a\u062a\u0631\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "13def411-3ea9-4aa0-93e1-ec5705a16dae",
      "question": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u062a\u062a\u0631\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "14d354e7-f34f-4e54-89bb-df93c56cfbca",
      "question": "\u0622\u0633\u0641 \u0625\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0634\u0627\u0639\u0631\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0631\u062d\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c0f105de-2fee-471e-8710-9f134918c73d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0630\u0627 \u062c\u0631\u062d\u062a \u0645\u0634\u0627\u0639\u0631\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0622\u0633\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u062f\u062e\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ea4ded1b-15c6-4161-b7d6-b97aa678e35a",
      "question": "\u0622\u0633\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0623\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "461ab2b1-2e6a-4f3e-b244-3c3b8141e1c7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0623\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0622\u0633\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3dbe0a9f-6a38-4871-8089-4fa2ab786995",
      "question": "\u0622\u0633\u0641 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0623\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "967ca9f9-e8a1-4ef6-9205-281415a1ba79",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0643\u0641\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0622\u0633\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2fb014a2-e7dd-45d6-b6ad-926f875bf54c",
      "question": "\u0622\u0633\u0641 \u0644\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0643\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "aa48a66a-6146-49c5-9afb-dccbaa0d580c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "baff3e58-d79b-4107-9037-76565b8ad9da",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0633\u0631\u0639\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6c00ce06-8bf4-4e20-af40-1e3c3fcc5a98",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6c8f8979-d72c-4986-9f44-3874cb37000a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a8302d0f-3a6f-4cef-99d4-5e399d75c5ef",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "56cae1ca-a7b1-48e2-8b6e-7c12e76f0a9e",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0641\u0627\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a \u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0639\u0644\u0648\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c834bda7-3a27-4b29-9307-a6bb0d221ed5",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0641\u0627\u0644 \u064a\u062c\u0639\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0631\u062d\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3f8c6899-1114-4331-a9b5-734ce8e2de42",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "925d83d4-1f79-435f-8eff-2874d2bf947f",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7c7dedfb-29a1-4856-833f-6d56736843e0",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a1a46dfe-a31f-4abc-8d98-4b3899349744",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5b1695ba-5311-4c21-8440-962aaac27c71",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f1f3fe39-40db-4705-8ee8-ffbf692ae6b7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ec1d3e80-3c61-47ee-b877-7dd6e710c13a",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5df98254-e0fb-4f25-902e-47b8811e7156",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0632\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d202fc7e-1df7-4f36-8017-f3682e3a2597",
      "question": "\u062f\u0648\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0632\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0642\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "36d23755-5d65-4512-9a74-99ac33207b97",
      "question": "\u062f\u0648\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0641\u062d\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0058ff8d-f694-4d64-b1a4-b1d4fab6ad0a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0633\u0627\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a9023d6b-ee3a-4b25-aee3-4cba9efcee0d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7196300f-ca61-4941-b356-aff816941f7f",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0648\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f9767561-b24f-49e3-ab9f-25407f182463",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u064a\u0646\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a4f62e97-26d4-434a-b061-da5d340892ee",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0639\u064a\u0646\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0643\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a92443a8-d07b-4d46-a21f-6cfa2f065b4f",
      "question": "\u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629 \u062a\u0628\u062f\u0623 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7d8a54dd-0e29-4234-b645-c3257beecdbb",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629 \u062a\u0628\u062f\u0623 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0633\u0631\u0639\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6df1e2aa-df61-441a-8cad-6f1d1c57a48e",
      "question": "\u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0628\u062f\u0623",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6540416c-4bef-40fd-b44c-46750af7d1f3",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "182ce089-c0cc-41d3-9380-a0d590516a0b",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c84bb00f-f4dc-4a43-a235-049386b7f0dc",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0627\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "75cdfd6c-75e5-4f47-8f09-156daa829922",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631 \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fd74fc37-3761-44f6-a94f-faa870802a23",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631 \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0643\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "30747093-ad31-4b3b-8afb-fa2716d29f4a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0631\u0642\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "317b6633-6f75-4dbc-a72d-2f17635a881a",
      "question": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0631\u0642\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5520ad73-3338-4a34-a03d-3b48af9d37a6",
      "question": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0641\u0644\u0627\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c17c9367-398a-4dfa-8c10-1f0c0589f3c9",
      "question": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "992382c6-e3ef-4224-9d7c-ff326c47ddd7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0630\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "85d73bf7-e403-4752-ba92-68c5c506f92e",
      "question": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0630\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "27ffe04a-2a99-4d1e-bd11-0ea7028f7469",
      "question": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0630\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1da8baf0-ae26-493b-81ea-89b3d840f611",
      "question": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "154e3050-0d89-4435-bcd6-ca59b0c4e027",
      "question": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "09ccf0e6-6731-4d1c-bbde-bfe78968c371",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0637\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "70fb6d34-06c6-4c78-9a0f-4e18c88dd98d",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u0627\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4e2a9f7e-f3a6-4206-a297-6df4b5bdfe07",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0643\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "37dadad6-023d-4114-b7c2-ea77e4c10446",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0635",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0623\u062d\u0627\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "58e2bde4-b8a1-4160-a94c-ab936d83669f",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u062d\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0635",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "97d8d247-e899-4414-b6b9-cadead86317b",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u062d\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0635",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0631\u0635\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ff5008a0-b7ae-4111-82a9-489147b3260c",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645\u0629 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0959c32b-ec0e-4085-bb44-d86b20d91270",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645\u0629 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0647\u062a\u0645\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7f99d0a7-bf5a-417b-90d7-b1229e745b6d",
      "question": "\u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2d1a2b3d-7262-465c-abcc-7064448cd4c5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "593cce9b-e253-4892-922e-35991f2650e2",
      "question": "\u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "170363db-c251-4587-b209-e053902a6239",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0639\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4192089f-cd67-455a-8dbb-198e01c0f268",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0639\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "77d1e3a8-4666-4dc1-b02c-784dd3ea19bf",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0627\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9cecdeaa-0c60-4e1a-812d-2c161d780345",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0627\u0644\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9f46f1e1-4bab-448a-9c07-9f2b66bac2d5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0627\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u062f\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0af373e2-5047-4a74-b983-aef92ec69563",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0635\u062d\u064a\u062d \u0644\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e5ac93b3-1535-473a-b02a-74f827a0bb14",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u062d\u064a\u062d \u0644\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8654f473-9e71-49a0-8976-99776adb4bc4",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u062d\u064a\u062d \u0644\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fadf3385-5234-405e-b7e8-5fa317cd7ffe",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062e\u062a\u0644\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2290f38a-0df2-4472-b355-46ac9f91db2e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649 \u0645\u062e\u062a\u0644\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b3bc06b4-0299-4b80-980c-9c5549c9af36",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0634\u0631\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c18c81bb-21d8-4049-a74c-112ec016612e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0634\u0631\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u062a\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a8ddf2d2-88e8-4acf-8805-99cab4f3f2fa",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0631\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "60c04de8-8011-4858-a060-7ec13bd18137",
      "question": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645) \u064a\u0642\u062f\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0639\u0645\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0646\u0636\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "76661a07-1416-476d-a758-e6e25fad4a07",
      "question": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645) \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0639\u0645\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0642\u062f\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "89347647-d3ab-42e0-ba61-a62f7f2e2114",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0642\u062f\u0645 \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0639\u0645\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645)",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d493117d-fdde-4567-ab2a-b51b3a71631c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639 \u0644\u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0634\u0627\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645)",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "01d322ed-c121-4d9a-8db3-717e5ae699d3",
      "question": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645) \u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0634\u0627\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0645\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7083e676-20f9-45cb-a65c-3cb00643b7ad",
      "question": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645) \u0645\u0634\u0647\u0648\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0623\u0637\u0628\u0627\u0642\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "95c2dabc-03cb-4543-9016-2ff07f598ca1",
      "question": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645) \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0623\u0637\u0628\u0627\u0642\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u0647\u0648\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "07a29459-73d6-405a-a884-3c322e8e5e9d",
      "question": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645) \u0645\u0634\u0647\u0648\u0631 \u0628\u0623\u0637\u0628\u0627\u0642\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0641\u062d\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ed7df428-2d01-46e2-93e6-d67a7021e46c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0640",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e8bd8dd8-9c59-4090-9d79-996722fe2e89",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0640 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2d53b7e0-8e35-4546-ba03-cca30e150b67",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0640 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0631\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9739c17e-0de9-43e0-9ed7-e8d832ba3ae1",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0640 \u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0647\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u062a\u0639\u0648\u062f\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4411437e-c6ef-4856-8410-46d75e017804",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0640 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0634\u0647\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6d060bc2-8fca-46bc-a1bd-953b5e0aa31b",
      "question": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645) \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "649b1bc4-eef2-468f-a1fd-d61858d38039",
      "question": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645) \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "759114e7-4b4b-4f4c-9fcc-b2906b33ec0a",
      "question": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645) \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e4793cfb-1074-4233-8acf-e40c78b05000",
      "question": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645) \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0622\u0633\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6bb8afe6-a913-452e-b90c-f7aae08dc9e6",
      "question": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645) \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645 \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c6a3b457-079f-46d7-941e-ca7a778c1bd4",
      "question": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645) \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f0ccd4e4-4985-4fff-a97a-766763fa210d",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ce22b371-5008-4be8-9dae-44bc0ea68035",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c \u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "99be3c20-30b4-4028-a8f8-d43ab53cbf76",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c \u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644 \u0641\u064a \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "930f4a53-8591-4cb9-9897-4cc3223f7b40",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u062f\u0648\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0642\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3e244cdc-4aa0-4a30-99cb-002ac96ab120",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u0645\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1dd34666-e836-4e2d-87ef-12fbee862962",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "aad4eaa4-ec37-44d8-8674-9d28107c0498",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "048b2f00-50a5-4b7d-87d4-dfde7f390cf6",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b68be37f-13db-4fb1-9776-f96c5a8476e7",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0644\u062d\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9c8ba69e-096b-4489-b840-a11fc9bf76ea",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062d\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a\u0632\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b322c704-a29e-456d-be36-c36e60eae658",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2fa90d63-36c4-4a88-9ba1-c83760133ad7",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c1f49b26-e4c2-42e0-98ac-504b2511b573",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "994b3126-fe7d-49c5-941c-36886aa336bb",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3848c9dc-92af-487f-adc3-9e7e25a2b344",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e7b1a435-f5ec-4378-9a29-2c824b4fc2d3",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ec75dcd4-27d3-40e7-9ed3-fc18ec93ad75",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b71db25b-6075-4cda-ac57-a4e6ec74c7d7",
      "question": "\u0643\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b86dda0a-08ee-4dc2-9cca-4a956123c23d",
      "question": "\u0643\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "475a4664-2ed3-40b9-b101-5ff2315ae95b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0627\u064a\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "112c7bcc-a92d-4187-b7b9-5a4f7c3fbf47",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0634\u0627\u064a\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0639\u0643\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "743bef35-3123-476d-a80c-b9fe8c83ca16",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u064a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0633\u062a\u0631\u062e\u0627\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "93f7be07-3f8f-432e-bfd1-a2a02bb465bf",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u064a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0627\u0633\u062a\u0631\u062e\u0627\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "46d242e2-a337-4bbb-a640-720e3cea948e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0633\u062a\u0631\u062e\u0627\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8af322ec-2eee-4e8d-b35f-514f53d9c17b",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u0634\u0627\u064a\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e5f32463-6e74-44c3-b7c3-9a4397227b9d",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0627\u064a\u064b\u0627 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0634\u0631\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ca84268f-dc5e-4e07-93e1-32764a9b1a83",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u062f\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0631\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "aefec3fb-2d83-4959-96e0-cc9a713a835a",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u062f\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4eb0b02c-0ba9-47f3-88e4-bfb02467ac72",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u062f\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0628\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3d8406f6-f4e4-4c87-8c4d-a2a7e46fef25",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0633\u062a\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0635\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "511b6689-2d04-49d6-acb6-4f0a74b2acee",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0645\u0631 \u0644\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0645\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u062f\u0627\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "27907774-40d0-4a20-ade0-0339334174c7",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0645\u0631 \u0644\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0645\u0627\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u062f\u0627\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "49f859fe-9298-4d49-9472-c5d297664499",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b3e0d39b-7db4-4bbf-9221-636fd523b633",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6cb11e78-4032-4a60-a56e-0c83af78bcc5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0648\u0646\u0647\u0627 \u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2825ad02-b6d2-4628-8693-aaa341b19166",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0644\u0648\u0646\u0647\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1198ff99-d79f-4d25-bf3a-85f94b980307",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0628 \u0644\u0648\u0646\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a478ee0e-e6ad-498a-b5bc-328a9f397470",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0648\u0646\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c54f2b79-42e7-4089-8133-fd0d758a18ee",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639 \u064a\u0636\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646\u0639\u0634\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0643\u0647\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8b92c06c-69d9-4a8d-812c-e13979c37fdb",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639 \u064a\u0636\u064a\u0641 \u0646\u0643\u0647\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646\u0639\u0634\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1cb782d7-4a37-44cd-9590-937ff548fdf2",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "83be290d-3e09-40bf-9571-e9dbdede4e14",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6b4bf3fd-646d-46ed-a5ef-a452ae3eee2b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0630\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "09723412-df8f-41cd-9631-c0b1bada3bc6",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "692bbae1-3414-4df2-be4f-5d85d69be72a",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0634\u0627\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b4c424e3-8e38-4e6a-a631-4c98990bdc00",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0634\u0627\u064a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e0fcb30d-3a53-450e-ab05-8bc52b54ece4",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "89d88f0e-3a3c-42ad-8c94-ffc84b787ed9",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u063a\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d964bb3a-b95b-43af-8145-c2a0e2d32c72",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0628 \u0645\u0639\u062f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e7c57532-c3ee-4b5b-9ad9-b8ce0f79cfda",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c94647e5-d715-4c46-984a-b2ea70a4fd4e",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "de138420-177f-43a6-8e69-2341d9061a21",
      "question": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e70cda1f-f233-46ea-b99b-4534cd544281",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0648\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4d2ef75d-7f6c-48bd-b915-aa20f5a47090",
      "question": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0633\u0631\u0639\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0631\u0635\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e7e37446-9bb6-4439-9736-4c231f475fd1",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0632\u064a\u062f\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u0643\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f3409ac7-6532-4112-9ef5-5ea3009e21da",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0632\u064a\u062f\u060c \u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "aa5cd36b-f7c1-4c52-bd37-cfba410db30f",
      "question": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062c\u0628\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062e\u0648\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8a301ada-fd38-422d-81df-ae3e33545dd3",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062c\u0628\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "75e70e26-adea-43c2-8f7b-00c6ad879cf4",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u064a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0642\u0648\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b85bae47-4b6d-4b5d-831f-39921e58f5a3",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0623\u0646 \u064a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0648\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "64313878-e226-47f7-b52f-49bdb502ea48",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9f40fd56-f431-4e15-adfe-8f712cc7e051",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bf16d818-e9c6-4ca6-a0e1-003dbdda143e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0641\u0639\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0635\u0639\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "15ac0f0d-3b95-48d9-92cf-a1e02239b841",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0635\u0639\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a13b542a-8f4b-4838-be80-234c92a23a25",
      "question": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0635\u062d\u064a\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dad80518-b77b-48af-804f-bd16000e78ba",
      "question": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u060c \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0635\u062d\u064a\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "33c0ad66-45fd-4466-833e-0add5390330e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u062a\u0642\u062f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u0647 \u0633\u064a\u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e2a0e54a-d893-4ae5-89d0-903d23859068",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u062a\u0642\u062f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u064a\u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f25fde92-a323-475a-8004-8da302ce5cc3",
      "question": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u060c \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0645\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0627\u0647\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "af9a310e-2cb9-4ff0-9d63-e9c690c9f3b3",
      "question": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u060c \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0644\u0627\u0647\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "44fa7ca4-d9e5-4b23-ad11-76a549e0984e",
      "question": "\u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u0641\u0644\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "792efe35-ea41-4c81-b0de-f5e14350692a",
      "question": "\u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5b5783e5-44e2-4122-a5b2-e041266b6158",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b3cd29d9-4c97-46d8-8318-5082d7db108c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0631\u0627\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0635\u0644\u0627\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cd89781e-0398-40e8-afd8-57c8128832b6",
      "question": "\u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4e81d227-837b-4cad-a4b1-a07d73b17cc3",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0627\u064a\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7f631f11-5447-4b02-ba49-c323101dcf33",
      "question": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u0645\u0634\u0645\u0633\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u0643\u0648\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2afaa1ef-7ab9-409e-bac7-65bbef81c006",
      "question": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0633\u064a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0634\u0645\u0633\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dd5aa3d3-13c1-41ae-a4da-7bbe2be34e49",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u064a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u0645\u0634\u0645\u0633\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "86578156-ed8a-43b2-a9e1-630df5aaced7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0637\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "70d3370a-7832-44d8-8a4a-e50df161177e",
      "question": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0637\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0644\u064a\u0628\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ad8367b0-c7cd-4834-997b-210e6f6f62d6",
      "question": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "170d7653-e599-4430-8c3d-eee29e8e2467",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "742830a6-0904-4eae-9abf-d1b445e984f9",
      "question": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0647\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u0637\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8a73ee9c-3d9d-4864-88b9-35a541044274",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0637\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0647\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "62e8e2bb-1366-4fcd-b085-a56fafd1fb06",
      "question": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0540819a-ce37-4cbc-b909-4cf8f12d4e8f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6413feb9-f657-4b70-9815-c45d0ffcf8a2",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "930c0be3-2046-4986-8a14-79f2f0929c4e",
      "question": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "feeef7da-d17f-468e-97b4-5d5cd1d7c2b7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0643\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "22cc3c78-b97e-484b-b3d8-e76dc2259a27",
      "question": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0643\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "214a3795-10ce-4684-8f38-cd3ac432ac7b",
      "question": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0631\u0635\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9fdccc94-d32d-4f89-a948-d42c12de3f4c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0647\u0627\u062a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ba58d1de-c3c2-432d-85d2-c6c04153de17",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0647\u0627\u062a\u0641 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0648\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f56e446c-4aa9-449a-b29d-8fe00ee56596",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643\u0645 \u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u0627\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1d102163-414e-43a2-8643-c19fe33e574e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643\u0645 \u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u0627\u062a \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cb3581d8-90f1-4fbd-a2e7-04af5cb65cb1",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u0627\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4aabdd7a-155b-409d-a434-a0ab75333412",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0645\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dd968d49-a94a-49b9-8590-b0b1e444522f",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0648\u0645\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6f44a67b-9e07-4a29-b201-47c787b9ea7d",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0642\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1fcd539c-3f94-4400-a7a9-f55756910a56",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2980eb48-5e7f-468a-9e3b-41e33e9757d4",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0631\u0635 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0623\u062a\u064a \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e4ab7bea-7ad3-4f6e-a283-3320cf469c18",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u062a\u0623\u062a\u064a \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0631\u0635",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d7d51a37-c48c-44d8-8862-0c0b542507af",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0631\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0623\u062a\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "79ea8d3d-4de6-497b-b0df-8ea1343f2172",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u0644\u0647\u0627 \u062a\u0635\u0645\u064a\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "297fd169-1d81-4c86-afe9-3d8dcef2dfe1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0647\u0627 \u062a\u0635\u0645\u064a\u0645 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "97a87d08-4fc5-40b8-bcd7-7204cbf1289d",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a5d9bb66-863d-4bef-8aa6-506148a64d91",
      "question": "\u0639\u0628\u062a \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a4adb983-8c12-4b7b-877c-392c4aa55c0c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f05ee086-31b1-4aa1-a9e0-01abf705f32a",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633 \u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5c6ede84-949b-4650-9e30-f43a62b8659b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633 \u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "15e16552-6fe4-4cb0-aaaa-cf07c1b9c96e",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d00316a8-120b-40ec-9a76-ddd2941b7e37",
      "question": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "22c3b398-bc0b-42dd-b047-3d1a13e02a0b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e8841759-67d6-4bbd-93da-a0e71015bc14",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "df213fb8-2f39-4ac0-9423-e7384bd42fb2",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062e\u064a\u0631\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "da268918-60b0-4d65-88b8-2cc14130f570",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062e\u064a\u0631\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "365a21c2-18b5-475b-95ff-bf315698503e",
      "question": "\u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u060c \u0643\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0639\u0631\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fa193992-d066-457e-88e6-740afbc6a18b",
      "question": "\u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0634\u0639\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "05f61640-4110-45fa-be8b-bb8272db77c6",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062d\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "995d3715-ae13-431a-a82e-0e5154471b78",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062d\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5bd578f6-7daf-4f92-9c79-aba077e71273",
      "question": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f516a23d-9a1c-41d6-9d44-756da63ca3a4",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f35819d3-d31a-426c-8111-446f1193e1cc",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "48708fcb-212f-4ba2-8b7f-f7853a4479dd",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f13ee141-f4db-456d-b3e6-ced80230b633",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062f \u064a\u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0642\u062a\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0d13baf8-d693-4224-8e09-b81b319262a9",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0642\u062a\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cbd2f21e-ea6b-44c5-8bb2-0af51dda46d5",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0648\u0642\u062a\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "be69f30d-4305-4d16-8361-ec8f80c7f2bc",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1bc67e90-94e3-4682-b4ca-4a7285c82edb",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8ceb7ca4-8859-419c-b1b7-6b6fb6eeaa66",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "14cddf9e-0a2a-4885-9fe6-05b9068c1d4f",
      "question": "\u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a3239d55-cb02-4d14-9d7b-b52ea21cf63c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9dff7697-9692-42ba-af2f-1a347f0f503a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "235c3b42-6000-4382-aaa6-fdbebe1e4795",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u0637\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cafa71a7-f955-4572-9c25-cef20b425c07",
      "question": "\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "111b7ce4-ebc5-499b-9a1d-6d72a02ca881",
      "question": "\u0647\u0648 \u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c06213e8-7996-49de-a728-d30455320444",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7dc7487a-4629-4cde-abea-0e5124e06cea",
      "question": "\u0647\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e1239668-3fd5-4e17-9d49-9a66a95bdb2d",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0648 \u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0628\u064a\u0639\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "51dc86fd-82c2-4d07-acbb-12493f91d89e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "159b31b1-4fc2-44a3-95bc-a2e5e80b2c77",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "86ea046a-8638-434b-94ed-a76af0861177",
      "question": "\u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0641\u0644\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4dcc40c5-1e9d-4fd3-9ccf-4d4d524f7458",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0627\u062f\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "59053fb0-d052-41ce-8a9e-93b89340d391",
      "question": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u062a\u0639\u0648\u062f\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ebd324eb-c4f4-4509-b861-a72ec89a78ba",
      "question": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062e\u0631\u062c\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "97c78612-18b1-4581-8e54-e1fcac7f45b5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062e\u0631\u062c\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "64e38ea3-a11e-45e2-85e1-61d9e9853b1d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "99194ff8-526d-4c9b-b198-a19cd84bbbe0",
      "question": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ef9d7ce4-9ccd-40be-9999-48d9920e8a5b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "daa6710a-c610-4959-b3cb-cf09d4f7f161",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a95be06a-7a0f-4e5e-a254-6efd9037a4e9",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f \u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5af4c095-68ed-40db-a143-04b7b34bfe9f",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f \u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0634\u0643\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "363948d8-fc3d-4fbe-87da-b9b20f9cfc65",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f \u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a3f0cd21-e1e9-4bed-a654-e8676a994fce",
      "question": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641 \u0642\u0628\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "23fd9085-5085-4569-ac2a-5ed9c7f17f84",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641 \u0642\u0628\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5561a03b-4190-499f-93cf-ea3678f64f76",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e387047d-82d6-47ca-bcb5-54a07ffd2f77",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a00cfa00-9dff-43bc-95c0-280b813db23b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f \u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7de40424-8882-41b2-8e6c-a295e7b29234",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f \u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0c18509b-5432-4581-80dd-064d2db020f8",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641 \u0642\u0628\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1b3ec7c7-870a-4c6d-b0c3-67a42d22ed76",
      "question": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641 \u0642\u0628\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0646\u0647\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f7c70058-b3fd-4908-a64c-65789cc4fb24",
      "question": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "746b2ab1-2e63-4b7a-9bca-09be42f408f2",
      "question": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4cbe3677-ba99-48c0-abab-dac145e3f084",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629 \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0624\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e0e71c1d-a52a-4015-b322-c5c191ee3ce2",
      "question": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "781e8f21-856a-4967-b2e1-0011162b44c4",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9bd51eab-a7bf-4498-acb0-e93c2ec65fbe",
      "question": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f8acbf10-10b4-456d-a263-a6a2c3b79c8f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "22a57efa-d859-421b-9702-67e628f69e6b",
      "question": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "73246712-3fa7-4857-a1be-2006c07fd7bd",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645 \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2730b9ab-fc69-4b6d-b0be-98f118baee18",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u0648\u0645 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "601b839f-0d06-4ca2-b878-db6fa453f981",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a \u0648\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0647\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a2284303-72f4-4ca7-a6a8-70bcb47e6875",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062f \u064a\u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0647\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8b1669ec-ff29-4850-a373-e49a576bdcfc",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "df973b18-800c-48c9-9a48-c5c1361c2de0",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u062d\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3ed0e34e-f318-4033-b37d-6158e243f896",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d5a02f40-3e46-4ebd-908a-3e6b66c125d7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "017e0573-55a9-4bae-8138-a3a23cf64067",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u063a\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7c3d72f6-945a-4b12-bc28-bade7fa6295e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0623\u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "721a18f2-f8ae-4f19-81b2-a892d9a3aca5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ede19c22-8844-4695-90bb-a53a654a3cbd",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0644\u062a\u0632\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "79d8155c-862a-422e-adb3-1369453ede23",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0646\u0642\u0648\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645)",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e63f1fcc-3151-4310-b4f3-e7aea9ba0470",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0642\u0648\u062f \u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c9e33926-cde9-46f9-a2c7-35aabc371bd1",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0641\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "19c1f66c-09fd-4adb-ab6c-4fcb73de61b9",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7687c3c6-9c0b-4340-902d-d369b9f45ade",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0643\u0648\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2a484b5a-b823-45e3-b070-7db54eb7f8fe",
      "question": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "45574aba-a704-4518-8a68-78316b8c1d3e",
      "question": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f0c26b17-7894-47b3-a79f-c40eedcfca34",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0641\u0644\u0627\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0c539268-a5fa-461e-9103-fd4a2b9430b0",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u063a\u0646\u064a \u0644\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1fec588d-f9ec-45b6-912a-58da4c65a87c",
      "question": "\u064a\u064f\u0639\u062a\u0628\u0631 \u0623\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u063a\u0646\u064a\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0648\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "29af842b-ce97-4826-b8f7-bc4138e84ed4",
      "question": "\u064a\u064f\u0639\u062a\u0628\u0631 \u0623\u062d\u0645\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0645\u063a\u0646\u064a\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0648\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7ac67bdd-2d9a-4045-9f3c-e983afe5082c",
      "question": "\u064a\u064f\u0639\u062a\u0628\u0631 \u0623\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0648\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u063a\u0646\u064a\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1cb6c8be-d09c-4e05-8a5c-322204cf4132",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "-",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "318e2c53-6965-48d4-ad0a-4d3fa13d2f1c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "59790ceb-646d-4074-907e-b41159a610fb",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062c\u0645\u0648\u0639\u0629 \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0627\u0646\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0647\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0635\u062d\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9515c491-cf66-49e6-8e6c-9311b86d2cc5",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0627\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u064a\u0645\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6bd08208-edaa-4206-a918-f72a5cbdb70e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bdc85176-e307-4056-8a6b-0a3e3e927306",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0647 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0636\u0648\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0639\u062a\u0642\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "39b8a586-65b1-4b08-b5d8-74b5871e4b8a",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062b\u0642 \u0628\u0646\u0641\u0633\u0643 \u0648\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0645\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0639\u0644\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e5171ffb-3778-4773-bea7-c280e0b66cde",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u0628\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062d\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "52a48a73-7c73-4048-bffe-62fc692a0c93",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u062a \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u0628\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "589a2793-5550-4b5d-8019-a054ae205a57",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "81e0234c-0ffa-47d7-98ce-99881248089b",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0642\u0627\u062f\u0631\u064b\u0627 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "45c19c74-5e2b-4b7c-a344-f4cb25ab117e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0642\u0627\u062f\u0631\u064b\u0627 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c16af346-1c61-45a9-a4e1-df90ec84c199",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u063a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2f724a5e-30a5-4e2e-9bad-57916385a9cd",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0634\u063a\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0646\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "33953c1e-b0de-4212-a338-ccd03b7e243b",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0636\u0639 \u062c\u0647\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0634\u063a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u062c\u0628\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8fd29ca3-fb00-4bf2-b715-56e933a2a799",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0647\u0627\u0632\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ac734e5e-0f5d-4f0a-9a90-8f137afef564",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0647\u0627\u0632\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1194369d-183c-4153-8f06-688424e237d8",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "91e63212-b9d4-46d9-a7f1-9f64c3705c17",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "95490a19-3129-4916-bd61-283b03dcab51",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0648\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "02cf1016-b369-42c4-b2f8-57930141faa6",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "023950b1-c27b-472e-97c0-660b067b9627",
      "question": "\u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641\u060c \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f5b2d918-df70-49a0-a799-92b93d40966c",
      "question": "\u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641\u060c \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c3feaab1-e24b-4ac0-ba51-790f27b74704",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0639\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ad929814-285d-4092-857e-70e902912231",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0644\u064a\u0633 \u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0643\u0645\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0646\u0628\u063a\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "-",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5c107064-b947-4a91-b724-86cff14727cf",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a\u0633 \u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0643\u0645\u0627 \u064a\u0646\u0628\u063a\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9dc91e26-aac9-498a-8065-8fafe0802357",
      "question": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ba22a28d-88da-46c7-8236-1c7397de4084",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0c205725-6e12-47c5-a0ae-81a54c42f5be",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c806f0c0-8493-44b0-b4e1-ea4767b0f209",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "859fdaa1-005e-4e50-a8e9-2ee6f44844b5",
      "question": "\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b12e1853-6546-4c35-b095-c2d1f99089dd",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dd72ba81-795d-494a-8407-fb975bc45f88",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0627\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "734c3c6f-1d06-45bc-a883-81fbc11b37ec",
      "question": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0635\u0628\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fadbb6fb-47cc-4aed-b850-e9a25d8aacb7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u0623\u0645 \u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u062a\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fdae79b5-2a94-4fcf-ae00-563ca6e13a63",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0645 \u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f3ebcf23-59c4-435e-9a55-25d8a669025c",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "979039da-cb3b-492b-901d-36e4b4e6ee7f",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2962cb79-f44b-47f1-b4bb-fcc642df4549",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631 \u0644\u064a\u0633\u062a \u0641\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0647\u0644\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4aaf7ae0-59ea-48cb-888d-cb67b1db7345",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u0627 \u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0631\u0624\u064a\u062a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "88067435-edac-4a36-af51-6dc9bdd1cf5e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u0633\u0646\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a89bb503-8fe3-41ff-a5d9-ce4fd3cc9896",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645 \u0645\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0642\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "56f8b8c3-651c-4c8f-af40-f90ef463b42c",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0647\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0636\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b35e89e0-6280-4599-bd40-ddaecf96d496",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0647\u0645 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0636\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0631\u062c\u0644\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "766547ab-ad21-4879-8c48-f2acfff8ff89",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0641\u0647\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0631\u064a\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0627\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fd98d553-28a6-433f-b6f6-d8a12cf0da6c",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u063a\u062a\u0647\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8d00d48e-672a-4438-bc60-6ba6e19ef90e",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u062d\u062a\u0631\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "264e5cae-a2ce-4069-958e-21c213d83b2e",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u062d\u062a\u0631\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e7a30be1-ee9d-42af-b4c2-bc5491ec0422",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0635\u064a\u0627\u0646\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "55202249-89e2-4a0a-a5e7-69a401d96bf8",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u064a\u0626 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4b01cec7-2bfd-4136-b00f-1c70240971c1",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u0626",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2046e006-a9bf-4116-bade-911e2da661c1",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0631\u0627\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "083d4017-5ac2-4bea-b12b-494281e91cfd",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0641\u064a\u062f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cef4b560-3a6b-4878-990c-b13c8f326a08",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d9a122a9-9cdd-48d6-a86c-5cea31f9e39c",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0642 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062c\u0647\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4a700942-fdb4-4e79-9ebc-d63d2059720b",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0634\u062a\u0627\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0646\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fe9464aa-845d-4dd0-b9d2-511a2a0688cb",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0634\u062a\u0627\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0642\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0b3d301c-c195-47aa-adff-f7ea99a23769",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0637\u0627\u0644\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c74c7e04-28ff-4c42-bba8-6f9c46a6e8b3",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0637\u0627\u0644\u0628 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a57d902c-8359-4616-a493-94622064daa1",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631 \u0630\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0642\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f87aae7b-8024-4fab-ac58-82f2422e7f86",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631 \u0630\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8331ac6b-b7d7-4354-9a91-a73b432ef978",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0632\u0639\u0627\u062c",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "952353ce-e0c0-418a-b763-3499dfb431c8",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0625\u0639\u0637\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f2bd9921-a841-430d-98a8-a9598fc425c1",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0634\u0631\u062d \u0644\u064a \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0b8b703f-889c-48a1-8f01-7fb8d67c974c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0646 \u062e\u0644\u0627\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0628\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "552ea41b-7d02-4043-bc8d-e46056248ede",
      "question": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6a8a7c78-4396-4b03-a345-cfe7a10ed671",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0632\u0641 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062a\u0627\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b9249d42-e332-4689-be3b-498114beff73",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0647\u062a\u0645 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0645\u062c\u0629 \u0648\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0645\u062c\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u063a\u0627\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f7dcae89-a794-4f94-a16d-6f1651fd3bf7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0644\u062a\u0632\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "abe9e04e-aa9d-4ea8-81c2-fc5b8ca1b17e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c996dc86-e8cf-4be5-be9e-b33fddd90c35",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0645\u0627\u0631\u0633\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1955956c-9bb0-4d5f-80fa-0b8cffa986fe",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0645\u0627\u0631\u0633\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "20e7519b-d484-4639-b546-fa91cc0360e8",
      "question": "\u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0631\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0646\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "054cc5bc-d8c7-4254-9107-00d81d1c5b93",
      "question": "\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u0645\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "62af7b8e-502d-4b45-b7ab-06aca55c7b19",
      "question": "\u0644\u0645 \u0623\u0633\u0645\u0639 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dc1df630-85ca-46d7-9820-ee4821232e69",
      "question": "\u0643\u0631\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "88c138ee-87c9-4217-a85f-25e2357cc4fb",
      "question": "\u0643\u0631\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0631 \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b3683698-91e5-4c00-8d93-04b4caa61f46",
      "question": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2577525d-f6c2-4e76-b0c5-6a3260d87fcf",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0639\u0646\u0627\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645)",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "84578651-9c10-4251-848a-4be402404fb1",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "df1bc6aa-1e22-4267-8ddc-452ebfb791aa",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u0628\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "860b5535-52ca-4ccf-8d3a-8ec44b632f9c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c868d82a-9855-4aca-9e79-beb1fd047697",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0633\u0628\u0627\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u0623\u064a\u0636\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7d5768bf-e654-44d1-94bc-6f411f3c80aa",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u062a\u0633\u064a\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "724ee4ce-ef3b-4afd-9597-7835d24f99f1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u062d\u0631\u0643 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u062d\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0639\u0637\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4d9e56bb-4bd5-4a22-86d5-45ae0f3390ef",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0631\u0646\u062a \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0635\u0641\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "11cb9c54-ef00-4b99-b0cc-0bcc6f84dde0",
      "question": "\u0627\u0642\u0631\u0623 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0635 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3c95a515-e412-4955-abe9-b68b93f11354",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "31c2e442-5419-4c60-bd68-0f32bffd5483",
      "question": "\u0636\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0628\u0636\u0639 \u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0642",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u0644\u062a\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bd4fc18f-d6db-43b3-b1cd-895a1f468f89",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0636\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0637\u0648\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0641\u062a\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0633\u0628\u0627\u0646\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8f8b507c-6f3b-4c04-b9bb-e9844e4bf4bc",
      "question": "\u0623\u0639\u0637\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u0621\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "04c6e74a-638f-49cc-83fc-2278e93d93a5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0ed353d0-9b6c-4c35-af64-bd7ccbe68b0a",
      "question": "\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0644\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0641\u0643\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6d6b3510-c3ae-4965-874a-edf97410f690",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0643\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0641\u0643\u0631 \u0628\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "37df68cc-b05b-43dc-84cd-e12244949282",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0644 \u0645\u0627 \u062a\u0641\u0643\u0631 \u0628\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062a\u062c\u0644\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1d473d3c-7557-47a7-aeea-aef015a11fc0",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ce75eb55-c2d2-45c5-bfcd-47200ec0c7c1",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0648\u0636\u0648\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6f12d1ff-87f5-4541-812b-e210ba46f876",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0648\u0636\u0648\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "747d3ccd-cfcd-4bca-93cb-4615073cab56",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u0644\u063a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0648\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "24bbcdfc-7370-4348-a112-2635a01801c4",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "70ffa7ad-6e88-49e5-b833-ab102083e88d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4f78b3da-a0f9-4acf-aa28-eb122bfe1dbb",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0631\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "01337c18-f1ca-480e-acda-4b4edc46967b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a33b93d1-5733-4412-a32d-c2e14b2e961f",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0633\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "81b1a3b0-8cbd-4e46-9ba9-a31a640a2247",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5ad6b2fd-f69c-4e97-8050-7ade5617e90b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0631\u062d\u0647 \u0644\u064a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "932f8af8-2427-474b-afa2-4d05268d00fd",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062a\u0627\u062d \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u0648\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ae57d2fd-fd93-4598-9ecb-8cadcb945b22",
      "question": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0641\u062d\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "648f0d07-d0d5-482a-83c2-a58e982d5cbc",
      "question": "\u062d\u062f \u064a\u0628\u062d\u062b \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0638\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8acfa1a8-03a9-40c8-b394-58b8df7b88d3",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "68de1422-7f45-4770-9880-960ce9af30a4",
      "question": "\u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "92630a94-ce12-49a0-840e-f5a5ff5e61b6",
      "question": "\u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "971e9aba-b7d0-4bd1-9115-16e7eb62ca02",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0641\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d073c045-526c-45dd-a3bd-f799b779b4fa",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0635\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u062d\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f05a8761-93e3-44f6-9e5c-ff3af87a3865",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0647\u0648\u0627\u064a\u0627\u062a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ba45115e-c5d5-4c48-b495-b4ed7c724fd6",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0633\u064a\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a459beb3-446f-4db2-87bf-f4e65abb13b0",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0631\u0649 \u0623\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "705a3b19-36b4-4861-b41c-f5b85bc28e21",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "042de914-b976-4a23-b3f4-45a1888e91f7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0641\u0639\u0644\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0d73dfc3-b27a-4058-a875-ed1ed0a4120e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u0637\u0644\u0628\u062a\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "66fc9413-5b5d-4fbe-872c-4bd77a6eb761",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0647\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "47f05ece-79ab-4afa-abcf-d5ae0011b5e5",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u0628\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ae757f0c-0b4c-41ff-a15e-b779cb61d7ff",
      "question": "\u064a\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u0647\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "847e1830-d779-4d4a-8227-3239d9b5c27d",
      "question": "\u064a\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u064a\u0627 \u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6583cd0f-1188-4ed4-84b3-5a250a452f9a",
      "question": "\u064a\u0627 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u064a\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "17b076f2-ce50-4be8-996a-be166ac1b3da",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629!",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bdd58384-6270-4593-969d-d0f48eadb94a",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0630\u0627\u0647\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0631\u0633\u0627\u0644\u0629 \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0623\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0d7ed3ca-ac9c-4f04-b6bf-10aa0da98481",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0630\u0627\u0647\u0628 \u0644\u0623\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0631\u0633\u0627\u0644\u0629 \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c8f46c62-e2db-471b-9fc9-648dde38e27c",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u0642\u0648\u0645 \u0628\u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u062c\u0644\u064a\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0c31b00b-d9ad-4240-9ccf-d808491dfd1c",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0648\u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0642\u0637",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d564cbd6-e473-4744-a36d-464df37510ac",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ef28929c-9ec9-4102-930c-a9cc7f03c61f",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0646\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cdb6151d-acf0-4b88-bbec-77f9cc43e36a",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "230edad2-771e-4072-8305-539b2db020d2",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0645\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f8171dff-a838-4a39-8298-c3f9d4ad8a7e",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "709d9e89-fc8c-4f82-be32-67a7b6454118",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0633\u0627\u0626\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1d3fc00f-4075-4b69-bb48-d0647f2b0546",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f206d1aa-d11d-4b41-b705-83d41ff68e9c",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062f\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7ab46e55-b7bf-4cbd-9eaa-b068a9ae8e5f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0639\u0645\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0629 \u0644\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "89fe76b1-d8b0-43ef-a2fc-14ece42135d7",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6c3b4a9a-5013-428c-aec9-3e8bc724da93",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4b1f4d8a-bb84-4e14-aefa-dfe694d59311",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0642\u0633 \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5092ba8c-3b68-432f-89a9-4622178c4d2d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u0648\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u0621\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f670a9f3-2b27-49e9-83ea-ec11ad8ca44b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0628\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0648\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2be37cc1-0a88-4e61-9717-efec58dcc555",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0644\u0645\u0633\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0639\u0629\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0646\u0647\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ca137573-4a72-4d61-857f-e76299831a62",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0644\u0645\u0633\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0639\u0629\u060c \u0625\u0646\u0647\u0627 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a2a6daed-045f-41cc-b819-f2d1fe1aae78",
      "question": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u063a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u064a\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "52794d39-90e5-409b-bdee-50e5bf73d6e0",
      "question": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u063a\u064a\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u064a\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c079f1c0-0387-4d6d-97b7-b75fa88693f9",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u062d\u062a\u064a\u0627\u0637\u064a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "36dd7b52-3ded-4123-be95-72f79022c3ef",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u062a\u062c\u0639\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u062a\u0633\u064a\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0633\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "52ca3934-2e2d-49c4-84dc-89507ca0d590",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u062a\u062c\u0639\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0633\u064a\u0631 \u0628\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0633\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b4e1b7c0-8e67-4e35-9ca0-ed7b4318e7bf",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u062a\u0633\u064a\u0631 \u0628\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0633\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062c\u0639\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5a7ce46c-da1a-483d-b571-f7e3206c1c07",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u062d\u0628\u0648\u0646\u0643 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0647\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0648\u0646\u0647\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "eb2ea473-2624-41e6-9ec0-7347213d3535",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0623\u0646\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u062d\u0628\u0648\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f97a2a33-75b2-4651-95ba-e8704f968dfd",
      "question": "\u0643\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0634\u063a\u0648\u0644\u064b\u0627 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "977afa2c-1616-4780-ae5a-45029d590228",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0634\u063a\u0648\u0644\u064b\u0627 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0646\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "641e1931-dc11-41b2-8ae4-af90eecd355a",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646\u0647\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "26da6421-dbbf-43ad-bf57-bf10ce2109d4",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u064a\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "408212ae-bbae-4ab9-ab96-b13310f1e276",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "04e0a6bb-7300-4577-9173-042e57f1bd51",
      "question": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0630\u0647\u0628\u0648\u0627 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u062d\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a85955ee-d963-4ed6-84ca-4503b1174dcb",
      "question": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u062d\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0630\u0647\u0628\u0648\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ddad614f-d46e-480e-8cc0-7f6c4b86c108",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a7fb906d-ee0d-469f-b5a1-616131659a3f",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0634\u0631\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cb7d6a05-abe0-433f-9bcc-d57229d27e5e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u062e\u0646\u0629 \u0623\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d7f4d26c-e37a-4bba-ad2a-99ce6ae1f2b2",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u062e\u0646\u0629 \u0623\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0639\u0646\u0627\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f1275178-1e1f-488b-9b71-bd8280e8d0ae",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0642\u0647\u0648\u062a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u0647\u0648\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0631\u0635",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "502dceb7-1e30-41ed-aa10-51dbcce7fa09",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0634\u0647\u0648\u0631 \u0628\u0642\u0647\u0648\u062a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2fe8b13c-92f7-4dcb-af9e-5f67afc1dd79",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0632\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cb20c067-76d2-44e7-8c3d-c07b3adc76f0",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0644\u064a\u0628\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "eb4de8df-81be-43cc-b3de-a4c197f5d187",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3839feec-acbe-4cf9-a23a-dc7fafc6beb8",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6d876a92-1a46-400b-b275-723d424fab1d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0631\u0643 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7e66f80b-b3a6-4fb5-8466-b058b2616996",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0631\u0643 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0ac98832-2695-4e59-b44b-9ea794c00f29",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u062a\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0645\u0628\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4d75bbc4-6dd8-4a4b-a814-5ce0c5031d35",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u0636\u064a\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "955c0e97-a922-414f-9a03-65350be2ef55",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u0636\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0631\u062c\u0644\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4f396852-6b9d-4852-bb98-71c9f8b83d45",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0645\u0633 \u062a\u0634\u0639 \u0628\u0636\u0648\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9f8b7b5a-3ca4-4c11-9c27-c5f644047fbd",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0628\u0629 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e75a4ca5-a83c-4e99-99bc-18ffe517da0b",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0634\u0627\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u062c\u0628\u0629 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "16bd9584-6e9f-4f12-9221-40486793c5c9",
      "question": "\u0634\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0646\u0627\u0645\u062c\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "36ebfbae-778f-4ba5-9e09-ecb9431ce5fc",
      "question": "\u0634\u0648 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0646\u0627\u0645\u062c\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "16c9e766-ebe6-4153-8034-bb60ea4f037d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0642\u0631\u0623\u062a\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7bafe214-935d-44f0-a9e4-f52f9b5898f0",
      "question": "\u0634\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "30b76478-46b7-4157-ac9c-075e81c0d1bb",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0645\u0646\u062d\u0646\u064a \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0642\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9953378f-400b-4103-84fd-b12af68b6f2c",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u0642\u0637 \u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d4494d3e-8b58-4da0-8db1-cb7e87459ba1",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u0642\u0637 \u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u062a\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d84eca33-36af-4866-b38c-7ba50061559c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0636\u064a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0643\u0631 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8672ee9d-9493-4749-8ce2-6d079ec6cc77",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0643\u0631 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0636\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0633\u0628\u0627\u0646\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cfc6562d-5b7a-4cbe-b451-fb6e588c69d0",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0639\u0643\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5e409b30-4b23-41db-83c3-284231ba3630",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0643\u0631 \u0628\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0645 \u0633\u0643\u0631 \u0623\u0628\u064a\u0636\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0623\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "117c42f2-fe53-4351-8f3e-7224db9ead3b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0633\u0643\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0645 \u0633\u0643\u0631 \u0623\u0628\u064a\u0636\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "19002db4-6f86-4743-a654-2447f3ad0025",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "03b9a6ff-14c3-450a-966a-71fbf33d3f8f",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f2ec3771-759f-473d-86b0-ed7c87cca512",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4732b5f2-e5d7-4370-bb30-879ebec4950e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0634\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0648\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0627\u064a\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "36b0f6f8-5d25-4a53-989d-d411ce7b191a",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "00669e4e-9029-4dda-bbff-6fe38560e69a",
      "question": "\u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u062f\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0644\u0628\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5717e417-2136-44ab-a5cb-eb858da52ab7",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0643\u0647\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0642\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "19857c0b-9b36-4883-a69b-94584f61388b",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a\u0632\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "96b97911-02b3-4308-9ffb-5319f31e306b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0648\u0639 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7d4cd1ab-9d0b-4039-936b-90c74f584297",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u064a \u0646\u0648\u0639 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8efe407a-9567-44f3-8f22-cf2fe291f9d8",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0635\u062d\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0635\u0645\u064a\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ebdee129-80a6-4d51-9e03-7f4bc343e7f5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c \u0642\u062f\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ab7a8ea2-d531-47a0-befc-adbd3c22ec70",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0641\u0627\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0627 \u0642\u0648\u0627\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0635\u0645\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "83fbc89c-06d0-4486-add1-85013bafc186",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0627\u0632\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0633\u0627\u0626\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "aa661181-101e-40a8-83ad-d2bd9e5c3832",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u0648\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0643\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e6cbd457-79e2-4476-b3bf-1d2b723fc38f",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0648\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0643\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8ba2a7ca-182b-4ed3-b871-d95c9bf7dca4",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u064a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0631 \u0647\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6c69d486-7a36-4e21-bc36-b5033f924bb6",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0642\u0637",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0648\u0646\u0647\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "74fdb164-3cf4-42c7-8fe3-8bbdfe455cab",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u064a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ab31c29d-2b7e-46b8-bae1-3aa70ea717cc",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647\u0627 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "67575132-461e-450b-99b9-ffdf71ed0227",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647\u0627 \u0647\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bfd4b4ad-e083-4924-8c4c-6fcebda98b66",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "df8289ca-dbfa-4bd3-8f96-bdb1bd47a227",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0accb0d9-4cf4-4e8b-b57e-f50222e2a254",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643\u061f - \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c7c69074-a9b6-401a-9c36-1277eb0e74d6",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643\u061f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u0634\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "-",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "67009446-50f6-452b-b33b-bff3fb002c85",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0628\u062e\u064a\u0631\u061f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0639\u0645\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "-",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u062d\u062c\u0632",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "61676e2e-4526-4aed-afdc-f60d4b59c59d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0628\u062e\u064a\u0631\u061f - \u0646\u0639\u0645\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "53c05964-eefb-4d97-8e63-2564b5b74ee4",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0648\u0645\u0643\u061f - \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "916f210f-6a3a-42c6-966c-fae807df4b85",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0637\u0641\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "75779d5f-053d-4198-a8cd-1588ab6dc397",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0643\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0621\u061f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0639\u0645\u060c \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "-",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fe4bd574-22bc-4b99-b8ae-d23375066b50",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0643\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0621\u061f - \u0646\u0639\u0645\u060c \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4150cd24-3300-400d-98a1-fd9b47ac316b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0648\u0641\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0643\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "47227b45-8dba-4977-a671-6ca559bb6924",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0644\u064a \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0648\u0641\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0641\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "eee0d739-e5ec-4d11-9e73-04b55108550c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0646 \u0644\u0643 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1e1fb560-7db1-4697-91ac-dbf94e50579a",
      "question": "\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a \u0623\u064a \u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2eeaa8e2-83fe-468b-8e43-85ee0c8da3f1",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0648\u062c\u0647\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "27d456fa-0880-48fd-bbaa-e1612380cbe8",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1a466015-770a-4749-8c20-67c6c35fa086",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0630\u0627\u0647\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0635\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3b12eb74-c942-43fa-be87-bdb6694311f4",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "393ea94a-dbe2-4005-9f66-7cb2fb8b8433",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0642\u0631\u0627\u0621\u062a\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c0f2e3e2-c49d-47db-9913-28a260251a69",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0642\u0631\u0627\u0621\u062a\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d2818df1-ffa0-4cdd-a4a0-1d99e58f8c11",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062d\u0628\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0648\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2c187c5b-e4f8-42ce-864c-d17ba23da44d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0648\u0646 \u062a\u062d\u0628\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5eee18eb-57c7-4957-a059-0716b260abbd",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cafcc8ab-f664-4f6d-8e2f-d131ab407c06",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u064a \u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u0645\u0624\u062e\u0631\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0645\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "866173bf-98ee-405a-89fe-62db25e91b13",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0642\u0645\u062a \u0628\u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u0645\u0624\u062e\u0631\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7f438f50-bdc4-4cc8-9399-8ac0eaea052c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u062a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0648\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f512cd59-4db6-4614-b01b-6a67cca4aaa3",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u062a\u0648\u062f \u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u062a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1c8adad3-73c6-4552-ba29-6b9f2d10df3c",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0641\u0631 \u0648\u0627\u0633\u062a\u0643\u0634\u0627\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3b7b8b0d-07b0-4115-8b8e-07d7bf9b5519",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0645\u062a \u0628\u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u062a\u0647\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d9152855-37f5-48e6-bbe7-a703c0cb8788",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u0642\u0645\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u062a\u0647\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1c908179-81eb-41b3-ac48-f7023c056604",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u0642\u0645\u062a \u0628\u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u062a\u0647\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d5895bd5-e0b1-425b-a791-702de6b5636f",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0645\u0635\u0631 \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u062d\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b29b1d76-bf8d-42f5-8e99-013d5b5e155d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u062d\u064a\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0645\u0635\u0631 \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a3be267a-cf20-4d3e-83db-27d0cfcb62f1",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0632\u0648\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "aa89ddc8-46ae-4ec4-9459-620c4ee8a249",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0644\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f - \u0622\u0633\u0641\u060c \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0641\u0627\u0636",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8b3d5883-3350-4cc1-89e7-9ceb06c58c20",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0644\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0644\u064a\u061f - \u0622\u0633\u0641\u060c \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0641\u0627\u0636",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c23b2446-48bf-4950-8f29-ebbe2dc8944b",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3f669170-e608-44fa-b949-83d06b92f437",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u0628\u0642\u0649 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062d\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0642\u0648\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "19e3665f-1585-43e5-8960-2d583959fda4",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0646\u062c\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062d\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "26eecf47-ab9f-4868-82e2-cce715402725",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0646\u062c\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3efb6a2e-cc6d-406f-8cbb-54f2e1d779c2",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0646\u062a\u0638\u0627\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062d\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062e\u0628\u0631\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3b28618e-b451-4a70-a3e9-d11ae8a68b49",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0646\u062a\u0638\u0627\u0631 \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d4d0d9e8-492b-4063-b5a0-d937d91ac263",
      "question": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u062a\u0630\u0647\u0628\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "effb9537-ddda-4ede-9eb0-1de1b1857cbd",
      "question": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u064a\u0642\u0638 \u0639\u0627\u062f\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u0628\u064a\u0628\u064a\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "78eb5ef2-f683-4b46-bb7b-e5df3692c593",
      "question": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u064a\u0642\u0638 \u0639\u0627\u062f\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "02c36b67-57bd-4802-8e4b-3efd6964c039",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d \u0637\u0648\u0627\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062d\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "36ff0a3e-7d2e-4261-9e51-c95416638eea",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6cf85a1d-640a-4335-864a-2fceb41a07e6",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9953db09-c85b-4137-a335-3f953ba55963",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u062a\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "80f843a6-a164-4a11-9bf7-f9a1de4e7aa5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062c\u0644\u0628 \u0644\u064a \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9902c643-6661-49e6-bc0d-82afea3010c8",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0642\u0648\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cfc06888-7f1d-48de-8abb-90a007abd2f0",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0642\u0648\u0645 \u0628\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0648\u0627\u0639\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2685d3db-0fa7-4687-bf21-960fabc447fe",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0644\u062a\u0632\u0645 \u0628\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u063a\u0627\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b6d84abc-f4f9-42cb-a2ad-b6b6fb4450be",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5d0e4003-a576-4012-9482-4129fd136538",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0646\u062f\u0642 \u064a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7140f050-80fc-4b40-8e86-a83f11705676",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0646\u062f\u0642",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "125cd669-ffd8-4657-a869-8ef10254d290",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0638\u0647\u0631 \u0644\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "95a62cbe-f575-4cef-95a0-c535b7024cc9",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0627 \u062b\u0644\u0627\u062b \u063a\u0631\u0641 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "aacb2f17-adc5-4ed1-a688-3314ce0b6deb",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u063a\u0631\u0641 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u062b\u0644\u0627\u062b",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0642\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "80283fd2-0de1-436d-9b96-6fdd1bd79ba8",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u0633\u0623\u0642\u064a\u0645 \u0641\u064a\u0647\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0d807ddf-2144-480a-9e30-c21902706612",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u0633\u0623\u0642\u064a\u0645 \u0641\u064a\u0647\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "42682b5c-0487-4fc8-9f49-1421acd5c87c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a\u0647\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0623\u0642\u064a\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bb17c108-4275-475e-9da2-abb992e09e5e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629 \u0648\u0645\u0631\u064a\u062d\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "18438d42-1537-433e-a0aa-167e7c4b5021",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0627\u062d\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1ecbe59d-9f34-4d18-a7a9-be9453ff59cd",
      "question": "\u064a\u0646 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u062a\u0627\u062d\u064a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3f87b1ea-f07f-4b8c-bf53-4ee9f12ddfca",
      "question": "\u064a\u0646 \u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0630\u0647\u0628\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9c44cfe2-9aaf-4bed-a8a9-a27e0d6278b9",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0631\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a03b3bba-b985-4ffb-aba3-1bab6a7fd5a4",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0632\u064a\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5affb07a-33da-4ac0-82cc-6c14554084c6",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0632\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6bef1e6a-f76f-415d-98a7-a22358a20387",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "907cc075-ebe8-4a8a-bff5-7979ef1e8506",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8328ad00-ccd3-4537-a02a-b3e9b5a2eb3f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "27b15d3b-5f5f-4d41-b7c1-6b47dc7433a6",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ce3497a6-050f-42bd-a19b-7ac578f81cde",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u0628\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f1767947-f062-4ed4-b76a-9088aa450db5",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "00412a38-c35b-4c98-8f52-7041c3ed1cfe",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0638\u064a\u0641 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5442138c-4436-44ef-bc70-bc5bf348735e",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0645\u0636\u064a \u0648\u0642\u062a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0631\u0627\u0621\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bf3a7bc3-ef47-4e44-bf73-9a6b2a6d8446",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0627 \u062a\u062a\u0645\u0646\u0627\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c4993341-b21d-4adc-961d-a85a4415434c",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "edc536eb-ea0f-4fff-8761-43daa2f71800",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0647\u0627\u062a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "31547973-8307-41f6-97e3-8e509ed50dc7",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7cd97924-c327-438b-909c-b9d646f9ee7b",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3b0ffe4d-9f9a-4676-a677-7eca38d9e8db",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c1f52a0e-9360-4f1c-b48f-cd4d657d1674",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0635\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "33809bd5-7a83-408f-8ea2-b443da724f81",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0627 \u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d1c588a4-5381-41aa-839e-0fb29d2075de",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u062e\u064a\u0631\u061f - \u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0f37b2b0-5f51-4813-bbd7-432c05c280be",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0628\u062e\u064a\u0631\u061f - \u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5cef2309-5154-4a97-b4fd-baa0fdcaa699",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a\u061f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "-",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d1038079-1fcf-46a8-92cc-1b08f7cd4018",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f - \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u062f\u0627\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8a9076e3-af1f-44b5-8daa-c3209a0c728d",
      "question": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633 \u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a0af9a51-f7de-4984-a3c9-29de161762f2",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "55778ce7-0c53-470f-bc06-64ba165465a5",
      "question": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7194b3f4-a2b3-4d4c-b9e8-d97c17152a9c",
      "question": "\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0627\u0626\u0644\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a21f9041-1533-4e30-a5da-f30b7f70dcac",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0639\u064a\u0634 \u0641\u064a \u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d74ccd5c-4ef9-449e-b48c-79d88df36e8c",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0639\u064a\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5aa9319b-eb79-4731-8ee1-3f959074b284",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u064a\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "334da3d2-0cca-4959-a7b4-d4ee83bc8d29",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629 \u062d\u0636\u0631\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fee624ee-7198-48c4-bc9e-efa415800126",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e80e1e33-db2f-439d-83c2-6bcf52b90c7c",
      "question": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634 \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5e5e65a4-5482-43c7-8d70-585eb7291143",
      "question": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634 \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0634\u0631\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2b4ea1ad-f027-45fa-84d2-20346fb1df00",
      "question": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634 \u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "899282fe-ce10-4c3c-a49b-0316dc6b4709",
      "question": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634 \u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0628\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b9b4a458-e48a-4d56-97fa-caf4c0fdedbb",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0641\u0633\u064a\u0631 \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u062d\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "04d223e8-be2a-45a6-9cdb-ccfa22dc078b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0641\u0633\u064a\u0631 \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "14d281eb-fd63-4e87-9451-5bc5b3fb26aa",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062c\u0645\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5c194b90-cb2b-4b12-a92e-180ed2ad1177",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0639\u062a\u0645\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4ecfdb83-d813-4195-8f1c-583924c66eb7",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u0629 \u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9540fb4a-0eab-437c-b1e9-8b8686352f30",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "63b050c9-cc80-4aa0-a7f4-1cf24d101127",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u0645\u0647\u0645\u0629 \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621 \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "031394cd-89eb-4289-84f4-efca2bcc9570",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0638\u0627\u0645 \u062a\u0642\u0644\u064a\u0644 \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "eeda7332-1a06-423c-aeb5-7c2b48944fa5",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0638\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u0628\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1833e8f7-8943-448c-987b-b83392208cda",
      "question": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0627\u0629 \u062a\u0632\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f\u0627 \u0628\u0639\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "874bb324-3ed0-4162-a5ee-d127ade81c40",
      "question": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0627\u0629 \u062a\u0632\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0639\u062f \u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9166af7d-1b2c-4d89-a3ec-22855aa8303d",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0627\u0628\u0644\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0646\u0628\u063a\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ee493856-f00d-4fb2-871e-736fdee987f3",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0648\u0627\u0639\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "932f40fa-d9ae-4d1c-9091-ac4c0941bcf7",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0648\u0627\u0639\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646\u0647\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9d8b835a-b849-4575-b784-5d4611800168",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8f1ccd9e-546e-4f39-8c45-a2ddeb99cd28",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ecb1c489-edf8-42f0-8998-ed58b7902dd1",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0627\u0626\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u0633\u0628\u0642\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u062d\u062c\u0632",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u0648\u062d\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "84e36e3e-9c87-4546-aa89-f67794029e40",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0623\u062e\u0630\u0646\u064a \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1b273ab3-7f59-4eff-b3c9-139d701262b2",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0623\u062e\u0630\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ff03685e-9390-49e2-aa11-691541bb4fcf",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "72832e26-79c1-46be-8eb1-e0ab23f848d9",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ff3316e4-3fe3-4b8a-9697-eb9d5750d99b",
      "question": "\u0623\u0645\u064a \u0647\u064a \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0634\u062e\u0635 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e119e499-08fe-49da-ae3d-b0900c462164",
      "question": "\u0623\u0645\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0645 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2fc0ebce-a860-425d-b4f3-bd09087f0bef",
      "question": "\u0623\u0645\u064a \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u062f\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "14e3102f-1793-49df-966e-3584fa777feb",
      "question": "\u0643\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062e",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f556c0da-eef8-4c2c-b7b7-3715d110200e",
      "question": "\u0643\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0627\u0639\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dd1d7f31-e4a3-4e2f-b424-b56b748b1b40",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0643\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c83b1ddd-f573-4e61-816b-7f9f54f4af83",
      "question": "\u0643\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9d1c0c96-9c0c-446c-a4d1-e3bcc2a8478a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cf4bc712-6b35-406e-9a85-1c56d9fafe40",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0f09e92e-f991-4b62-a8e2-168cceb1a793",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639\u064b\u0627 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c9f3d106-c012-4e34-a675-2be7da3ac491",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d40b14c3-a3cd-43f2-8b95-bcc7cbb7ee19",
      "question": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6461a7e8-3d1d-460c-9476-7c2310d4d8de",
      "question": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0644\u0627\u062c\u062a\u064a\u0627\u0632 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0627\u0645\u062a\u062d\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "11f6fdbf-0dec-45ab-afcd-261a30e40782",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0644\u0644\u0635\u0644\u0627\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "03923620-d123-4455-9022-9a961075684b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0645 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0645 \u0639\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "50a9f2aa-046f-481a-84c9-85af5c27fc03",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0645 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0645 \u0639\u0627\u0644\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u062f\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0648\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2e5029af-0bf3-472e-baac-ba732130e739",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5917cb01-5aad-4913-999a-2f7305068102",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b6ce6f48-6d23-4b28-a51f-2953c22e9f85",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5e3feb74-9ac8-457a-b6e8-c97aaca20c4a",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0639\u0646\u0627\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3863dcf0-1f4e-44da-9d57-834187ca3625",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u064a \u062f\u0648\u0644\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4aba7c1d-46a3-49f1-8b6e-ec586af3bc8a",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0631\u0623\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "10ccf9d7-8b1b-4141-97ec-4c77290131c5",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629 \u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0645\u062a\u0646\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "84053b09-3919-41f6-b711-c00a5fa37d3e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0644\u0628 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0632\u064a\u062f\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e29baf21-f219-4a32-ab6b-7079ab335b07",
      "question": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0637\u0648\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b409e370-37c7-4a11-a998-d2eab2f6646e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0637\u0648\u0631 \u0643\u0644 \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "303add07-bcd7-4ffb-b33c-a4cfaf3b86dc",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0644\u0648\u0645\u0627\u062a \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0631\u0646\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2d6a52b6-19c0-4b9d-8080-aacb630f9e64",
      "question": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0644\u0648\u0645\u0627\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0631\u0646\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "35f96c4d-435c-46be-8586-46232b365482",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "adbddb64-44d6-4a70-81e0-ee9ea55391f5",
      "question": "\u0643\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0639\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1fcc36a7-4f52-4e90-a34f-84bee9c6f57a",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0631\u0643\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "361c27b2-1446-4e01-b6cd-93f4f80d8485",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0631\u0643\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c8ae028d-18e9-42a9-86e1-98f1315792e2",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0645\u0648\u0627\u0639\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062c\u0645\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4853efc1-4d8a-4033-83bd-d30c080e3e01",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u0645\u0632\u062f\u062d\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "86f54824-27b5-446b-b843-a4384fe36b80",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u062f \u0648\u0635\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2ba28f3d-c80a-466b-8285-8f9a7a42abc5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0623\u062e\u0630 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d84cd9e3-63d8-4a08-9a81-80eb30a9f403",
      "question": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6fa2b126-70dc-4bc4-97d1-3d91111a2d16",
      "question": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6bb25c0c-2d02-4676-ba2b-b208fad75e0a",
      "question": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3d533a38-1868-44bb-910f-9c25cdd628de",
      "question": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0631\u064a\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629 \u0643\u0644 \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0627\u0644\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0648\u0646\u0647\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "974a2441-2d76-4f04-80e9-a2b009b3e590",
      "question": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0627\u0644\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u064a\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u0644\u064a\u0644\u0627\u064b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e332ded4-64be-42be-a48f-fafb6a005efd",
      "question": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0627\u0639\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "70ef8d04-f528-40b5-a8db-35e76c3aa58c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0627\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "594d9941-05b7-4dd6-8920-ffc08dd73026",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0644 \u0644\u064a\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u062a\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3f3ec1bb-ae29-40f4-8b77-ccc3d4946536",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a\u0633 \u0645\u0627\u062a\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062a\u062c\u0644\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "39aa702d-1976-4ca3-8c74-3ca31cd9c272",
      "question": "\u0646\u0645\u062a \u0637\u0648\u0627\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "23168e93-8c32-487e-936c-74ea913bfa85",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644\u0629 \u0627\u061f\u061f\u061f\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7fa29361-e361-44b3-b06d-00e1cb6d0a28",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c16de3b2-35c8-456d-8daa-2b94ca1efa1c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u062c\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "48703ee2-cc24-4f60-b26b-a2f4118dee97",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0631\u062c\u0644\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "48531b8d-4381-4e07-a819-22e6cd4e8a03",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4dcd08c6-350f-477c-817b-da284b3f48bb",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7dea46eb-30b9-40b4-9f00-59862bd762d0",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0644\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b95afdbf-eac5-4b0e-a772-9eebef6429d1",
      "question": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646 \u0646\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u063a\u062a\u0647\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "64be0205-0981-4eac-b413-be8de1021216",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0633\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8011086d-a0e0-4178-8844-0ff757083344",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9298b694-da76-46b3-ad72-40a20df0a0d5",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a\u0632\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u063a\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6677492d-e85c-42df-ab6b-7a75fedbcac4",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0647\u0649",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0623\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "63ec27e5-32a2-4b51-9898-fe1b1f7535cf",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0631\u0623\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7ea5fe8e-d5c0-4a16-b98d-6154b1030fb2",
      "question": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a66c470f-7492-47c2-a93d-2b2dbf5b133d",
      "question": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u0645\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "eeec873a-c8ab-41d6-b6b1-9e5159b485f7",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646 \u0643\u0646\u062a \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0648\u0643\u0648\u0644\u0627\u062a\u0629\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8159f7d2-3f17-474d-8e0c-b9cda3323b47",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646 \u0643\u0646\u062a \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0648\u0643\u0648\u0644\u0627\u062a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "77cdb879-9ec5-40b8-be5c-95b253b8763a",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u064a \u0623\u0633\u0626\u0644\u0629\u060c \u0641\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u062a\u0631\u062f\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0637\u0631\u062d\u0647\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "33134866-a5c9-40d6-8479-809e50c16f08",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0646\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c5a33e6a-9df6-4fb1-a397-9f8b4eaea842",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643 \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0646\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3c2d7df8-b1ea-4b12-bb81-9570a722d3d7",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u062c\u0648\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ced67f0c-af33-4c3a-8309-545c925ec92d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a \u062a\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0639\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1b6c4e90-d3d1-4879-ae97-ef7bf78d5cd4",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0648\u0639\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bee0a1da-6849-4f58-8c64-230553e726ce",
      "question": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a51494fa-69f9-40a9-9fc0-63fa58b8dc1f",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u062e\u0631\u062c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0642\u0631\u064a\u0628\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a825d5fa-d695-4f88-ba5c-eb9b759bf620",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0633\u062a\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6372979d-0ff3-4081-9f14-67d852dc1dd0",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u064a\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0628\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0628\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7272690b-6c42-44bb-b725-c9124d91a851",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u061f\u061f\u061f\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "76f88ad6-0611-4628-9adb-dacd17651c34",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0645\u0627 \u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0623\u0634\u062a\u0631\u064a \u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4b9f2c9a-0663-44c7-a7c3-3a202a985812",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5bb37809-9ee8-4d08-9726-18819910d576",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0643\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "94530930-85f0-4ce8-a2bf-7af52c5a17f7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ee761625-1af1-42d0-b50f-1ba319565db1",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "37d3e88f-b37e-45a7-8e74-4237e2b63a7d",
      "question": "\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0636\u0648\u0636\u0627\u0621!",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4994378e-0856-4a6a-9e78-41d3413ba8ff",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062b \u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0639\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "dffc2cf3-57fb-4bf5-8ea3-6bdc84fd2548",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u0639\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bfb208ad-77f7-42bf-bffe-403d05979f9f",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0646\u064a \u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "daf73659-fc0d-439a-83bd-57a65b9500e3",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646\u0647 \u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0633\u0628\u0629 \u0644\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0646\u0627\u0645\u062c\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "745079ae-b523-4581-84d5-d02f2a20d025",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6deb611e-5c4d-4b66-b0e4-1c3fde66eb68",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u0648\u0645\u062a\u0646\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8e9771f7-5c9c-410c-8566-10550480dd6d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "62bffc64-1e75-49eb-8578-fdcc5c600653",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0646\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f287bde4-5356-478c-82dc-8e65f5b38613",
      "question": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0644\u0628\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0632\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "aadd2909-02b7-4df1-8e93-5f54abc638fc",
      "question": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0644\u0628\u0648\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "212eea1c-4215-47f0-a3b6-ddbf39141fa6",
      "question": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fcd2d6a6-6841-48f6-91d2-ffb54afe0754",
      "question": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u0648\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0645\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7852a04a-c15b-43ca-9f67-c2f7fa07a107",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "20bd5839-cb56-49a8-99d2-392de01ae616",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "93617ccd-ec7c-4081-9333-37d15de1190a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u064a \u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0648\u0627\u0637\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e34ff0c0-76d4-47e3-8df5-f090ac754ae1",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0645\u0627\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "27195773-603f-421a-a3d1-b7314510ea5d",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a431ce5d-5e10-4eab-a696-9aad808b2bfb",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "01652d00-f1b2-4a47-b19d-a05e55e29262",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c9f1ba78-9ba1-4537-91da-666e146851f0",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0642\u062a\u0631\u0627\u062d \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u062a\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9480a08e-edc0-4505-8746-2aca978150f2",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0642\u062a\u0631\u0627\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cbf4b3b0-ce73-4ea9-bf6d-ed311f22ddd9",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0639\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d36aecd5-13d0-4494-be24-50a33c437a03",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0639\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fcc4b8fd-5e8f-4e0b-91b7-ff2238a8d09a",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0644\u0648\u0643 \u063a\u064a\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u063a\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0644\u0627\u0626\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5ac5878a-7f8d-4fa8-a9c1-1e20aeac5034",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u063a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0644\u0627\u0626\u0645 \u063a\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0644\u0648\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7aed4a76-b29b-4d5c-89a4-35a7c1636809",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "48d12307-b549-4967-925e-e687c63dd1be",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0638\u0647\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "-",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2b29ad60-a095-4255-b3ec-8db120b1ec14",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0629 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u062f\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4309f6d8-e44d-4756-a76d-7008fc43bba2",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0644\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "32fc7bcd-1483-4c1a-b391-75ac3ecdf065",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u0639\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c815cdc5-8bc5-4aa9-b75d-230aaa1a595f",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a92c0782-bfa8-4c04-8572-d4eed633368d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e00d46fe-81c0-458a-8ee4-da73d685b851",
      "question": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0636\u0648\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7cf2ea67-73b4-4144-b7c2-6e969c17306f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u0632\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u062d\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "eec08ed3-c439-47ae-bf60-44dd85795631",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u0632\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ab9b9213-0d17-4b5d-a7c0-884b5d2b9c9e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "101f6547-e7eb-41b0-bfb2-6ecce878bd6b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a\u0632\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "77ccfd38-9a1b-4a28-acb6-91c793e07aa6",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a2c759ae-e58e-4709-b6fe-673ef2db9187",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f\u064a\u0646 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0637\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cc4a39ed-385f-445d-8faa-831247ba26fa",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0633\u0628\u0629 \u0644\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "23514dd2-f3f3-4247-91ba-7517dcc49c88",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u0628\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0623\u062c\u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "98a0f79c-c0d7-4008-aca7-69e00c0afaa1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u0628\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0644\u0623\u062c\u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bc817300-fbf4-4b8b-8a58-4575c5900ba7",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649 \u062a\u0639\u0628\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0627\u0639\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2a9d7365-2fc9-4908-b30a-64f95e4462b7",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649 \u062a\u0639\u0628\u0631 \u0639\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0627\u0639\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ee314ab5-ef06-41e4-a5a2-3009d256b898",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c5d0f24e-50a4-4fb2-92ae-9590a739daba",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062d\u0628 \u0644\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a49c6968-8339-4758-bd36-18672f8b4e99",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5881512c-ba57-441e-86b7-ce2e89255df0",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u064a\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "604e6c90-b47f-4e66-941e-af43b3193bd7",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0648\u062d\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cb579573-7b21-4189-a7aa-196c96d7c65b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u063a\u0631\u0648\u0628 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0645\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "88c7ddda-e661-4490-af84-b55b699025c9",
      "question": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0635\u063a\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0634\u064a\u0627\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d48c30fd-5307-4a19-8523-fa79f861a97b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u0644\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0639\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "14628462-9966-4d57-8172-9380870c54a4",
      "question": "\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u0633\u062a\u0623\u062a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "79d64bb1-b971-4c1c-87f7-b28792010f1c",
      "question": "\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u062a\u0623\u062a\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0641\u062a\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b4c9ae09-af34-44b6-acb4-93e5f05bd0dd",
      "question": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647 \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0647\u062a\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "503ff495-a383-4124-a247-5fb02b0c4bc5",
      "question": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647 \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u062a\u062a\u0631\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "be2b1e1d-6b07-42d7-8367-578546b0519e",
      "question": "\u0622\u0633\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0631\u062d\u062a \u0645\u0634\u0627\u0639\u0631\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9cd0bad9-317e-46b5-9d3f-ea11c98948de",
      "question": "\u0622\u0633\u0641 \u0625\u0630\u0627 \u062c\u0631\u062d\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u0627\u0639\u0631\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645)",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "40c537c2-79d2-44d2-8ede-febde8aa0bcf",
      "question": "\u0622\u0633\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0643\u0641\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b223f13e-d194-4c55-a85e-68f314b6eb68",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0627\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "84d0ab66-c5a0-43fe-a675-a3216850b38a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u062c\u0639\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a \u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0641\u0627\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "829249c6-c90d-4c7e-b4a0-ee163701ed91",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0641\u062d\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8761b38a-6443-446d-a6df-97974828e7ea",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "30eec318-12f9-4f58-a055-0f4afdad40db",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8a93b092-79ea-42b7-9a50-78ab3bbea7c6",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8af04ca8-8e49-4c55-ae9e-e10c1eb0bb33",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0641\u062d\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "59093138-12de-4e76-a16f-b902aa17ce0b",
      "question": "\u062f\u0648\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0633\u0627\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "75bdcfcd-4799-477a-9724-1ac4f95eb3d5",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6162a109-92cd-4246-b374-8a3d53aa9e1a",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "77c205ba-f0a6-4f7b-ad3b-be0b2789cfa2",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u0639\u064a\u0646\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b9d9cad2-d6c0-490c-a7f8-47f6f0cd7294",
      "question": "\u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629 \u062a\u0628\u062f\u0623 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "16301036-5521-47e9-a4f0-e48b798c1ac5",
      "question": "\u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0628\u062f\u0623 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "42c5b1e7-dcb6-46d3-aeb3-34daf535f495",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7da204af-65a6-48d8-bd7b-27e067ed43c9",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bab21445-fd81-49cd-9c5b-5053a8b4d9db",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1c3b3e9b-a32a-4d0a-88f7-3a229240b34d",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d135e880-1d59-45ad-93a3-5d2b56bd298d",
      "question": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0631\u0642\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "93440f42-c247-43e6-a6ec-1b56035347a9",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4295c0c8-8c92-4b07-b91f-bd503b553ab6",
      "question": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7878defa-bc8d-4feb-8f7a-4ab964ac123f",
      "question": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "17b498ca-dcd2-486b-969f-683d27a29d6a",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u062d\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0635",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0631\u062c\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0631\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7585342e-c890-4483-b36e-6a37bf98bfa6",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8d7ac68d-665c-4c38-8f95-aae8308acd57",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0627\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u062d\u062c\u0632",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "77f224cc-10d5-446e-b240-3e29cf48a475",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u062d\u064a\u062d \u0644\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u063a\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b5c416d3-3da8-47dd-ac79-4c45d46167a8",
      "question": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645) \u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639 \u0644\u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0634\u0627\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "940dafd7-1ed5-4b31-a44e-a2130d705eee",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0634\u0647\u0648\u0631 \u0628\u0623\u0637\u0628\u0627\u0642\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645)",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c2a7dd9e-c083-4fdb-88d1-3798e8508811",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0640 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "af465a4e-ddeb-4fbd-ab94-89aea36e0715",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0640 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "58aea7de-a11f-43b3-a1f7-99bd90f926de",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0640 \u0645\u0633\u0631\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "150ded31-152d-4aa6-8b17-f5ff1a1e6768",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0633\u0631\u062d \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0640",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "40d933d9-0369-4452-bd58-f94dd17f731a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "correct_answer": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645)",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2c125e25-2ae0-4354-be84-966c15c79edd",
      "question": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645) \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ddad7bcb-fd41-4890-890e-4d679e9f61f0",
      "question": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645) \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "37c9fe5f-82bb-4cfa-b838-2448893953bb",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645 \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645)",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8e9e9bc4-f9dc-48d5-82d8-beabec9e5242",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c \u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "86038069-a199-447b-a311-2673369ff58c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644 \u0641\u064a \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0635\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "adf3b50e-27d5-4582-98a4-e34800a17688",
      "question": "\u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062f\u0648\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "91edf4e3-6809-49e9-9f2f-bcdf151e4ce2",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f953f027-7630-4362-95c9-3d6923b43d0a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0644\u062d\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ec97a2b9-38b5-485e-be16-89684fb440ce",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ede40320-59d5-4c32-99f0-c5b282628538",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627 \u0647\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "332fe340-4528-4032-8b22-9ac07538ac2b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "158c696f-04ec-41b7-bb73-6572a9d4d7f1",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0627\u064a\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0a217f9b-a1b2-4143-b095-83ae4857b599",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0633\u062a\u0631\u062e\u0627\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c0b8e039-4dca-4dd0-bdb4-991a40d2ccb1",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0627\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "36915304-50ff-4362-9773-0ea1b5ce1ec6",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u0634\u0627\u064a\u064b\u0627 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "763b33de-77e7-40b5-a7ff-c5a8a038067d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0633\u062a\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0633\u0627\u0626\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4d22edcf-8165-48a2-8128-7c5b04b420c1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0645\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u062f\u0627\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0645\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "28e74620-7196-4b89-a0fd-2868ab4eebca",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u0648\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "07f31653-898a-4b77-bcc4-d635d084022b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "09c491f8-a403-4510-9649-c55616490c8c",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0648\u0646\u0647\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d99ff5a5-6dec-4bb1-9304-f58116742076",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0643\u0647\u0629 \u0645\u0646\u0639\u0634\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0636\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "652b60f0-05c0-492b-8567-d3bae236c8a3",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0636\u064a\u0641 \u0646\u0643\u0647\u0629 \u0645\u0646\u0639\u0634\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ea831637-fffb-4b65-850b-38e3a21e7ff7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a3353611-c932-4fe1-ad7c-ba19eae6a6ee",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0dd7230e-1d83-4058-86a8-c6d5184602a2",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0639\u062f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "04d72b54-5795-46c1-b2cb-52ffbe6b11a7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "edb19998-7549-44d2-92db-ecef6e7f84b4",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0632\u064a\u062f\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3633cfce-b403-4658-a50e-83675bf49526",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0632\u064a\u062f\u060c \u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1495b8d6-6a0e-4202-9d78-c68f09031c27",
      "question": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u062c\u0628\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fe6a623a-19a0-410a-84b9-9a3d43a07c02",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0648\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0643\u0648\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8487b728-1e10-4290-88e3-d3869d4c28a3",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u062c\u0627\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0b1a1e22-3d37-482f-b55b-0343bb7c8ee0",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0635\u0639\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u062a\u0630\u0647\u0628\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "77c12e73-997f-494d-aaab-7a0d89774eae",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0635\u062d\u064a\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c872433b-9873-436f-9405-07cdc1de00bf",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u0647 \u0633\u064a\u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u062a\u0642\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f00d3fc3-2d87-41e4-add7-ae7bd7462695",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u062a\u0642\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0647 \u0633\u064a\u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "04f11498-6acf-4c0c-bddf-8893ae6c9a26",
      "question": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0644\u0644\u0627\u0647\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1600f4fe-f6d2-421e-a885-1efa83692b35",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u0641\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8489d9ee-dcc1-4dbc-9aad-616fe1c26a1b",
      "question": "\u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0631\u0627\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "452c0bd4-c745-4e95-a1ba-9f41317a7bc1",
      "question": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0633\u064a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0634\u0645\u0633\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8e625b26-99f9-4ce3-9e7e-3f042a5bf935",
      "question": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0637\u0644\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6c118ac4-5091-4f15-bc46-76e12aad7238",
      "question": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0637\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f27c5018-6efb-45a6-a86d-ed506a86925e",
      "question": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "83cf9606-918e-44f5-a325-b75e58c600ee",
      "question": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "55a764d8-e2e0-4a08-8250-1e7af074dbe5",
      "question": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643 \u0641\u0631\u0635\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fa0a66cf-b0f9-4bae-a68c-5a70d7375661",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0631\u0635\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "32f7d8db-f44f-46b4-b35f-b386b9b17b28",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u0627\u062a \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b914604d-060c-4e4f-bf09-bc19f4c94e7b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0648\u0645\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e0f743d3-8f7c-4b2f-8102-a7501bd279d6",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0631\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u062a\u0623\u062a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "eb73dd2d-20f1-46d0-ad26-64e7b533e7af",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u0644\u0647\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0635\u0645\u064a\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fd89cfe3-137b-43fa-9ba4-de1a845ff3b8",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2854c757-a8ee-4372-b3b0-cf3ab468277c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0628\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0642\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "443d2839-4bd6-4731-b80e-cd7780c3f70e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633 \u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "40463459-ff1a-4f61-9780-ab804419e24d",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633 \u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "41effe74-8799-4e54-9fa4-4833dcafcb22",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0645\u062a\u0646\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ec7e90f0-fe04-4c85-9d6d-24afc1a1e35f",
      "question": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8a9fdf9c-d0fe-4a63-bbbb-bda55bea01fc",
      "question": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "44a65470-1361-494c-9199-5946f06719c3",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633 \u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2a3e3ec7-4516-4c04-b33a-a4827057dce6",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633 \u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d6178db0-db44-429d-bffc-d2ec4ecbf178",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643\u061f \u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ea4d3491-c628-4679-99bc-0846f70af1c6",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u062e\u064a\u0631\u060c \u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cfea3a82-023a-4e57-b10e-4e82717a4f8d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062a\u0634\u0639\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3d92e716-a927-4bd0-90d4-4898de247336",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062f \u064a\u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0648\u0642\u062a\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0627\u064a\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "19559c82-f884-4a53-adb2-04b18ade4839",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "749c5ea6-1d20-4ce6-91dc-9e0076f1af5f",
      "question": "\u0647\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "78cc9ccb-f7d6-4e14-8745-e0380d8bf31f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 \u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "607c210e-0181-442d-a762-b1ef4db18537",
      "question": "\u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0630\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "31e5e498-653f-4797-a7eb-75a1c63720b2",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u062a\u0639\u0648\u062f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "850fd4b9-ee72-4e75-99ba-fced5b7e4af2",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8670e9b0-306f-4093-aad2-7dde261c2fcd",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "30976176-3660-4ce6-8834-c40501926ab6",
      "question": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0628\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b5c7cd93-606e-4160-a6f3-c68e12399edf",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "106a8026-f055-4536-901f-46ea5edab1fb",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "424ee551-8303-4522-8b24-b8737e963b14",
      "question": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0647\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0628\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062f\u0627\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "84fbb6e5-12c9-4722-bf7a-7adbb5e9c434",
      "question": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0628\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7eb9d1f1-ea26-43dd-96f8-bb7337d426d0",
      "question": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4a491a7d-5117-4503-bb52-0c0b817a7a7a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u0648\u0645 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2218ce65-d4eb-41eb-a83d-673ec32a34ed",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u062c\u064a\u062f \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0faee2d2-a8f1-461c-9dfa-1f981110a6d1",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a\u062f \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f145eda6-4514-496c-8f2c-248a04b528c4",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0646\u0642\u0648\u062f \u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6f81e444-67b1-45e2-9d95-121c8894994d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0637\u0627\u0644\u0628 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0641\u0644\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f5357873-9270-4160-bb60-c740fcabd442",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u063a\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fffdb5c1-e699-4ea0-945a-88c2d2672320",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0647\u0645 \u0645\u062c\u0645\u0648\u0639\u0629 \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0627\u0646\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b43fdce3-3362-4c50-aade-6fbeb187c0ad",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u064a\u0645\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0627\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6ecb1dbd-a6d1-4c48-9b10-9546dac49a52",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645)",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2ad764d5-7f92-4c81-b443-ec1900abe922",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u062a\u0642\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0647 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0636\u0648\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "88876ae0-1761-4b84-b9d6-7410862813e0",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062b\u0642 \u0628\u0646\u0641\u0633\u0643 \u0648\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0645\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0639\u0644\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3c2fe989-0d8f-49e1-be31-6c37b4debacb",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062b\u0642 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0645\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0641\u0639\u0644\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0646\u0641\u0633\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623\u0647\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e9ba383d-b737-44c2-82a4-efcb9fff0fc5",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u0628\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "68cd7737-591d-4d88-b20b-0759d757133b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u062a\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a069585f-26f4-4704-994a-3b7c7fb1156e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0639\u0643\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a6b09abb-8084-4528-a1f7-85b58085b875",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0642\u0627\u062f\u0631\u064b\u0627 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "37fe5455-aba3-48a8-ae12-b195b084cda6",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u063a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5bdc6b23-40e7-4968-8677-b8e1ac8dd5cb",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0636\u0639 \u062c\u0647\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0634\u063a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "27bb25e7-63d5-43e9-a43b-76b48880012e",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0647\u0627\u0632\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "58bf798e-b047-426a-bd11-cf6c5558a6fc",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0630\u0647\u0628\u0648\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "08bc20ab-dd0a-4bd5-b863-26aa874644d4",
      "question": "\u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "44c2ad71-449f-428a-be22-1daa116cc04e",
      "question": "\u0642\u0645 \u0628\u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u0648\u0627\u0639\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ee09a78a-4c90-443d-8f85-dae192bd025e",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0636\u0631\u0648\u0631\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bb73a69e-2cad-4870-b358-90bb498d4657",
      "question": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5ad0bc97-3f65-4c5d-a3bc-c4c0d7e768fb",
      "question": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9d6ef4e9-ab7e-4fd3-b3fc-8d4720f88901",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9029015a-96fa-462f-aecf-ad4f8dd7c5e1",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0621\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ecc792a7-5069-4dd0-80e2-bc7d61a56e6d",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0644\u0643 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0627\u062d\u0642",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8709e304-23c5-4ed3-a877-f764af3a4779",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "86d16023-f81a-4ec7-b62b-9ec389f16e6e",
      "question": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0648\u0627\u0633\u0637\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b52eecb6-09af-45e0-8880-8a8074f205fb",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "372fecd1-325c-4a82-933d-cd7dc2a83eea",
      "question": "\u0641\u0627\u060c \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u0633\u0646\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0627\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "72f7262c-88f1-468c-bfb8-f13b94655976",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0627 \u0623\u0642\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b3a681b6-747e-4712-ac46-a64b58d887c0",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0647\u0645 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0636\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "86646551-b2af-488d-88f8-e6f8c343f770",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0639\u0628 \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0642\u0637",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "77daead9-c818-4c2d-ad3d-e54313878e17",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u064a \u0644\u063a\u062a\u0647\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5c848462-eabf-40cd-9c39-09fe18cb48f3",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0627\u0635\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "98c260c8-00a1-4490-a07b-b02f728c0cab",
      "question": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0635\u064a\u0627\u0646\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e8ef0778-8fce-4235-803e-af96b73fa1b9",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u0633\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0644\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "65e6fc81-dea3-4bea-aa7a-00523a073d9f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "594824e0-bc1b-4a3f-bb22-c40cb9d835e2",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0633\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0645\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ec487c23-699e-48be-a235-e05e19b29d8f",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "813418b6-6866-4b1f-b352-06430fc43801",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648 \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "16510139-e6a3-4daa-b7dc-4841866deb89",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u062a\u0627\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "03ba309d-8e7a-4dcb-873d-47f8c76b802c",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648 \u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0634\u062a\u0627\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6408ff4a-cd1f-448c-b33b-51e6433b4130",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "21cfd8ee-8bea-451b-9fe0-fbe3d83c59ea",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0637\u0627\u0644\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "688ca266-db47-4072-bfd5-ebb8b06edf69",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0637\u0627\u0644\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0631\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "10329f06-726d-47ed-a4f6-82937f9a9147",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0634\u0631\u062d \u0644\u064a \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "38cd6d68-bde8-4a6a-ac2d-0aeb56903aa4",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0634\u0631\u062d \u0644\u064a \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f62e8a7e-8209-479b-ae22-64f52e9b6911",
      "question": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0634\u0631\u062d \u0644\u064a \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d3d4fee8-9903-4f2c-88eb-09791338a577",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0646 \u062e\u0644\u0627\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u0628\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "22e90c17-c37d-46a6-912e-3f5843ec0020",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0632\u0641 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062a\u0627\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0636\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9412d29a-54d3-4d34-ac98-896fa0d8e778",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0647\u062a\u0645 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0645\u062c\u0629 \u0648\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0644\u063a\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0645\u062c\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a937a87f-f85b-4bdf-b279-aff2e3f36f05",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0647\u062a\u0645 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0645\u062c\u0629 \u0648\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0644\u063a\u0627\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0645\u062c\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "54834c69-060c-437a-b46a-ea6c6833aa64",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u0645\u0646\u0630 \u0641\u062a\u0631\u0629 \u0637\u0648\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d6e33bd8-1e82-400e-9b53-15939a869145",
      "question": "\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u0645\u0646\u0630 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0637\u0648\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u062a\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1cdf05b3-404a-4723-85a1-643270a0e087",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0627\u0631\u0633\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "405d839d-de51-4925-9d17-dea81f3efa2e",
      "question": "\u0644\u0645 \u0623\u0633\u0645\u0639 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0fe9a2e7-84c7-4b5f-84c4-bb5a3325351a",
      "question": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "698f57a5-a530-4558-a747-80a7d0155451",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627 \u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "32b4112f-726f-461b-8988-7d68a25e33f4",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0639\u0646\u0627\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u063a\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "46d6542b-284f-476b-a515-c984ce9b09f4",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0643\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b597ca0b-beb5-4fd1-b0ea-293451d559c9",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "520de99b-12f1-4999-93ae-5eac682d15c7",
      "question": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ecc6d61e-b69c-49ea-90d6-d0aabd55bcc8",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062a\u062d\u0631\u0643 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u062d\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0639\u0637\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d97b88e3-9178-4146-abb7-9c86258202e6",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0635\u0641\u062d \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0631\u0646\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "086ae7b9-4109-4965-a608-0526aa66c951",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u0644\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d65efc5a-13e8-4f34-b708-f208b322f033",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u0644\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3b4e4f39-ffb5-4921-887b-1eeda0cf0eef",
      "question": "\u0633\u0627\u0631\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u0646\u062d\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7f1916fe-9e0c-411e-8174-37e5e7a46c42",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u0646\u062d\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0627\u0631\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f2f0b7b8-d777-4af9-be95-a61b32b2bc6b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0636\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643 \u0644\u0641\u062a\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u0637\u0648\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d9d0634a-deae-4625-bd97-08dbaae12865",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4ad7e720-10f3-48a1-b314-8011f9f1b092",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0627 \u062a\u0641\u0643\u0631 \u0628\u0647",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b6549f79-8f2d-439f-9760-ecbcfcd67704",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "041343ac-360a-41c6-956b-c6a684442212",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3bd6a90f-5cb1-45cb-8866-c720d55b07b1",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0648\u0636\u0648\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "eeb37462-e43c-4b05-9c63-c3bb6c34eede",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5ef861ff-abab-4c28-90d0-0117c6432a87",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0634\u0631\u062d \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c209c233-14d8-4c23-aa16-78626aaa5ae1",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bd121e4e-e976-467a-b0e6-d84d22b5149f",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d084cb47-99b0-4d4d-a8da-48c24e9fcd61",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0631\u062d\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2631b052-f8a5-4ec1-8275-9b938579e72e",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u062d\u062f \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e56fcd58-ea7c-4676-988e-7180a2ff5599",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0642\u0637",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4fc90d78-f104-4db3-a0a9-cdee0fd7cd21",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0631\u0649 \u0623\u064a \u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b06419b2-ae01-4c37-bbd6-9e3f664adf81",
      "question": "\u0644\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0631\u0649 \u0623\u064a \u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0628\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6f87284c-1ef3-491b-96db-44e83b6f4b03",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u0628\u0647\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "48ab680a-8238-4517-b203-5559648d209f",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1968168b-beef-4466-b3dd-83bcadb05446",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0627 \u0622\u0643\u0644 \u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4fb662d3-2e48-4093-a502-7b1ba1b03216",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u060c \u0644\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0622\u0643\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7bdcfcef-3c8c-4854-acc7-ad838a960d3e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062e\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a \u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b974327a-eea7-4110-904f-fd77edae819b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062e\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "45f4d6c1-c1b1-43e1-80ac-387a78f0dbf1",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "27057f5b-3a8a-4627-b9e0-703f63239fdd",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646 \u064a\u062a\u062c\u0646\u0628\u0648\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0648\u0627\u0646\u0627\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u0627\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7d488a67-b28d-4986-a2d9-ced6d200ee30",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0647\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8fabd909-ecf7-4bc8-b05b-4db39f5d14e9",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0645\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bba8ca8f-9aed-4c8b-97cc-8d50daa7f7ea",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "20459c76-5251-4d4f-9a89-ed805b1f3a15",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0639\u0645\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0629 \u0644\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0637\u0648\u0627\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f0c080d2-7ac0-4a31-97e9-0a215c15f245",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7e52c4a2-6a30-4584-8b94-f6478bea260c",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0642\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "51e15de3-75ed-4b33-9446-ee306aec2d4d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u063a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u064a\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2ee5ed68-91ae-40d7-af25-3772dfcf2ca1",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "513a36f5-d820-498f-a296-7171958ffd36",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u062e\u0646\u0629 \u0623\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0637\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "43098e88-c0e6-4534-bf6c-a86f58bd726f",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0643\u0648\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "132bd63a-7f1b-4b81-b927-542e30f0e0d8",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0645\u0628\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0623\u062a\u0631\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2973fd64-c402-4d88-9f84-8fa89d7f11c0",
      "question": "\u0633\u0623\u062a\u0631\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0628\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "54701358-5101-40fb-89d6-bdb09bd37254",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d2434704-9f72-4088-9f1c-43c09e4936d3",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a357462d-08f7-4959-83e2-b0b0fa60529b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u0636\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u062d\u062c\u0632",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4281e334-e695-4c2d-9645-ca90bb0bbc67",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d5333e77-3e54-4533-bf5e-25900b3ab9af",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "604ddf7b-6769-4066-8de8-7a3998e9f379",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0634\u0627\u0621 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u062c\u0628\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e3a17e92-c776-4b9e-a4dc-91714295a220",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631 \u0643\u0627\u0646\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0641\u062d\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "75535b82-8dce-4031-ac4a-8710bfce9b22",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "25829079-9271-4480-9581-6411bf960227",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0645\u0646\u062d\u0646\u064a \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u0648\u0642\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cd21b596-f6f0-4425-8a99-f7284b76fef3",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0645\u0646\u062d\u0646\u064a \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u0648\u0642\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0632\u0627\u0626\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b0ecca4c-267b-4500-ac53-356e5c9a05a6",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u0642\u0637 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "16f79347-f697-4968-acb4-2bd27b6dfe86",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0633\u0643\u0631 \u0628\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0645 \u0633\u0643\u0631 \u0623\u0628\u064a\u0636\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e069a24d-efb1-4d44-9d1c-c464eb4b4d7a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0635\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u062a\u0630\u0647\u0628\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "20bb95d0-3e66-4851-971a-1e2a56f8c78a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ff890524-8735-4462-8713-13915afad2db",
      "question": "\u0646\u062d\u0646 \u0646\u0642\u0628\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "32e58024-69b7-4e01-9e35-e4c5061d6431",
      "question": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u063a\u062f\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7172a52b-09c1-42aa-b273-de008221d0bc",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7bb24943-a0d0-44fa-ba03-addcd55fbe76",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c \u0642\u062f\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "115cab07-a99c-4d60-a7f9-919346dc8011",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4d515b46-e44a-4d35-a715-ceb481fa0f8a",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a\u0632\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "148d58f7-4c4d-431d-974e-d16f45270439",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u064a \u0646\u0648\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8a792915-7004-4167-92a7-76783d268211",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u064a \u0646\u0648\u0639 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e175f5bf-2b61-480e-a883-b0742be973fa",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0635\u062d\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3a0cb6da-5a11-43a0-897d-9e81a7b5db17",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4ca16ede-0509-4dce-b4b5-64cc19f8c7f5",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0641\u0627\u0644 \u0623\u0646 \u064a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0648\u0627\u0639\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "21fa89c0-cafe-4606-be58-15fe9caef1dc",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0641\u0627\u0644 \u0623\u0646 \u064a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0627 \u0642\u0648\u0627\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "79eef191-9b50-4a67-96ae-b0ccc4150e6c",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646 \u0647\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0647\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0646\u0647\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cf385a80-130c-4401-97f1-b898e9f03ee2",
      "question": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0648\u0633\u0627\u0626\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0627\u0632\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c79e9574-28df-4af2-beb3-40e2d430cd3c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0647\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "32c01d59-4663-4f49-adad-3b2f9dbe5ff9",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u064a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0631 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "39e579b7-5028-4eb3-9891-4a17eb01726d",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u064a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e05c1deb-353c-4081-ade6-f068b17882d1",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647\u0627 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "15269737-ad11-46a2-a99a-8ac599663f2c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643\u061f - \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u0634\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3cf5238f-760e-48b0-9d01-a8293a8fb691",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u0643\u061f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "-",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "64f08fb8-fdc0-456d-936c-267f2dc9978a",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0632\u0627\u0626\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0633\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e5b76cf4-924e-418b-9e17-90f315c246d4",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0643 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u062a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0633\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "45bbdd31-d6a4-41d0-ad9c-23bccf6c595d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0648\u062c\u0647\u0646\u064a \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5a14c8e5-9cc0-46be-9e48-cce4219eae2d",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0648\u062c\u0647\u0646\u064a \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a8427d00-57fd-4f17-b8c4-fef424a899d6",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b91993d3-6906-4cc5-a5ed-e66e75f83430",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u062d\u0635\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0630\u0627\u0647\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7d5516f3-23e1-4a74-8e09-40072d731bf3",
      "question": "\u0623\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0644\u0644\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0642\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062d\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "975f6ff6-b258-438f-b1be-147f63554fc9",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0642\u0645\u062a \u0628\u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u0645\u0624\u062e\u0631\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "72e40a9e-e849-4af9-942f-3209186b8696",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0627\u0633\u062a\u0643\u0634\u0627\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0641\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "-",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "718ac646-72f7-4e5a-95f3-9ddba1cb7ac0",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u062d\u064a\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0645\u0635\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "df8883af-b62a-4b2a-a1d7-05a51b9e9a80",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0632\u0648\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5a5bc6b5-5c19-41d5-b7ad-4fd9507a27bd",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0632\u0648\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ce1f4375-5799-47f7-9d90-34c4711271dd",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0641\u062d\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d7259aab-8660-49d4-9441-e997d2796975",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0646\u062a\u0638\u0627\u0631 \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b4dfe60d-af7b-4152-8d73-52117b56469e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u063a\u0631\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fd8c29e2-0bd9-488a-8cfe-23c3b805fece",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d \u062d\u062a\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "340c404a-a2bf-4716-a4f3-191c568e1a87",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062c\u0644\u0628 \u0644\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0624\u0644\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f2cc391b-586d-45f1-8fdc-8cdc4e035b26",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062c\u0644\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0627\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a9cf4c9d-3ba2-4298-9f5b-8e362ee1c1ff",
      "question": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u062f\u0627\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0623\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "084522c2-5a93-4255-9202-ca9f06fa4f6b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u0633\u0623\u0642\u064a\u0645 \u0641\u064a\u0647\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u062a\u0627\u062d\u064a\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e7184987-e624-4187-acae-06242afc6e8b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0646\u0638\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "82c6d95d-e592-4b8e-af3a-45d8bf2af7ad",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0646\u0638\u064a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "090fa9d1-429b-49f9-aa27-1ed496e285f1",
      "question": "\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0627\u062d\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e1b477d6-c9d6-4a9f-9ca1-9f180315b4f2",
      "question": "\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0630\u0647\u0628\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "56b8e07a-05f1-441a-a598-f39ae6232f09",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u0644\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bf31a12f-ca70-457a-91cd-43ca5d6a1967",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0630\u0647\u0627\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f5bf095d-cd69-4d47-a5c6-05444a5ea59c",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0635\u0641\u062d",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9d8a6b80-8332-446a-94f4-8bc6d9c659f9",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u064a\u0642\u0638 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0643\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "90d98972-1a2d-4eb1-8d86-bf7e2214ea2c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0643\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0633\u062a\u064a\u0642\u0638",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062d\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9792a79a-b8d6-4456-91ce-1a4956fa9f54",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0645\u0636\u064a \u0648\u0642\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0631\u0627\u0621\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "16bd3d33-2fa7-4d10-8972-fc8ed0833cf7",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u0635\u0645\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6e7dc005-90ee-466e-859a-e71e5aa02f06",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0627\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e79ddee1-8978-48ae-8d12-9a0e9b67b348",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0629 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0631\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a37b02cc-9880-41ae-b17e-24ec0ef55261",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f - \u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e41ec555-ae2f-4df0-b35d-17faae43631c",
      "question": "\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u0639\u0627\u0635\u0645\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4e69d602-87a6-4e18-92c5-23bf0a2d7d83",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629 \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629 \u0648\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062b\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "82b3ee5d-027d-47df-b454-5291200126e7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u064a \u0639\u0627\u0635\u0645\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4e3b8d03-0e32-4fcf-994c-ed4cf7a8ca9d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629 \u062d\u0636\u0631\u064a\u0629 \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0640",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "107415ee-0f65-4ac1-b8ae-942cf85822ad",
      "question": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "39281537-c239-4c29-a3f3-e99bf3e76ac9",
      "question": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634 \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "637f86c4-a0ef-42d6-87ec-94a7fba82bb9",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0641\u0633\u064a\u0631 \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e848eb2b-a1f4-4377-9803-00c8c670b121",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0633\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "36b9844c-c34f-4bb0-97e2-49bebe847ebf",
      "question": "\u0643\u0645 \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641 \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0645\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "50df5808-8d27-4296-a018-583203bd9390",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "25abd9be-d321-4416-b5e8-d1919343fac6",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621 \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0647\u0645\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8638664d-d49a-4d9c-9f7b-3ed07cbca3be",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u0645\u0647\u0645\u0629 \u0639\u0646\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6ee544ea-5649-4a69-b588-0e6e2881db9e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062e\u062f\u0645\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5b1908b6-6ce9-4ea9-ab49-cba221582c17",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u0642\u0627\u0628\u0644\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u064a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a9fd00d1-4da5-4f3c-9610-699fd5b39797",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0627 \u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f0016405-8aab-455b-9f67-e91aa5f66239",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "41100721-fa12-4b12-9aaf-7bcffc31473c",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u062d\u062c\u0632 \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0633\u0628\u0642\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0627\u0626\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "72652b86-01e6-4732-a805-523ca2ca42f4",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "be5b1631-4fee-4b58-a575-c31ba7ca82c7",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0623\u062e\u0630\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bfd89319-e804-4435-9570-249966b5a9f4",
      "question": "\u0623\u0645\u064a \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0647\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3d22b3df-6384-4b39-999b-deb59121fab9",
      "question": "\u0623\u0645\u064a \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u062d\u062a\u064a\u0627\u0637\u064a\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "74ef5230-aaf3-4be5-8ed4-e23791c5046f",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062f\u0631\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u062f\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8ac85d89-1f33-4cdd-92cd-1bf42041b989",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6548f6b7-9667-47d8-82c4-5725ea5d9f14",
      "question": "\u0645\u0635\u0631 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0647\u0627 \u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e \u0637\u0648\u064a\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0639\u0631\u064a\u0642",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2a8896dd-ad63-48ef-90ff-48272d7f938b",
      "question": "\u0645\u0635\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e \u0637\u0648\u064a\u0644 \u0648\u0639\u0631\u064a\u0642",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0647\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "79db1923-d402-4ab1-a847-dc2d0b923892",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0631\u0623\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u0628\u064a\u0628\u064a\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "03b22b38-62ff-4330-b782-a124a249d11c",
      "question": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0636\u0627\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u0642",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9c9e65f0-01d9-435f-bead-f5dcfea11185",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0642\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u062a\u063a\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e98bd6bc-7726-4b75-a0c4-d2ffac833ca0",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0645\u0648\u0627\u0639\u064a\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cdd0a814-42c3-4f55-bbda-3c7d8cfcb2ce",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u0645\u0632\u062f\u062d\u0645 \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627\u060c",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8049f3e1-0654-41aa-8618-3c71f50b2764",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u0642\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0635\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6dc42d86-f64f-4c97-bfb7-be223d81ed29",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u0645\u062a\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "44eb872d-10cb-4e24-87b5-58d7c4e1f5bf",
      "question": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0636\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "55c16428-8a54-456d-b149-c5ff66c84d00",
      "question": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0646\u062f\u0648\u0642",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cb8a8870-6349-4687-afb9-938ee4e39a9c",
      "question": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0627\u0644\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u064a\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629 \u0643\u0644 \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d24203fb-460f-4f29-b91a-82b32830825d",
      "question": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062d\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062f\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "50826b84-2b39-4260-97b6-bc71facbc2ed",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u063a\u062f\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u062a\u062c\u0644\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5aa536ec-9716-4ed7-a79b-8dc1e258ec0c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0648\u0627\u0643\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "02fca9bd-8588-4d7f-be6e-529bf33c3f60",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "53b5c595-958e-49a3-a545-bcac624519f4",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u0645\u0639\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b4ac19ac-c56b-49a5-9af5-17c9c55caa8f",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646 \u0643\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f\u064b\u0627\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6ea8b4ec-0148-4722-bdec-889273783c5f",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u064a \u0623\u0633\u0626\u0644\u0629\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062a\u0631\u062f\u062f \u0641\u064a \u0637\u0631\u062d\u0647\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0644\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "cf47eaa0-5d88-476f-b73a-d4799b85646e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u064a \u0623\u0633\u0626\u0644\u0629\u060c \u0641\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u062a\u0631\u062f\u062f \u0641\u064a \u0637\u0631\u062d\u0647\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0645\u0627\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b42fb14a-a313-47a3-9930-af60621ea97e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a \u062a\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0639\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0647\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ad77bbd1-a7a1-469b-bd92-589e96715d24",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062e\u061f\u061f\u061f\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0639\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f82033b5-bbdd-440c-8ce5-35c7d5cf5302",
      "question": "\u0628\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0644\u064a \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u0641\u0644\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3a7b6f02-8738-47a2-b3f7-cbb6a9ce49a4",
      "question": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0637\u0648\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "33611c29-aa22-4521-975a-16f19232714c",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062e\u0628\u0631\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f\u0645\u0627 \u062a\u062e\u0631\u062c\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u0633\u062a\u0643\u0634\u0627\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8731b15b-4493-434f-b4ea-0ab23ec4d0c4",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u062c",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8e446d1b-47ad-4e08-8e3b-020c054f28cc",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0623\u062a\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "5728d7aa-b2a2-4916-91d7-2eb6b096d3fa",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0647",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "49aab547-d058-43fe-9983-b41760618989",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u0641\u0644\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "ae5d46fd-d3e6-4662-909f-5b79c9fa4b57",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4b865b9b-10a6-46ea-a67c-30fa8561c88c",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e57c7d77-b3a5-474b-90df-ddbf3bb88412",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645)",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b90e6263-112a-4773-b388-84d4f6efd215",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u0639\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c051a3a2-aaf2-4e41-ba66-4679513862e8",
      "question": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3aa37caf-9bef-490d-a309-3efdbc9b102c",
      "question": "\u0625\u0646\u0647 \u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0633\u0628\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "e3824cf0-8663-4ed4-9afd-832b5aa0ccea",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062b\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u0639\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6fa5b755-15ad-4a43-81dd-685ddf8d0cc1",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u0639\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062b\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u0648\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6ecc5d81-e47d-4840-a380-05d7711b66d5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b2b14ffc-f07a-416c-803f-592c41bf6aab",
      "question": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "baaec0e1-d29e-4ba8-90f2-5094afeef096",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648 \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0632\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4d4a766a-6522-45be-a906-7e78e2c685cc",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0632\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "be09a062-f979-4d57-a5a3-76ed7e525c50",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b69fc219-1b46-410a-a468-033189de2256",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0637\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f\u064a\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c0d59b9f-291b-4123-bb2d-d5ee986fcf86",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f\u064a\u0646 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0637\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0643\u0648\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "50540245-2db4-4543-b005-008947b175f4",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0633\u0628\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0639\u064a\u0646\u0629\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "2d9968c2-fb35-4853-b719-2e149ff7c87b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0633\u0628\u0629 \u0644\u064a",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fe3c4c25-7e04-4508-87b1-8132d6c22f2a",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0623\u062c\u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7761c147-dac8-4be6-b0ba-5e4adb8626de",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0647\u0645",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4d99fe1c-0c60-4f92-9908-54de9ba0fbd8",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062d\u0628",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "21553d75-7fc3-4140-ae33-3667d2424bc2",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u062a\u0627\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7cd1e590-c92c-4259-93e8-33fafc677e1b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0632\u0647\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u064a\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "0ba8bedf-42b8-400c-b683-d57f0f9d076c",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1599a9dd-dab9-42aa-86af-9abab4f1eed8",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0647\u0627 \u0644\u064a\u0633\u062a \u0645\u0634\u0643\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bab9d347-9e13-4d85-aec4-d96e03afb206",
      "question": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "33ff89f8-9e49-401c-9f86-6e27394a6f24",
      "question": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "59d598ea-143a-40f8-960b-712f2ab13e45",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "406ca315-43c0-401d-97f9-17dd246c9e4d",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "d31841d6-961e-4aee-a508-eabeb66b09f0",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u061f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "01697efc-8d65-4245-8261-543da7a3d74e",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "12eba276-657b-47c5-94c6-b1ef5fc59d4e",
      "question": "\u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a681eedc-b4c4-4a09-95f2-0f7ee3f74d06",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0639\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "020d5c5d-d5be-4550-ab6c-5a7363c25cbe",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0631\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "6b63585d-ff44-4574-b315-6f845a9065e3",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0640 \u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0647\u064a\u0631",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "9fc53424-5fbc-41af-9e9f-a0260fe553e5",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645)",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "f49bc753-df28-4a57-97ad-54c7a0e72f81",
      "question": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645) \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0643",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "72eda04f-4c51-4f2b-a991-e8c047d35fc3",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u062f\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b4afb04f-a60d-4a44-b477-37a9a190d705",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0645\u0631 \u0644\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u062f\u0627\u0621",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0645\u0627\u0621",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "39448f83-6632-42ea-8b5f-3b5e3222524e",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0634\u0627\u064a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "3e183c8a-3c34-4040-94b1-97c03325f6ee",
      "question": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0642\u0648\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bf5d0a21-17f7-434b-8490-126ae26e5e4b",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u062a\u0642\u062f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0637\u0644\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fa250786-8506-4d75-9a0d-6a9193d66b4b",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0645\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0644\u0644\u0627\u0647\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u060c",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "08aa4780-675d-4043-a4a6-820941acadd8",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u0627\u062a\u0641 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "7e7cbdbe-e19b-4903-8459-fd539b4b027e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0645\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "01d0ef7e-3ca6-49ab-b582-d40778118016",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0628",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "4f1cda3b-ec76-46a7-b968-fc628582688d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "38f18e69-657e-467e-949c-a67bf4582604",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0631",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "579a142e-93b5-48d0-8022-8bc3975578c7",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633 \u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0644",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "bbf62729-e169-422b-9558-5a13d63cda3f",
      "question": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643\u061f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "c636b212-b859-4d32-b032-afe97187c395",
      "question": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062d\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u064a\u0648\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "b1039f08-6b8e-4340-a127-cb5252d063a8",
      "question": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "8742200c-151b-4859-994e-015ea3a2dd9e",
      "question": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0646",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "a2ea8f3f-28b7-44f5-a2a3-2116d122a1c4",
      "question": "\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0644\u0628\u0648\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "64fcb746-9667-4c53-b0fc-dbf09d14535d",
      "question": "\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "1887957a-d1e7-47a4-a00b-bf0f30d01711",
      "question": "\u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0642\u0637",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "00c268f8-360c-4c80-a04d-54fc8ea33a5c",
      "question": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0631\u0629",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0631\u0642\u0627\u0645",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "question": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641 \u0642\u0628\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628",
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "type": "cloze"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am here.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "back": "I am here.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "There is a good restaurant here.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643 \u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645 \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643 \u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645 \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "back": "There is a good restaurant here.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you come here tomorrow?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u0648\u0645 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u0648\u0645 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Can you come here tomorrow?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Good work requires time and effort.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062f \u064a\u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a \u0648\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0647\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062f \u064a\u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a \u0648\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0647\u062f",
      "back": "Good work requires time and effort.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is a very good book.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u062c\u064a\u062f \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u062c\u064a\u062f \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "back": "This is a very good book.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You should have good friends.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0646",
      "back": "You should have good friends.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I will pay the bill.",
      "back": "\u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "back": "I will pay the bill.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can I pay with a credit card?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "back": "Can I pay with a credit card?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I will pay in cash.",
      "back": "\u0633\u0623\u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u0623\u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "I will pay in cash.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What's your news? (How are you?)",
      "back": "\u0627\u0634 \u0623\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0634 \u0623\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "What's your news? (How are you?)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What is this?",
      "back": "\u0627\u0634 \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0634 \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "What is this?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What is your name?",
      "back": "\u0627\u0634 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0634 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "What is your name?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I pay in cash.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "back": "I pay in cash.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you accept cash payments?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634\u061f",
      "back": "Do you accept cash payments?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I need to have cash on hand.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0646\u0642\u0648\u062f \u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0646\u0642\u0648\u062f \u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "back": "I need to have cash on hand.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I love to travel.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0641\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0641\u0631",
      "back": "I love to travel.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am a student at the university.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0637\u0627\u0644\u0628 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0637\u0627\u0644\u0628 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "back": "I am a student at the university.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am here to help you.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u0643",
      "back": "I am here to help you.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I want a cup of coffee.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "back": "I want a cup of coffee.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you want to clean the room?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u062a\u0646\u0636\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u062a\u0646\u0636\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you want to clean the room?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you want to help me with this project?",
      "back": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639\u061f",
      "back": "Do you want to help me with this project?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I love to sing at parties.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0641\u0644\u0627\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0641\u0644\u0627\u062a",
      "back": "I love to sing at parties.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you sing us a song?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u063a\u0646\u064a \u0644\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u063a\u0646\u064a \u0644\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Can you sing us a song?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Ahmed is considered one of the best pop singers.",
      "back": "\u064a\u064f\u0639\u062a\u0628\u0631 \u0623\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0645\u063a\u0646\u064a\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0648\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u064f\u0639\u062a\u0628\u0631 \u0623\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0645\u063a\u0646\u064a\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0648\u0628",
      "back": "Ahmed is considered one of the best pop singers.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This song is very beautiful.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "back": "This song is very beautiful.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "They have a wonderful collection of songs.",
      "back": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0647\u0645 \u0645\u062c\u0645\u0648\u0639\u0629 \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0627\u0646\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0647\u0645 \u0645\u062c\u0645\u0648\u0639\u0629 \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0627\u0646\u064a",
      "back": "They have a wonderful collection of songs.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I like to listen to old songs.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0627\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u064a\u0645\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0627\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u064a\u0645\u0629",
      "back": "I like to listen to old songs.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you help me?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "back": "Can you help me?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I don't think I can attend.",
      "back": "\u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u062a\u0642\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0647 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0636\u0648\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u062a\u0642\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0647 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0636\u0648\u0631",
      "back": "I don't think I can attend.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You should believe in yourself and know what you can do.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062b\u0642 \u0628\u0646\u0641\u0633\u0643 \u0648\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0645\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0641\u0639\u0644\u0647",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062b\u0642 \u0628\u0646\u0641\u0633\u0643 \u0648\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0645\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0641\u0639\u0644\u0647",
      "back": "You should believe in yourself and know what you can do.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You are able to do it.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u062a \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u0628\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u062a \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u0628\u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "back": "You are able to do it.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you do that for me?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "back": "Can you do that for me?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You should be able to speak English.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0642\u0627\u062f\u0631\u064b\u0627 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0642\u0627\u062f\u0631\u064b\u0627 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "You should be able to speak English.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I have a lot of work today.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u063a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u063a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "back": "I have a lot of work today.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you like your job?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0634\u063a\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0634\u063a\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "Do you like your job?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You should put effort into your work.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0636\u0639 \u062c\u0647\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0634\u063a\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0636\u0639 \u062c\u0647\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0634\u063a\u0644",
      "back": "You should put effort into your work.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How can this device be operated?",
      "back": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0647\u0627\u0632\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0647\u0627\u0632\u061f",
      "back": "How can this device be operated?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You should learn how to operate the car.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "back": "You should learn how to operate the car.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you play the video?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0648\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0648\u061f",
      "back": "Can you play the video?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The air conditioner is not working.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "back": "The air conditioner is not working.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "In the summer, we should use the air conditioner.",
      "back": "\u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641\u060c \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641\u060c \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "back": "In the summer, we should use the air conditioner.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The air conditioner makes the room cool.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u062c\u0639\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u062c\u0639\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u0629",
      "back": "The air conditioner makes the room cool.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The air conditioner is not as cool as it should be.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0644\u064a\u0633 \u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0643\u0645\u0627 \u064a\u0646\u0628\u063a\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0644\u064a\u0633 \u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0643\u0645\u0627 \u064a\u0646\u0628\u063a\u064a",
      "back": "The air conditioner is not as cool as it should be.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Turn on the air conditioner.",
      "back": "\u0642\u0645 \u0628\u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0642\u0645 \u0628\u062a\u0634\u063a\u064a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "back": "Turn on the air conditioner.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The air conditioner is necessary in the summer.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0636\u0631\u0648\u0631\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0636\u0631\u0648\u0631\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "back": "The air conditioner is necessary in the summer.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I can help you.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0643",
      "back": "I can help you.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I can do that.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "back": "I can do that.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I can go tomorrow.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "I can go tomorrow.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The bill must be paid now.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "back": "The bill must be paid now.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can I pay with a credit card?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "back": "Can I pay with a credit card?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I will pay in cash.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0633\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0633\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "I will pay in cash.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I always pay in cash.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "back": "I always pay in cash.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I will pay you later.",
      "back": "\u0633\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0644\u0643 \u0641\u064a \u0648\u0642\u062a \u0644\u0627\u062d\u0642",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0644\u0643 \u0641\u064a \u0648\u0642\u062a \u0644\u0627\u062d\u0642",
      "back": "I will pay you later.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Would you like me to pay now?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "back": "Would you like me to pay now?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you accept Visa cards?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Do you accept Visa cards?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You can pay with Visa.",
      "back": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0648\u0627\u0633\u0637\u0629 \u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0648\u0627\u0633\u0637\u0629 \u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "back": "You can pay with Visa.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I will use my Visa card for the reservation.",
      "back": "\u0633\u0623\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0645 \u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u0644\u0644\u062d\u062c\u0632",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u0623\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0645 \u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u0644\u0644\u062d\u062c\u0632",
      "back": "I will use my Visa card for the reservation.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You can pay with Visa.",
      "back": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "back": "You can pay with Visa.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you want to pay with Visa or cash?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u0623\u0645 \u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u0623\u0645 \u0646\u0642\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Do you want to pay with Visa or cash?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "They don't accept Visa payments here.",
      "back": "\u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0642\u0628\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "back": "They don't accept Visa payments here.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Things are not so easy.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631 \u0644\u064a\u0633\u062a \u0641\u0627 \u0633\u0647\u0644\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631 \u0644\u064a\u0633\u062a \u0641\u0627 \u0633\u0647\u0644\u0629",
      "back": "Things are not so easy.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am so happy to see you.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u0627 \u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f \u0628\u0631\u0624\u064a\u062a\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u0627 \u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f \u0628\u0631\u0624\u064a\u062a\u0643",
      "back": "I am so happy to see you.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "So, what are we going to do today?",
      "back": "\u0641\u0627\u060c \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u0633\u0646\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0641\u0627\u060c \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u0633\u0646\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "back": "So, what are we going to do today?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you understand what I'm saying?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645 \u0645\u0627 \u0623\u0642\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645 \u0645\u0627 \u0623\u0642\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "back": "Do you understand what I'm saying?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I'm sure they understand the situation.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0647\u0645 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0636\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0647\u0645 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0636\u0639",
      "back": "I'm sure they understand the situation.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I don't understand math well.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0641\u0647\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u064a\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0627\u062a \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0641\u0647\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u064a\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0627\u062a \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "I don't understand math well.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Arabs are a large nation.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628 \u0634\u0639\u0628 \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628 \u0634\u0639\u0628 \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631",
      "back": "Arabs are a large nation.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Arabic is their language.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u0644\u063a\u062a\u0647\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u0644\u063a\u062a\u0647\u0645",
      "back": "Arabic is their language.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We should respect Arab culture.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u062d\u062a\u0631\u0645 \u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u062d\u062a\u0631\u0645 \u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628",
      "back": "We should respect Arab culture.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is my car.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a",
      "back": "This is my car.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I have my own car.",
      "back": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0627\u0635\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0627\u0635\u0629",
      "back": "I have my own car.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "My car needs maintenance.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0635\u064a\u0627\u0646\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0635\u064a\u0627\u0646\u0629",
      "back": "My car needs maintenance.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This movie is very bad.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u0633\u064a\u0626 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u0633\u064a\u0626 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "This movie is very bad.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Don't do anything bad.",
      "back": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u0633\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u0633\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "Don't do anything bad.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I heard he has a bad reputation.",
      "back": "\u0633\u0645\u0639\u062a \u0639\u0646\u0647 \u0633\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u0645\u0639\u062a \u0639\u0646\u0647 \u0633\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "back": "I heard he has a bad reputation.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "These books are bad.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "back": "These books are bad.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am not bad.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0633\u062a \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0633\u062a \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "back": "I am not bad.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Don't behave in a bad way.",
      "back": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u062a\u0635\u0631\u0641\u064a \u0628\u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642\u0629 \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u062a\u0635\u0631\u0641\u064a \u0628\u0637\u0631\u064a\u0642\u0629 \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "back": "Don't behave in a bad way.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This food is very delicious.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "back": "This food is very delicious.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "It's very hot today.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648 \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648 \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "back": "It's very hot today.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This movie is very enjoyable.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "back": "This movie is very enjoyable.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This book is very useful.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0645\u0641\u064a\u062f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0645\u0641\u064a\u062f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "back": "This book is very useful.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Hard work is very tiring.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0642 \u0645\u062c\u0647\u062f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0642 \u0645\u062c\u0647\u062f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b",
      "back": "Hard work is very tiring.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The weather is very cold in winter.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648 \u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0634\u062a\u0627\u0621",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648 \u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627\u064b \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0634\u062a\u0627\u0621",
      "back": "The weather is very cold in winter.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Excuse me, can you help me?",
      "back": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "back": "Excuse me, can you help me?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Excuse me, I am a new student here.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0637\u0627\u0644\u0628 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0637\u0627\u0644\u0628 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "back": "Excuse me, I am a new student here.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Excuse me, can you repeat that?",
      "back": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631 \u0630\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631 \u0630\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "Excuse me, can you repeat that?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Excuse me for the inconvenience.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0632\u0639\u0627\u062c",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0632\u0639\u0627\u062c",
      "back": "Excuse me for the inconvenience.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Excuse me, can you give me the menu?",
      "back": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0625\u0639\u0637\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0625\u0639\u0637\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Excuse me, can you give me the menu?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Excuse me, can you explain how to get there?",
      "back": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0634\u0631\u062d \u0644\u064a \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0634\u0631\u062d \u0644\u064a \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "Excuse me, can you explain how to get there?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We should learn from experience.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0646 \u062e\u0644\u0627\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0628\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0646 \u062e\u0644\u0627\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0628\u0631\u0629",
      "back": "We should learn from experience.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you like learning languages?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0627\u062a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0627\u062a\u061f",
      "back": "Do you like learning languages?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I learned a lot from this book.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "back": "I learned a lot from this book.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am learning to play the guitar.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0632\u0641 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062a\u0627\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0632\u0641 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062a\u0627\u0631",
      "back": "I am learning to play the guitar.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Are you interested in programming and learning programming languages?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0647\u062a\u0645 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0645\u062c\u0629 \u0648\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0644\u063a\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0645\u062c\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0647\u062a\u0645 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0645\u062c\u0629 \u0648\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0644\u063a\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0645\u062c\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Are you interested in programming and learning programming languages?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I have been learning English for a long time.",
      "back": "\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u0645\u0646\u0630 \u0641\u062a\u0631\u0629 \u0637\u0648\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u0645\u0646\u0630 \u0641\u062a\u0631\u0629 \u0637\u0648\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "back": "I have been learning English for a long time.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The Arabic language is beautiful.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "back": "The Arabic language is beautiful.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I speak the Arabic language.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "I speak the Arabic language.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Arabic language needs practice.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0645\u0627\u0631\u0633\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0645\u0627\u0631\u0633\u0629",
      "back": "Arabic language needs practice.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Please repeat the sentence.",
      "back": "\u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c \u0643\u0631\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0644\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c \u0643\u0631\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0644\u0629",
      "back": "Please repeat the sentence.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I didn't hear well, can you repeat?",
      "back": "\u0644\u0645 \u0623\u0633\u0645\u0639 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u0645 \u0623\u0633\u0645\u0639 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u061f",
      "back": "I didn't hear well, can you repeat?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Repeat the process again.",
      "back": "\u0643\u0631\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0631 \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u0631\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0631 \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649",
      "back": "Repeat the process again.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Repeat it, please.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "back": "Repeat it, please.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you repeat it for me?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627 \u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627 \u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "back": "Can you repeat it for me?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You should make sure to repeat it carefully.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0639\u0646\u0627\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0639\u0646\u0627\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "You should make sure to repeat it carefully.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You should learn how to speak English.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "You should learn how to speak English.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you speak another language?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "back": "Can you speak another language?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Speak slowly, please.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "back": "Speak slowly, please.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You speak English fluently.",
      "back": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u0628\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u0628\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "back": "You speak English fluently.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you speak Arabic?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you speak Arabic?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you speak Spanish as well?",
      "back": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0633\u0628\u0627\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u0623\u064a\u0636\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0633\u0628\u0627\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u0623\u064a\u0636\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Do you speak Spanish as well?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The car is moving slowly.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u062a\u0633\u064a\u0631 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u062a\u0633\u064a\u0631 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "back": "The car is moving slowly.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You should move slowly around the corner.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u062d\u0631\u0643 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u062d\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0639\u0637\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u062d\u0631\u0643 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u062d\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0639\u0637\u0641",
      "back": "You should move slowly around the corner.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Browsing the internet is slow.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0635\u0641\u062d \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0631\u0646\u062a \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0635\u0641\u062d \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0631\u0646\u062a \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "back": "Browsing the internet is slow.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Read the text slowly.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0642\u0631\u0623 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0635 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0642\u0631\u0623 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0635 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "back": "Read the text slowly.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You should eat slowly to enjoy the meal.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u0644\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u0644\u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "back": "You should eat slowly to enjoy the meal.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The car moved slowly toward the destination.",
      "back": "\u0633\u0627\u0631\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u0646\u062d\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u0627\u0631\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u0646\u062d\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u0641",
      "back": "The car moved slowly toward the destination.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Stay here for a few minutes.",
      "back": "\u0636\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0628\u0636\u0639 \u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0642",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0636\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0628\u0636\u0639 \u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0642",
      "back": "Stay here for a few minutes.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I want to stay there for a longer period.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0636\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643 \u0644\u0641\u062a\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u0637\u0648\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0636\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643 \u0644\u0641\u062a\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u0637\u0648\u0644",
      "back": "I want to stay there for a longer period.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You should stay calm.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0636\u0644 \u0647\u0627\u062f\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0636\u0644 \u0647\u0627\u062f\u0626\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "You should stay calm.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you help me, please?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "Can you help me, please?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Give me some water, please.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0639\u0637\u0646\u064a \u0645\u0627\u0621\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0639\u0637\u0646\u064a \u0645\u0627\u0621\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "back": "Give me some water, please.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Please have a seat.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633",
      "back": "Please have a seat.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Say what you're thinking.",
      "back": "\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0644\u064a \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u062a\u0641\u0643\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0644\u064a \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u062a\u0641\u0643\u0631",
      "back": "Say what you're thinking.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you tell me the truth?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Can you tell me the truth?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Don't say everything you think.",
      "back": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0643\u0644 \u0645\u0627 \u062a\u0641\u0643\u0631 \u0628\u0647",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0643\u0644 \u0645\u0627 \u062a\u0641\u0643\u0631 \u0628\u0647",
      "back": "Don't say everything you think.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you say it again?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "back": "Can you say it again?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You say it well.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0634\u0643\u0644 \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0634\u0643\u0644 \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "back": "You say it well.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You should make sure you say it clearly.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0648\u0636\u0648\u062d",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0648\u0636\u0648\u062d",
      "back": "You should make sure you say it clearly.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you speak English?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you speak English?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "English is a global language.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "English is a global language.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am learning English.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "I am learning English.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you speak in English?",
      "back": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Can you speak in English?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you explain that in English?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0634\u0631\u062d \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0634\u0631\u062d \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Can you explain that in English?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Please write in English.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0631\u062c\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0631\u062c\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "Please write in English.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is a new English book.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "back": "This is a new English book.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am learning the English language.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "I am learning the English language.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I have an English friend.",
      "back": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642 \u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642 \u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a",
      "back": "I have an English friend.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What is this?",
      "back": "\u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "What is this?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What's new?",
      "back": "\u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u061f",
      "back": "What's new?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What's your news? (How are you?)",
      "back": "\u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0623\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0623\u062e\u0628\u0627\u0631\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "What's your news? (How are you?)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you explain it to me in Arabic?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0634\u0631\u062d\u0647 \u0644\u064a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0634\u0631\u062d\u0647 \u0644\u064a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Can you explain it to me in Arabic?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The book is available in Arabic and English.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0645\u062a\u0627\u062d \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u0648\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0645\u062a\u0627\u062d \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u0648\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "The book is available in Arabic and English.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you write in Arabic?",
      "back": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Can you write in Arabic?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Someone is looking for you.",
      "back": "\u062d\u062f \u064a\u0628\u062d\u062b \u0639\u0646\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062d\u062f \u064a\u0628\u062d\u062b \u0639\u0646\u0643",
      "back": "Someone is looking for you.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I don't know anyone here.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u062d\u062f \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u062d\u062f \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "back": "I don't know anyone here.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Someone can help us.",
      "back": "\u062d\u062f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0623\u0646 \u064a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062d\u062f \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0623\u0646 \u064a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0646\u0627",
      "back": "Someone can help us.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I have only one.",
      "back": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f \u0641\u0642\u0637",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f \u0641\u0642\u0637",
      "back": "I have only one.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you have one?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f\u061f",
      "back": "Do you have one?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "One of my friends went to Egypt.",
      "back": "\u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "back": "One of my friends went to Egypt.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is the same book.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628",
      "back": "This is the same book.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We are in the same class.",
      "back": "\u0646\u062d\u0646 \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0635\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u062d\u0646 \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0635\u0644",
      "back": "We are in the same class.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you have the same hobbies?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u0648\u0627\u064a\u0627\u062a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u0648\u0627\u064a\u0627\u062a\u061f",
      "back": "Do you have the same hobbies?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Did you forget something?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0646\u0633\u064a\u062a \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0646\u0633\u064a\u062a \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Did you forget something?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I can't see anything.",
      "back": "\u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0631\u0649 \u0623\u064a \u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0631\u0649 \u0623\u064a \u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "back": "I can't see anything.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is something new.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "back": "This is something new.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The only thing I can do.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0641\u0639\u0644\u0647",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0641\u0639\u0644\u0647",
      "back": "The only thing I can do.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Where is the thing you asked for?",
      "back": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u0637\u0644\u0628\u062a\u0647\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u0637\u0644\u0628\u062a\u0647\u061f",
      "back": "Where is the thing you asked for?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you know what the thing that needs to be done is?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u0628\u0647\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u0628\u0647\u061f",
      "back": "Do you know what the thing that needs to be done is?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "O God, what is this?",
      "back": "\u064a\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0647\u060c \u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0647\u060c \u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "O God, what is this?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "O my friends, let's go.",
      "back": "\u064a\u0627 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a\u060c \u0647\u064a\u0627 \u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0627 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a\u060c \u0647\u064a\u0627 \u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628",
      "back": "O my friends, let's go.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "O, what a wonderful moment!",
      "back": "\u064a\u0627 \u0644\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629!",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0627 \u0644\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629!",
      "back": "O, what a wonderful moment!",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This means a lot to me.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "back": "This means a lot to me.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I'm going to write a letter to me.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0630\u0627\u0647\u0628 \u0644\u0623\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0631\u0633\u0627\u0644\u0629 \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0630\u0627\u0647\u0628 \u0644\u0623\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0631\u0633\u0627\u0644\u0629 \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "back": "I'm going to write a letter to me.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I will do it for me, to me.",
      "back": "\u0633\u0623\u0642\u0648\u0645 \u0628\u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u062c\u0644\u064a\u060c \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u0623\u0642\u0648\u0645 \u0628\u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u062c\u0644\u064a\u060c \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "back": "I will do it for me, to me.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I'm vegetarian, I don't eat meat.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u060c \u0644\u0627 \u0622\u0643\u0644 \u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u060c \u0644\u0627 \u0622\u0643\u0644 \u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "back": "I'm vegetarian, I don't eat meat.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you have vegetarian options on the menu?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062e\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a \u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062e\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a \u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you have vegetarian options on the menu?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "My friend and I are vegetarians.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0648\u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642\u064a \u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0648\u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642\u064a \u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646",
      "back": "My friend and I are vegetarians.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you know any vegetarians?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0623\u064a \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0623\u064a \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "back": "Do you know any vegetarians?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Vegetarians avoid consuming animal products.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646 \u064a\u062a\u062c\u0646\u0628\u0648\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0648\u0627\u0646\u0627\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u064a\u0646 \u064a\u062a\u062c\u0646\u0628\u0648\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0648\u0627\u0646\u0627\u062a",
      "back": "Vegetarians avoid consuming animal products.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I have a vegetarian friend.",
      "back": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642 \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642 \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a",
      "back": "I have a vegetarian friend.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am at home.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a",
      "back": "I am at home.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Let's meet at the restaurant.",
      "back": "\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "back": "Let's meet at the restaurant.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Where are you at right now?",
      "back": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "back": "Where are you at right now?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you have a car?",
      "back": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643 \u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643 \u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you have a car?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you have siblings?",
      "back": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643 \u0623\u062e\u0648\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643 \u0623\u062e\u0648\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you have siblings?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You have many friends.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621 \u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u0648\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621 \u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u0648\u0646",
      "back": "You have many friends.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I want to order from the list.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "back": "I want to order from the list.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you give me the list?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0625\u0639\u0637\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0625\u0639\u0637\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Can you give me the list?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The list contains many options.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a",
      "back": "The list contains many options.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is the list.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "back": "This is the list.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The list contains my favorite foods.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0639\u0645\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0629 \u0644\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0639\u0645\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0629 \u0644\u064a",
      "back": "The list contains my favorite foods.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You should read the list carefully.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "You should read the list carefully.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The food is very hot.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "back": "The food is very hot.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The weather is hot in the summer.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0642\u0633 \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0642\u0633 \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "back": "The weather is hot in the summer.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The tea is hot and delicious.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u0648\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u0648\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "back": "The tea is hot and delicious.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The soup is hot.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0648\u0631\u0628\u0629 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0648\u0631\u0628\u0629 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "back": "The soup is hot.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This bag is hot.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0628\u0629 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0628\u0629 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "back": "This bag is hot.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Don't touch the piece, it's hot.",
      "back": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0644\u0645\u0633\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0639\u0629\u060c \u0625\u0646\u0647\u0627 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0644\u0645\u0633\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0639\u0629\u060c \u0625\u0646\u0647\u0627 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "back": "Don't touch the piece, it's hot.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You need to change the old tire.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u063a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u064a\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u063a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u062f\u064a\u0645",
      "back": "You need to change the old tire.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you have a spare tire?",
      "back": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631 \u0627\u062d\u062a\u064a\u0627\u0637\u064a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631 \u0627\u062d\u062a\u064a\u0627\u0637\u064a\u061f",
      "back": "Do you have a spare tire?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "New tires make the car drive smoothly.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u062a\u062c\u0639\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u062a\u0633\u064a\u0631 \u0628\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0633\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0627\u0631\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u062a\u062c\u0639\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u062a\u0633\u064a\u0631 \u0628\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0633\u0629",
      "back": "New tires make the car drive smoothly.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I love this place a lot.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631",
      "back": "I love this place a lot.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you know they love you a lot?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0623\u0646\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u062d\u0628\u0648\u0646\u0643 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0623\u0646\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u062d\u0628\u0648\u0646\u0643 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631\u061f",
      "back": "Do you know they love you a lot?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I was very busy today.",
      "back": "\u0643\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0634\u063a\u0648\u0644\u064b\u0627 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0634\u063a\u0648\u0644\u064b\u0627 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "back": "I was very busy today.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I have two of them.",
      "back": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0645\u0646\u0647\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0645\u0646\u0647\u0645",
      "back": "I have two of them.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can I get two?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "back": "Can I get two?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Two of my friends went to the beach.",
      "back": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0630\u0647\u0628\u0648\u0627 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u062d\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0626\u064a \u0630\u0647\u0628\u0648\u0627 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u062d\u0631",
      "back": "Two of my friends went to the beach.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I love to drink coffee in the morning.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "back": "I love to drink coffee in the morning.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you prefer hot coffee or cold coffee?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u062e\u0646\u0629 \u0623\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u062e\u0646\u0629 \u0623\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0631\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you prefer hot coffee or cold coffee?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This place is famous for its delicious coffee.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0645\u0634\u0647\u0648\u0631 \u0628\u0642\u0647\u0648\u062a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0645\u0634\u0647\u0648\u0631 \u0628\u0642\u0647\u0648\u062a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629",
      "back": "This place is famous for its delicious coffee.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Coffee is very delicious.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "Coffee is very delicious.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you drink coffee with milk?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0644\u064a\u0628\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0644\u064a\u0628\u061f",
      "back": "Do you drink coffee with milk?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I need a cup of coffee.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "back": "I need a cup of coffee.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You should leave this place.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0631\u0643 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0631\u0643 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646",
      "back": "You should leave this place.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you leave a comment?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0631\u0643 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0642\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0631\u0643 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0642\u061f",
      "back": "Can you leave a comment?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I will leave work early today.",
      "back": "\u0633\u0623\u062a\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0645\u0628\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u0623\u062a\u0631\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0645\u0628\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "back": "I will leave work early today.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Turkish food is delicious.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "back": "Turkish food is delicious.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I love Turkish tea.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a",
      "back": "I love Turkish tea.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you know how to make Turkish coffee?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u0636\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u0636\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you know how to make Turkish coffee?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This food is light on the stomach.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u062f\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u062f\u0629",
      "back": "This food is light on the stomach.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The dress is light and suitable for summer.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0648\u0628 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641 \u0648\u0645\u0646\u0627\u0633\u0628 \u0644\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0648\u0628 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641 \u0648\u0645\u0646\u0627\u0633\u0628 \u0644\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "back": "The dress is light and suitable for summer.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The sun is shining with a light.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0645\u0633 \u062a\u0634\u0639 \u0628\u0636\u0648\u0621 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0645\u0633 \u062a\u0634\u0639 \u0628\u0636\u0648\u0621 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641",
      "back": "The sun is shining with a light.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This bag is light.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0628\u0629 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0642\u064a\u0628\u0629 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "back": "This bag is light.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Dinner was a light meal.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0634\u0627\u0621 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0648\u062c\u0628\u0629 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0634\u0627\u0621 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0648\u062c\u0628\u0629 \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "back": "Dinner was a light meal.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The rain was light this morning.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631 \u0643\u0627\u0646\u062a \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631 \u0643\u0627\u0646\u062a \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "back": "The rain was light this morning.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What's on the program?",
      "back": "\u0634\u0648 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0646\u0627\u0645\u062c\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0634\u0648 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0631\u0646\u0627\u0645\u062c\u061f",
      "back": "What's on the program?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What's the best book you've read?",
      "back": "\u0634\u0648 \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0642\u0631\u0623\u062a\u0647\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0634\u0648 \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0642\u0631\u0623\u062a\u0647\u061f",
      "back": "What's the best book you've read?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What do you want to do today?",
      "back": "\u0634\u0648 \u0628\u062a\u062d\u0628 \u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0634\u0648 \u0628\u062a\u062d\u0628 \u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "back": "What do you want to do today?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I need a little time.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "back": "I need a little time.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you give me a little of your time?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0645\u0646\u062d\u0646\u064a \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u0648\u0642\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0645\u0646\u062d\u0646\u064a \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u0648\u0642\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "Can you give me a little of your time?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I just need a little help.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u0642\u0637 \u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u0642\u0637 \u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0629",
      "back": "I just need a little help.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you add sugar to your coffee?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0636\u064a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0643\u0631 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0636\u064a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0643\u0631 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you add sugar to your coffee?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The cake contains a lot of sugar.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0639\u0643\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0639\u0643\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "back": "The cake contains a lot of sugar.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you have brown sugar or white sugar?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0633\u0643\u0631 \u0628\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0645 \u0633\u0643\u0631 \u0623\u0628\u064a\u0636\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0633\u0643\u0631 \u0628\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0645 \u0633\u0643\u0631 \u0623\u0628\u064a\u0636\u061f",
      "back": "Do you have brown sugar or white sugar?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Where is the credit card?",
      "back": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0626\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "back": "Where is the credit card?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You can pay with a debit card.",
      "back": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0635\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0635\u0645",
      "back": "You can pay with a debit card.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I have an ID card.",
      "back": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0647\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629 \u0647\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "I have an ID card.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can I pay by card?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Can I pay by card?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We accept payment by card.",
      "back": "\u0646\u062d\u0646 \u0646\u0642\u0628\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u062d\u0646 \u0646\u0642\u0628\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "back": "We accept payment by card.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I prefer to pay by card.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "back": "I prefer to pay by card.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Where is the bill?",
      "back": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Where is the bill?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you ask for the bill?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Can you ask for the bill?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The bill includes the food and drinks.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u062a\u0634\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0648\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u062a\u0634\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0648\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0628",
      "back": "The bill includes the food and drinks.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is the bill.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "back": "This is the bill.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Please bring the bill.",
      "back": "\u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c \u0642\u062f\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c \u0642\u062f\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "back": "Please bring the bill.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The bill is a bit expensive.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0642\u0644\u064a\u0644\u0627\u064b",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0642\u0644\u064a\u0644\u0627\u064b",
      "back": "The bill is a bit expensive.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We should eat fruit every day.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0643\u0647\u0629 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0643\u0647\u0629 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "We should eat fruit every day.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you like to eat meat?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645\u061f",
      "back": "Do you like to eat meat?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I love to eat pizza.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a\u0632\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a\u0632\u0627",
      "back": "I love to eat pizza.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you have any type of food?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u064a \u0646\u0648\u0639 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u064a \u0646\u0648\u0639 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "back": "Do you have any type of food?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The food here is very delicious.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "The food here is very delicious.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We should eat healthy food.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0635\u062d\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0635\u062d\u064a",
      "back": "We should eat healthy food.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you pay the check?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635\u061f",
      "back": "Can you pay the check?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The check includes the food and drinks.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u064a\u0634\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0648\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u064a\u0634\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0648\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0631\u0627\u0628",
      "back": "The check includes the food and drinks.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Please bring the check.",
      "back": "\u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c \u0642\u062f\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u060c \u0642\u062f\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u062d\u0635",
      "back": "Please bring the check.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Children should learn safety rules.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0641\u0627\u0644 \u0623\u0646 \u064a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0627 \u0642\u0648\u0627\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0641\u0627\u0644 \u0623\u0646 \u064a\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0627 \u0642\u0648\u0627\u0639\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646",
      "back": "Children should learn safety rules.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Safety is the most important thing.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0647\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0647\u0645",
      "back": "Safety is the most important thing.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you have the necessary safety equipment?",
      "back": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0648\u0633\u0627\u0626\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0627\u0632\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0648\u0633\u0627\u0626\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0627\u0632\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you have the necessary safety equipment?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This thing is important.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c \u0645\u0647\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c \u0645\u0647\u0645",
      "back": "This thing is important.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you have a thing you want to share?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u0648\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0643\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u0648\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0643\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Do you have a thing you want to share?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The only thing needed is patience.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u064a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0631 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u064a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0631 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0631",
      "back": "The only thing needed is patience.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I have only one thing.",
      "back": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f\u0629 \u0641\u0642\u0637",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f\u0629 \u0641\u0642\u0637",
      "back": "I have only one thing.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you have a thing you need?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u064a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u064a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Do you have a thing you need?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The only thing you need is love.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647\u0627 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0647\u0627 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0628",
      "back": "The only thing you need is love.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Mom, I'm hungry.",
      "back": "\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062c\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062c\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "back": "Mom, I'm hungry.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Mom, can you help me?",
      "back": "\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "back": "Mom, can you help me?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Mom, I love you.",
      "back": "\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062d\u0628\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062d\u0628\u0643",
      "back": "Mom, I love you.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How are you? - Fine, thanks.",
      "back": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643\u061f - \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u0634\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643\u061f - \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u060c \u0634\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "How are you? - Fine, thanks.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Are you okay? - Yes, I'm fine.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0628\u062e\u064a\u0631\u061f - \u0646\u0639\u0645\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0628\u062e\u064a\u0631\u061f - \u0646\u0639\u0645\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "back": "Are you okay? - Yes, I'm fine.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How was your day? - It was fine.",
      "back": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u0643\u061f - \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u0643\u061f - \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "How was your day? - It was fine.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I'm just a child.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0637\u0641\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0637\u0641\u0644",
      "back": "I'm just a child.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Is that all? - Yes, just that.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0643\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0621\u061f - \u0646\u0639\u0645\u060c \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0643\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0621\u061f - \u0646\u0639\u0645\u060c \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "back": "Is that all? - Yes, just that.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I'm just a visitor here.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0632\u0627\u0626\u0631 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0632\u0627\u0626\u0631 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "back": "I'm just a visitor here.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you do me a favor?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0644\u064a \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0648\u0641\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0644\u064a \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0648\u0641\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Can you do me a favor?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am grateful for this favor.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0646 \u0644\u0643 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0646 \u0644\u0643 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "back": "I am grateful for this favor.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You didn't do me any favor.",
      "back": "\u0644\u0645 \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0644\u064a \u0623\u064a \u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u0645 \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0644\u064a \u0623\u064a \u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "back": "You didn't do me any favor.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Please come in.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062f\u062e\u0648\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062f\u062e\u0648\u0644",
      "back": "Please come in.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Please have some coffee.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0628\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0628\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "back": "Please have some coffee.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Please take these books.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628",
      "back": "Please take these books.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Where is the bathroom?",
      "back": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "back": "Where is the bathroom?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you direct me to the bathroom?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0648\u062c\u0647\u0646\u064a \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0648\u062c\u0647\u0646\u064a \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "back": "Can you direct me to the bathroom?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I need to use the bathroom.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0633\u062a\u062e\u062f\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "back": "I need to use the bathroom.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you like swimming?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you like swimming?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I'm going to the swimming class.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0630\u0627\u0647\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u062d\u0635\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0630\u0627\u0647\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u062d\u0635\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629",
      "back": "I'm going to the swimming class.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Swimming is fun in the summer.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "back": "Swimming is fun in the summer.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Which book do you prefer to read?",
      "back": "\u0623\u064a \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0642\u0631\u0627\u0621\u062a\u0647\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u064a \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0642\u0631\u0627\u0621\u062a\u0647\u061f",
      "back": "Which book do you prefer to read?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Which color do you like?",
      "back": "\u0623\u064a \u0644\u0648\u0646 \u062a\u062d\u0628\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u064a \u0644\u0648\u0646 \u062a\u062d\u0628\u061f",
      "back": "Which color do you like?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Which day do you prefer to meet?",
      "back": "\u0623\u064a \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0644\u0644\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0642\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u064a \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0644\u0644\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0642\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "back": "Which day do you prefer to meet?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What happened?",
      "back": "\u0623\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u064a \u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "back": "What happened?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What's new?",
      "back": "\u0623\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u061f",
      "back": "What's new?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What is this?",
      "back": "\u0623\u064a\u0647 \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u064a\u0647 \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "What is this?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Have you visited any new places recently?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0642\u0645\u062a \u0628\u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u064a \u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u0645\u0624\u062e\u0631\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0642\u0645\u062a \u0628\u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u064a \u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u0645\u0624\u062e\u0631\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Have you visited any new places recently?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you have a list of places you want to visit?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u062a\u0648\u062f \u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u062a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u062a\u0648\u062f \u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u062a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Do you have a list of places you want to visit?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I love traveling and exploring new places.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0641\u0631 \u0648\u0627\u0633\u062a\u0643\u0634\u0627\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0641\u0631 \u0648\u0627\u0633\u062a\u0643\u0634\u0627\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "back": "I love traveling and exploring new places.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "These are the places I visited.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u0642\u0645\u062a \u0628\u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u062a\u0647\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u0642\u0645\u062a \u0628\u0632\u064a\u0627\u0631\u062a\u0647\u0627",
      "back": "These are the places I visited.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The tourist places in Egypt are wonderful.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u062d\u064a\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0645\u0635\u0631 \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u062d\u064a\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0645\u0635\u0631 \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639\u0629",
      "back": "The tourist places in Egypt are wonderful.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You should visit historical places.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0632\u0648\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0632\u0648\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "You should visit historical places.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The box is empty.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0646\u062f\u0648\u0642 \u0641\u0627\u0636",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0646\u062f\u0648\u0642 \u0641\u0627\u0636",
      "back": "The box is empty.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you fill the cup for me? - Sorry, the cup is empty.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0644\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0644\u064a\u061f - \u0622\u0633\u0641\u060c \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0641\u0627\u0636",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0644\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0644\u064a\u061f - \u0622\u0633\u0641\u060c \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0628 \u0641\u0627\u0636",
      "back": "Can you fill the cup for me? - Sorry, the cup is empty.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The place is empty today.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "back": "The place is empty today.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The empty page.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0641\u062d\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0641\u062d\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "The empty page.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The street is empty.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639 \u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639 \u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a",
      "back": "The street is empty.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The room is empty.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "The room is empty.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I will stay here until arrival.",
      "back": "\u0633\u0623\u0628\u0642\u0649 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u0623\u0628\u0642\u0649 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644",
      "back": "I will stay here until arrival.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You should work until you succeed.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0646\u062c\u0627\u062d",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0646\u062c\u0627\u062d",
      "back": "You should work until you succeed.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you wait until the afternoon?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0646\u062a\u0638\u0627\u0631 \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0646\u062a\u0638\u0627\u0631 \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "back": "Can you wait until the afternoon?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "When will you go?",
      "back": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0633\u062a\u0630\u0647\u0628\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0633\u062a\u0630\u0647\u0628\u061f",
      "back": "When will you go?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "When do you usually wake up in the morning?",
      "back": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u064a\u0642\u0638 \u0639\u0627\u062f\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u064a\u0642\u0638 \u0639\u0627\u062f\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "back": "When do you usually wake up in the morning?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "When will we meet again?",
      "back": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "back": "When will we meet again?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The shop is open all day.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062d\u0644 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d \u0637\u0648\u0627\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062d\u0644 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d \u0637\u0648\u0627\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "back": "The shop is open all day.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Is the office open today?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "back": "Is the office open today?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The store is open until midnight.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d \u062d\u062a\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d \u062d\u062a\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "back": "The store is open until midnight.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you bring me a book?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062c\u0644\u0628 \u0644\u064a \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062c\u0644\u0628 \u0644\u064a \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Can you bring me a book?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I want you to bring the food.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062c\u0644\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062c\u0644\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "back": "I want you to bring the food.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I brought the gift with me.",
      "back": "\u062c\u0644\u0628\u062a \u0645\u0639\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062c\u0644\u0628\u062a \u0645\u0639\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "I brought the gift with me.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is my duty.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "back": "This is my duty.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I must do my duty.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0642\u0648\u0645 \u0628\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0642\u0648\u0645 \u0628\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "back": "I must do my duty.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am committed to my duty.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0644\u062a\u0632\u0645 \u0628\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0644\u062a\u0632\u0645 \u0628\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "back": "I am committed to my duty.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What is your duty?",
      "back": "\u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "What is your duty?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Duty comes first.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628 \u064a\u0623\u062a\u064a \u0623\u0648\u0644\u0627\u064b",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628 \u064a\u0623\u062a\u064a \u0623\u0648\u0644\u0627\u064b",
      "back": "Duty comes first.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You must fulfill your duty.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u062f\u0627\u0621 \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u062f\u0627\u0621 \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643",
      "back": "You must fulfill your duty.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This hotel has many rooms.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0646\u062f\u0642 \u064a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0646\u062f\u0642 \u064a\u062d\u062a\u0648\u064a \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641",
      "back": "This hotel has many rooms.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you show me the room?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0638\u0647\u0631 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0638\u0647\u0631 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Can you show me the room?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We have three rooms in the house.",
      "back": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0627 \u062b\u0644\u0627\u062b \u063a\u0631\u0641 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0627 \u062b\u0644\u0627\u062b \u063a\u0631\u0641 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "back": "We have three rooms in the house.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is the room I will stay in.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u0633\u0623\u0642\u064a\u0645 \u0641\u064a\u0647\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u0633\u0623\u0642\u064a\u0645 \u0641\u064a\u0647\u0627",
      "back": "This is the room I will stay in.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The room is large and comfortable.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629 \u0648\u0645\u0631\u064a\u062d\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629 \u0648\u0645\u0631\u064a\u062d\u0629",
      "back": "The room is large and comfortable.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you clean the room?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0646\u0638\u064a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0646\u0638\u064a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Can you clean the room?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Where is the cat?",
      "back": "\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u061f",
      "back": "Where is the cat?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Where can I find my keys?",
      "back": "\u064a\u0646 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0627\u062d\u064a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0646 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0627\u062d\u064a\u061f",
      "back": "Where can I find my keys?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Where do you want to go?",
      "back": "\u064a\u0646 \u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0630\u0647\u0628\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0646 \u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0630\u0647\u0628\u061f",
      "back": "Where do you want to go?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Where did he go?",
      "back": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u0631\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u0631\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "back": "Where did he go?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Where are the books?",
      "back": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628\u061f",
      "back": "Where are the books?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Where can I find the restaurant?",
      "back": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0641\u064a\u0646 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645\u061f",
      "back": "Where can I find the restaurant?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I need more time.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0632\u064a\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0632\u064a\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "back": "I need more time.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you need help?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you need help?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I need some rest.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629",
      "back": "I need some rest.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I need to go to the bathroom.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u0647\u0627\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0630\u0647\u0627\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "back": "I need to go to the bathroom.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Where can I find the bathroom?",
      "back": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u062b\u0648\u0631 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "back": "Where can I find the bathroom?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The bathroom is occupied now.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0645\u0634\u063a\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0645\u0634\u063a\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "back": "The bathroom is occupied now.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is the bathroom.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "back": "This is the bathroom.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The bathroom is very clean.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0646\u0638\u064a\u0641 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0646\u0638\u064a\u0641 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "The bathroom is very clean.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I'm in the bathroom now.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "back": "I'm in the bathroom now.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Good morning.",
      "back": "\u0635\u0628\u062d \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0635\u0628\u062d \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "back": "Good morning.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you always wake up early in the morning?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u064a\u0642\u0638 \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0643\u0631\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u064a\u0642\u0638 \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0643\u0631\u061f",
      "back": "Do you always wake up early in the morning?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I love to spend my time in the morning reading.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0645\u0636\u064a \u0648\u0642\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0631\u0627\u0621\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0645\u0636\u064a \u0648\u0642\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0631\u0627\u0621\u0629",
      "back": "I love to spend my time in the morning reading.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Good night.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "back": "Good night.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "May you become what you wish for.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0627 \u062a\u062a\u0645\u0646\u0627\u0647",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0627 \u062a\u062a\u0645\u0646\u0627\u0647",
      "back": "May you become what you wish for.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How do you become in the morning?",
      "back": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d\u061f",
      "back": "How do you become in the morning?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The book is on the table.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0627\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0627\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "back": "The book is on the table.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I'm on the phone now.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u0627\u062a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u0627\u062a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "back": "I'm on the phone now.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The cat is on the bed.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0629 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0631\u064a\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0629 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0631\u064a\u0631",
      "back": "The cat is on the bed.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Good morning.",
      "back": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "back": "Good morning.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Have a good day.",
      "back": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "back": "Have a good day.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The food was very good.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "The food was very good.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How are you?",
      "back": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "How are you?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How are things?",
      "back": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631\u061f",
      "back": "How are things?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How do we get there?",
      "back": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u0646\u0635\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u0646\u0635\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "How do we get there?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How are you, my friend?",
      "back": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643 \u064a\u0627 \u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642\u064a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643 \u064a\u0627 \u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642\u064a\u061f",
      "back": "How are you, my friend?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How are you, my love?",
      "back": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643 \u064a\u0627 \u062d\u0628\u064a\u0628\u064a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643 \u064a\u0627 \u062d\u0628\u064a\u0628\u064a\u061f",
      "back": "How are you, my love?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Are you okay? - Okay.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0628\u062e\u064a\u0631\u061f - \u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0628\u062e\u064a\u0631\u061f - \u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "back": "Are you okay? - Okay.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Are you enjoying your time? - Okay.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a\u061f - \u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a\u061f - \u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "back": "Are you enjoying your time? - Okay.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you help me? - Okay.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f - \u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a\u061f - \u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "back": "Can you help me? - Okay.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Are you good, my friend?",
      "back": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633 \u064a\u0627 \u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642\u064a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633 \u064a\u0627 \u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642\u064a\u061f",
      "back": "Are you good, my friend?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Good means okay.",
      "back": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633 \u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633 \u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "back": "Good means okay.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Good, thank you.",
      "back": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c \u0634\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c \u0634\u0643\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "Good, thank you.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Where do you live?",
      "back": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646\u061f",
      "back": "Where do you live?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you live in Cairo?",
      "back": "\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you live in Cairo?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you live with your family?",
      "back": "\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0645\u0639 \u0639\u0627\u0626\u0644\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0645\u0639 \u0639\u0627\u0626\u0644\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "Do you live with your family?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Where do you live?",
      "back": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "back": "Where do you live?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Who do you live with?",
      "back": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0645\u0639 \u0645\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0645\u0639 \u0645\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "back": "Who do you live with?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you live in an apartment?",
      "back": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0641\u064a \u0634\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0641\u064a \u0634\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you live in an apartment?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I live in Cairo.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u064a\u0634 \u0641\u064a \u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u064a\u0634 \u0641\u064a \u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "back": "I live in Cairo.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Cairo is the capital of Egypt.",
      "back": "\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u0639\u0627\u0635\u0645\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u0639\u0627\u0635\u0645\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "back": "Cairo is the capital of Egypt.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Cairo is a big and modern city.",
      "back": "\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629 \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629 \u0648\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062b\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629 \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629 \u0648\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062b\u0629",
      "back": "Cairo is a big and modern city.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I live in Cairo.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u064a\u0634 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u064a\u0634 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "back": "I live in Cairo.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Cairo is the capital of Egypt.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u0639\u0627\u0635\u0645\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u0639\u0627\u0635\u0645\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "back": "Cairo is the capital of Egypt.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Cairo is a large urban city.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629 \u062d\u0636\u0631\u064a\u0629 \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629 \u062d\u0636\u0631\u064a\u0629 \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "back": "Cairo is a large urban city.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Nice to meet you.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a \u0628\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a \u0628\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0643",
      "back": "Nice to meet you.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Nice to meet you.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "back": "Nice to meet you.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Nice to talk to you.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0625\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0625\u0644\u064a\u0643",
      "back": "Nice to talk to you.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I don't know.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634",
      "back": "I don't know.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I don't know what I should do.",
      "back": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634 \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634 \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "back": "I don't know what I should do.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I don't know how to answer this.",
      "back": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634 \u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0634 \u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "back": "I don't know how to answer this.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you explain that by your knowledge?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0641\u0633\u064a\u0631 \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0641\u0633\u064a\u0631 \u0630\u0644\u0643 \u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "Can you explain that by your knowledge?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you help me by your knowledge?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a \u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a \u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "Can you help me by your knowledge?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I rely on your knowledge.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u062a\u0645\u062f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u062a\u0645\u062f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643",
      "back": "I rely on your knowledge.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What is your name?",
      "back": "\u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "What is your name?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you write your name here?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u0629 \u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u0629 \u0627\u0633\u0645\u0643 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Can you write your name here?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I really like my name.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0633\u0645\u064a \u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0633\u0645\u064a \u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "I really like my name.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What is your name?",
      "back": "\u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "What is your name?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Your name is beautiful.",
      "back": "\u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "back": "Your name is beautiful.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can I know your name?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "Can I know your name?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How much does this car cost?",
      "back": "\u0643\u0645 \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641 \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u0645 \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641 \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "How much does this car cost?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you specify the cost?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Can you specify the cost?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Cost is important when buying something new.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u0645\u0647\u0645\u0629 \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621 \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0647\u064a \u0645\u0647\u0645\u0629 \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621 \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "back": "Cost is important when buying something new.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is the cost of the service.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u062f\u0645\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0647\u064a \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u062f\u0645\u0629",
      "back": "This is the cost of the service.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The system must reduce the cost of production.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0638\u0627\u0645 \u062a\u0642\u0644\u064a\u0644 \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0638\u0627\u0645 \u062a\u0642\u0644\u064a\u0644 \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "back": "The system must reduce the cost of production.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The cost of living is increasing day by day.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0627\u0629 \u062a\u0632\u064a\u062f \u064a\u0648\u0645\u0627 \u0628\u0639\u062f \u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0627\u0629 \u062a\u0632\u064a\u062f \u064a\u0648\u0645\u0627 \u0628\u0639\u062f \u064a\u0648\u0645",
      "back": "The cost of living is increasing day by day.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you remember the moment we met?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u0642\u0627\u0628\u0644\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u064a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u064a \u0642\u0627\u0628\u0644\u0646\u0627 \u0641\u064a\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Do you remember the moment we met?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You should remember the rules.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0648\u0627\u0639\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0648\u0627\u0639\u062f",
      "back": "You should remember the rules.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you remember what happened?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631 \u0645\u0627 \u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631 \u0645\u0627 \u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "back": "Can you remember what happened?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Where can you buy the ticket?",
      "back": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u064a\u0646 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0634\u0631\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Where can you buy the ticket?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you have the admission ticket?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u062e\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u062e\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "back": "Do you have the admission ticket?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We should book the airplane ticket in advance.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u062d\u062c\u0632 \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0627\u0626\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u0633\u0628\u0642\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u062d\u062c\u0632 \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0627\u0626\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u0633\u0628\u0642\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "We should book the airplane ticket in advance.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I will go to work.",
      "back": "\u0633\u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "back": "I will go to work.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you take me to the airport?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0623\u062e\u0630\u0646\u064a \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0637\u064a\u0639 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0623\u062e\u0630\u0646\u064a \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631\u061f",
      "back": "Can you take me to the airport?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you know how to get to the library?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0643\u064a\u0641\u064a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you know how to get to the library?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "My mother loves cooking.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0645\u064a \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0647\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0645\u064a \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0647\u064a",
      "back": "My mother loves cooking.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "My mother is the best person in the world.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0645\u064a \u0647\u064a \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0634\u062e\u0635 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0645\u064a \u0647\u064a \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0634\u062e\u0635 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645",
      "back": "My mother is the best person in the world.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "My mother always gives me advice.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0645\u064a \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0645 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0645\u064a \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0645 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "back": "My mother always gives me advice.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How many brothers do you have?",
      "back": "\u0643\u0627\u0645 \u0623\u062e \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u0627\u0645 \u0623\u062e \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "How many brothers do you have?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How many watches do you have?",
      "back": "\u0643\u0627\u0645 \u0633\u0627\u0639\u0629 \u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u0627\u0645 \u0633\u0627\u0639\u0629 \u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "How many watches do you have?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How many books do you read?",
      "back": "\u0643\u0627\u0645 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623\u0647\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u0627\u0645 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u062a\u0642\u0631\u0623\u0647\u061f",
      "back": "How many books do you read?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How was today's lesson?",
      "back": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "back": "How was today's lesson?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you have a lesson tomorrow?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u062f\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u062f\u061f",
      "back": "Do you have a lesson tomorrow?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The lesson was very enjoyable.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639\u064b\u0627 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639\u064b\u0627 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "The lesson was very enjoyable.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I study at the university.",
      "back": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "back": "I study at the university.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I study to pass the exam.",
      "back": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0644\u0627\u062c\u062a\u064a\u0627\u0632 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0645\u062a\u062d\u0627\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0644\u0627\u062c\u062a\u064a\u0627\u0632 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0645\u062a\u062d\u0627\u0646",
      "back": "I study to pass the exam.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I study about history.",
      "back": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0639\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0639\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e",
      "back": "I study about history.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is a big mosque.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631",
      "back": "This is a big mosque.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The mosque is a place for prayer.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u0647\u0648 \u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0644\u0644\u0635\u0644\u0627\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u0647\u0648 \u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0644\u0644\u0635\u0644\u0627\u0629",
      "back": "The mosque is a place for prayer.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I like to go to the mosque on Fridays.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "back": "I like to go to the mosque on Fridays.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The university provides high-quality education.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0645 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0645 \u0639\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u062f\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0645 \u062a\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0645 \u0639\u0627\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u062f\u0629",
      "back": "The university provides high-quality education.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you study at the university?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you study at the university?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am from Egypt.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0646 \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0646 \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "back": "I am from Egypt.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Egypt is a beautiful country.",
      "back": "\u0645\u0635\u0631 \u0647\u064a \u062f\u0648\u0644\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0635\u0631 \u0647\u064a \u062f\u0648\u0644\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "back": "Egypt is a beautiful country.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Egypt has a long and rich history.",
      "back": "\u0645\u0635\u0631 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0647\u0627 \u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e \u0637\u0648\u064a\u0644 \u0648\u0639\u0631\u064a\u0642",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0635\u0631 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0647\u0627 \u062a\u0627\u0631\u064a\u062e \u0637\u0648\u064a\u0644 \u0648\u0639\u0631\u064a\u0642",
      "back": "Egypt has a long and rich history.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "She is Egyptian.",
      "back": "\u0647\u064a \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u064a \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "She is Egyptian.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The Egyptian woman is strong.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0631\u0623\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629 \u0642\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0631\u0623\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629 \u0642\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "The Egyptian woman is strong.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Egyptian culture is rich and diverse.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629 \u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u0648\u0645\u062a\u0646\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629 \u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u0648\u0645\u062a\u0646\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "back": "Egyptian culture is rich and diverse.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you get me some water?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062c\u0644\u0628 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062c\u0644\u0628 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "back": "Can you get me some water?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I need you to get me food.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0643 \u0644\u062a\u062c\u0644\u0628 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c\u0643 \u0644\u062a\u062c\u0644\u0628 \u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "back": "I need you to get me food.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Did you get the car key?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062c\u0644\u0628\u062a \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062c\u0644\u0628\u062a \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Did you get the car key?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I get vegetables from the market.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0636\u0627\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u0642",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0636\u0627\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u0642",
      "back": "I get vegetables from the market.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I get breakfast every morning.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0637\u0648\u0631 \u0643\u0644 \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0637\u0648\u0631 \u0643\u0644 \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "back": "I get breakfast every morning.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I get information from the internet.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0644\u0648\u0645\u0627\u062a \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0631\u0646\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0644\u0648\u0645\u0627\u062a \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0631\u0646\u062a",
      "back": "I get information from the internet.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What is the price of this product?",
      "back": "\u0643\u0645 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u0645 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u061f",
      "back": "What is the price of this product?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The price is reasonable.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0639\u0642\u0648\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0639\u0642\u0648\u0644",
      "back": "The price is reasonable.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The price may change.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0642\u062f \u064a\u062a\u063a\u064a\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0642\u062f \u064a\u062a\u063a\u064a\u0631",
      "back": "The price may change.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I want to take the bus.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0631\u0643\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0631\u0643\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "back": "I want to take the bus.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can I know the bus schedule?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0645\u0648\u0627\u0639\u064a\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0645\u0648\u0627\u0639\u064a\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633\u061f",
      "back": "Can I know the bus schedule?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The bus is crowded at this time.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u0645\u0632\u062f\u062d\u0645 \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u0645\u0632\u062f\u062d\u0645 \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0642\u062a",
      "back": "The bus is crowded at this time.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The bus has arrived.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u0642\u062f \u0648\u0635\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u0642\u062f \u0648\u0635\u0644",
      "back": "The bus has arrived.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We should take the bus.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0623\u062e\u0630 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0623\u062e\u0630 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "back": "We should take the bus.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Is the bus available now?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u0645\u062a\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u0645\u062a\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646\u061f",
      "back": "Is the bus available now?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "He goes to school every day.",
      "back": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "He goes to school every day.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "He goes to work by car.",
      "back": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "back": "He goes to work by car.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "He goes to the gym every morning.",
      "back": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0627\u0644\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u064a\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629 \u0643\u0644 \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0627\u0644\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u064a\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629 \u0643\u0644 \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "back": "He goes to the gym every morning.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "He goes to the university.",
      "back": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "back": "He goes to the university.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "He goes to work by train.",
      "back": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0627\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0637\u0627\u0631",
      "back": "He goes to work by train.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "He goes to the library on Sundays.",
      "back": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628\u0629 \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062d\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628\u0629 \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062d\u062f",
      "back": "He goes to the library on Sundays.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The flower is dead.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0632\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u0627\u062a\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0632\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u0627\u062a\u062a",
      "back": "The flower is dead.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Is this animal dead?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0648\u0627\u0646 \u0645\u062a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u064a\u0648\u0627\u0646 \u0645\u062a\u061f",
      "back": "Is this animal dead?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Hope is not dead.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0644 \u0644\u064a\u0633 \u0645\u0627\u062a\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0644 \u0644\u064a\u0633 \u0645\u0627\u062a\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "Hope is not dead.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I slept all night.",
      "back": "\u0646\u0645\u062a \u0637\u0648\u0627\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u0645\u062a \u0637\u0648\u0627\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "back": "I slept all night.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I slept in the big room.",
      "back": "\u0646\u0645\u062a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u0645\u062a \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "back": "I slept in the big room.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I didn't sleep last night.",
      "back": "\u0644\u0645 \u0623\u0646\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u0645 \u0623\u0646\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "I didn't sleep last night.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What do you eat for lunch?",
      "back": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0644\u0644\u063a\u062f\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0644\u0644\u063a\u062f\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "back": "What do you eat for lunch?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you eat fruits every day?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0648\u0627\u0643\u0647 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0648\u0627\u0643\u0647 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064a\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Do you eat fruits every day?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is the new house.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "back": "This is the new house.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you know this man?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u062c\u0644\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u062c\u0644\u061f",
      "back": "Do you know this man?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is my favorite book.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "back": "This is my favorite book.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We want tea.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646 \u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646 \u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "back": "We want tea.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We want to go to the restaurant.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646 \u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0644\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646 \u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0644\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645",
      "back": "We want to go to the restaurant.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We want to learn something new.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646 \u0646\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646 \u0646\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "We want to learn something new.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Will you have lunch with me?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u0645\u0639\u064a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u0645\u0639\u064a\u061f",
      "back": "Will you have lunch with me?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Will you have lunch at school?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0633\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0633\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Will you have lunch at school?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I love having pizza for lunch.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u062a\u063a\u062f\u064a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a\u0632\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u062a\u063a\u062f\u064a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a\u0632\u0627",
      "back": "I love having pizza for lunch.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We have lunch at the caf\u00e9.",
      "back": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0647\u0649",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0647\u0649",
      "back": "We have lunch at the caf\u00e9.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We have lunch at school.",
      "back": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629",
      "back": "We have lunch at school.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We have lunch with friends.",
      "back": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u0645\u0639 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649 \u0645\u0639 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "back": "We have lunch with friends.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "If you're ready, we'll go now.",
      "back": "\u0625\u0646 \u0643\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0633\u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0646 \u0643\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f\u064b\u0627\u060c \u0633\u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0622\u0646",
      "back": "If you're ready, we'll go now.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "If you like chocolate, this is for you.",
      "back": "\u0625\u0646 \u0643\u0646\u062a \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0648\u0643\u0648\u0644\u0627\u062a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0644\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0646 \u0643\u0646\u062a \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0648\u0643\u0648\u0644\u0627\u062a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0644\u0643",
      "back": "If you like chocolate, this is for you.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "If you have any questions, feel free to ask.",
      "back": "\u0625\u0646 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u064a \u0623\u0633\u0626\u0644\u0629\u060c \u0641\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u062a\u0631\u062f\u062f \u0641\u064a \u0637\u0631\u062d\u0647\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0646 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u064a \u0623\u0633\u0626\u0644\u0629\u060c \u0641\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u062a\u0631\u062f\u062f \u0641\u064a \u0637\u0631\u062d\u0647\u0627",
      "back": "If you have any questions, feel free to ask.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What are you doing?",
      "back": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "back": "What are you doing?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How are you?",
      "back": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643 \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643 \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "back": "How are you?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Where are you going?",
      "back": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u0628\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u0628\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "back": "Where are you going?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Hunger hurts.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0639 \u064a\u0624\u0644\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0639 \u064a\u0624\u0644\u0645",
      "back": "Hunger hurts.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am very hungry.",
      "back": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u062c\u0648\u0639 \u0634\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u062c\u0648\u0639 \u0634\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "back": "I am very hungry.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you help me relieve hunger?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a \u062a\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0639\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0645\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f\u062a\u064a \u0641\u064a \u062a\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0639\u061f",
      "back": "Can you help me relieve hunger?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I'm hungry.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062c\u0648\u0639\u0627\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062c\u0648\u0639\u0627\u0646",
      "back": "I'm hungry.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can I get something to eat?",
      "back": "\u0628\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0644\u064a \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0644\u064a \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0644\u0623\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "back": "Can I get something to eat?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "When do we go for food?",
      "back": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0644\u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0646\u0630\u0647\u0628 \u0644\u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "back": "When do we go for food?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I will leave the office soon.",
      "back": "\u0633\u0623\u062e\u0631\u062c \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0642\u0631\u064a\u0628\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u0623\u062e\u0631\u062c \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0642\u0631\u064a\u0628\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "I will leave the office soon.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you inform me when you leave?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062e\u0628\u0631\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f\u0645\u0627 \u062a\u062e\u0631\u062c\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062e\u0628\u0631\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f\u0645\u0627 \u062a\u062e\u0631\u062c\u061f",
      "back": "Can you inform me when you leave?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Don't leave me.",
      "back": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a",
      "back": "Don't leave me.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Will you leave me?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0633\u062a\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0633\u062a\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "back": "Will you leave me?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You leave me alone.",
      "back": "\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a \u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a \u0648\u062d\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "You leave me alone.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Will he go down the mountain?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0633\u064a\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0628\u0644\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0633\u064a\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0628\u0644\u061f",
      "back": "Will he go down the mountain?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I want to go down the stairs.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u062c",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u062c",
      "back": "I want to go down the stairs.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can I lower the window?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Can I lower the window?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I go down the stairs slowly.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u062c \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u062c \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "back": "I go down the stairs slowly.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "When I go down the street, I will buy food.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0645\u0627 \u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639\u060c \u0633\u0623\u0634\u062a\u0631\u064a \u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0645\u0627 \u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639\u060c \u0633\u0623\u0634\u062a\u0631\u064a \u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "When I go down the street, I will buy food.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Lower the volume, please.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "back": "Lower the volume, please.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You must stop the car.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "back": "You must stop the car.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The bus will stop here.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u0641\u0644\u0629 \u0633\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u0641\u0644\u0629 \u0633\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "back": "The bus will stop here.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you stop for a moment?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0644\u062d\u0638\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Can you stop for a moment?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You must stop here.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "back": "You must stop here.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Stop this noise!",
      "back": "\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0636\u0648\u0636\u0627\u0621!",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0636\u0648\u0636\u0627\u0621!",
      "back": "Stop this noise!",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you stop the car?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Can you stop the car?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I don't like talking about myself.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062b \u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u062d\u062f\u064a\u062b \u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "back": "I don't like talking about myself.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you know anything about me?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u0639\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u0639\u0646\u064a\u061f",
      "back": "Do you know anything about me?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I don't talk about myself much.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0639\u0646\u064a \u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0627 \u0623\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0639\u0646\u064a \u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "I don't talk about myself much.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What does this word mean?",
      "back": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "What does this word mean?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "It means a lot to me.",
      "back": "\u0625\u0646\u0647 \u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0633\u0628\u0629 \u0644\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0646\u0647 \u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0633\u0628\u0629 \u0644\u064a",
      "back": "It means a lot to me.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I don't know what it means.",
      "back": "\u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u0627 \u0623\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "back": "I don't know what it means.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am Arab.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a",
      "back": "I am Arab.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Arab culture is rich and diverse.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u0648\u0645\u062a\u0646\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0642\u0627\u0641\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u0648\u0645\u062a\u0646\u0648\u0639\u0629",
      "back": "Arab culture is rich and diverse.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "He speaks Arabic fluently.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u0628\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062a\u062d\u062f\u062b \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629 \u0628\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "back": "He speaks Arabic fluently.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I didn't understand what you said.",
      "back": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634 \u0645\u0627 \u0642\u0644\u062a\u0647",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634 \u0645\u0627 \u0642\u0644\u062a\u0647",
      "back": "I didn't understand what you said.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I didn't understand this lesson.",
      "back": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "back": "I didn't understand this lesson.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I didn't understand the situation.",
      "back": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "back": "I didn't understand the situation.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I like this place.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "back": "I like this place.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Comedy movies are liked by everyone.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0641\u0644\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0645\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0629 \u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0641\u0644\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0648\u0645\u064a\u062f\u064a\u0629 \u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0639",
      "back": "Comedy movies are liked by everyone.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What do you like about this artist?",
      "back": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643 \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0646\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0643 \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0646\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "back": "What do you like about this artist?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I like this album.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0644\u0628\u0648\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0644\u0628\u0648\u0645",
      "back": "I like this album.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I really like the movie.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "I really like the movie.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I like this color.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0648\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0648\u0646",
      "back": "I like this color.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I love to listen to music.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "back": "I love to listen to music.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Music is the language of emotions.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649 \u0647\u064a \u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0648\u0627\u0637\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649 \u0647\u064a \u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0648\u0627\u0637\u0641",
      "back": "Music is the language of emotions.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you play music?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0632\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0632\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649\u061f",
      "back": "Do you play music?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can I listen to your music?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0633\u0645\u0627\u0639 \u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0633\u0645\u0627\u0639 \u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "Can I listen to your music?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am a fan of your music.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0639\u062c\u0628 \u0628\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0639\u062c\u0628 \u0628\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643",
      "back": "I am a fan of your music.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How can I get your music?",
      "back": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "How can I get your music?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This proposal is acceptable.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0642\u062a\u0631\u0627\u062d \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0642\u062a\u0631\u0627\u062d \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "back": "This proposal is acceptable.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The price is very acceptable.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "The price is very acceptable.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Inappropriate behavior is not acceptable.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0644\u0648\u0643 \u063a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0644\u0627\u0626\u0645 \u063a\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0644\u0648\u0643 \u063a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0644\u0627\u0626\u0645 \u063a\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "back": "Inappropriate behavior is not acceptable.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This idea is acceptable.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "back": "This idea is acceptable.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The overall appearance is acceptable.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0638\u0647\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0638\u0647\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "back": "The overall appearance is acceptable.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The quality provided is very acceptable.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u062f\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0629 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u062f\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0629 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "The quality provided is very acceptable.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I will go down the stairs.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0644\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0644\u0645",
      "back": "I will go down the stairs.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I will go down the street.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u0631\u0639",
      "back": "I will go down the street.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I will lower the volume.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a",
      "back": "I will lower the volume.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I have an appointment at 3 o'clock.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u0639\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062b\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0627\u0639\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062b\u0627\u0644\u062b\u0629",
      "back": "I have an appointment at 3 o'clock.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I have many friends.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0635\u062f\u0642\u0627\u0621",
      "back": "I have many friends.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I have a good idea.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "back": "I have a good idea.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I turned on the TV.",
      "back": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0644\u0641\u0632\u064a\u0648\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0644\u0641\u0632\u064a\u0648\u0646",
      "back": "I turned on the TV.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I turned on the music.",
      "back": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "back": "I turned on the music.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I turned on the light.",
      "back": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0636\u0648\u0621",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0636\u0648\u0621",
      "back": "I turned on the light.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The weather is very hot.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648 \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u0632\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648 \u062d\u0627\u0631 \u0632\u0627",
      "back": "The weather is very hot.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This food is very delicious.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630 \u0632\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630 \u0632\u0627",
      "back": "This food is very delicious.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This movie is very enjoyable.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u0632\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u064a\u0644\u0645 \u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u0632\u0627",
      "back": "This movie is very enjoyable.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am sure about that.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0630\u0644\u0643",
      "back": "I am sure about that.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Are you sure about the answer?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0648\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "back": "Are you sure about the answer?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We must be sure about the plan.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f\u064a\u0646 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0637\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0646\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f\u064a\u0646 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0637\u0629",
      "back": "We must be sure about the plan.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is the best book ever for me.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0633\u0628\u0629 \u0644\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0633\u0628\u0629 \u0644\u064a",
      "back": "This is the best book ever for me.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you do this for me?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u0628\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0644\u0623\u062c\u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u064a\u0627\u0645 \u0628\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0644\u0623\u062c\u0644\u064a\u061f",
      "back": "Can you do this for me?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is very important for me.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0645\u0647\u0645 \u0644\u064a \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0645\u0647\u0645 \u0644\u064a \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "This is very important for me.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Music expresses emotions.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649 \u062a\u0639\u0628\u0631 \u0639\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0627\u0639\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649 \u062a\u0639\u0628\u0631 \u0639\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0627\u0639\u0631",
      "back": "Music expresses emotions.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you listen to music?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0633\u062a\u0645\u0639 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649\u061f",
      "back": "Do you listen to music?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am a music lover.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062d\u0628 \u0644\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062d\u0628 \u0644\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "back": "I am a music lover.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This place is very beautiful.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "This place is very beautiful.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This painting is beautiful.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0648\u062d\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0648\u062d\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "back": "This painting is beautiful.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The sunset is beautiful.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0645\u0633 \u063a\u0631\u0648\u0628 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0645\u0633 \u063a\u0631\u0648\u0628 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "back": "The sunset is beautiful.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This girl is beautiful.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u062a\u0627\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u062a\u0627\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "back": "This girl is beautiful.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Nature is very beautiful.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0628\u064a\u0639\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0628\u064a\u0639\u0629 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "Nature is very beautiful.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This flower is beautiful.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0632\u0647\u0631 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0632\u0647\u0631 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "back": "This flower is beautiful.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Don't be upset quickly.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634 \u0628\u0633\u0631\u0639\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634 \u0628\u0633\u0631\u0639\u0629",
      "back": "Don't be upset quickly.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Don't be upset about this.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634 \u0645\u0646 \u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634 \u0645\u0646 \u0647\u0630\u0627",
      "back": "Don't be upset about this.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Don't be upset about small things.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0634\u064a\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u063a\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0634\u064a\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u063a\u064a\u0631\u0629",
      "back": "Don't be upset about small things.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What do you mean by this?",
      "back": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f \u0628\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0627\u0630\u0627 \u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f \u0628\u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "What do you mean by this?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you mean you don't know?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641\u061f",
      "back": "Do you mean you don't know?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you mean you will come tomorrow?",
      "back": "\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u0633\u062a\u0623\u062a\u064a \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u0633\u062a\u0623\u062a\u064a \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Do you mean you will come tomorrow?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you mean you don't care?",
      "back": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647 \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0647\u062a\u0645\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647 \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0647\u062a\u0645\u061f",
      "back": "Do you mean you don't care?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you mean it's not a problem?",
      "back": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647 \u0623\u0646\u0647\u0627 \u0644\u064a\u0633\u062a \u0645\u0634\u0643\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647 \u0623\u0646\u0647\u0627 \u0644\u064a\u0633\u062a \u0645\u0634\u0643\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you mean it's not a problem?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you mean you will leave?",
      "back": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647 \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u0633\u062a\u062a\u0631\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647 \u0623\u0646\u0643 \u0633\u062a\u062a\u0631\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "Do you mean you will leave?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I'm sorry if I hurt your feelings.",
      "back": "\u0622\u0633\u0641 \u0625\u0630\u0627 \u062c\u0631\u062d\u062a \u0645\u0634\u0627\u0639\u0631\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0622\u0633\u0641 \u0625\u0630\u0627 \u062c\u0631\u062d\u062a \u0645\u0634\u0627\u0639\u0631\u0643",
      "back": "I'm sorry if I hurt your feelings.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Sorry for the delay.",
      "back": "\u0622\u0633\u0641 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0623\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0622\u0633\u0641 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0623\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "back": "Sorry for the delay.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Sorry is not enough.",
      "back": "\u0622\u0633\u0641 \u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0643\u0641\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0622\u0633\u0641 \u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0643\u0641\u064a",
      "back": "Sorry is not enough.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This place is very noisy.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "This place is very noisy.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The sound is noisy.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a \u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0635\u0648\u062a \u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634",
      "back": "The sound is noisy.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Children make the house noisy.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0641\u0627\u0644 \u064a\u062c\u0639\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a \u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0641\u0627\u0644 \u064a\u062c\u0639\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u064a\u062a \u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "Children make the house noisy.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "These books are very good.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "These books are very good.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This food is good.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "back": "This food is good.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Is this idea good?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Is this idea good?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Turn the button.",
      "back": "\u062f\u0648\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0632\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062f\u0648\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0632\u0631",
      "back": "Turn the button.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Turn the page.",
      "back": "\u062f\u0648\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0641\u062d\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062f\u0648\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0641\u062d\u0629",
      "back": "Turn the page.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Turn left.",
      "back": "\u062f\u0648\u0631 \u064a\u0633\u0627\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062f\u0648\u0631 \u064a\u0633\u0627\u0631\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "Turn left.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am taking a course in English.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0623\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "I am taking a course in English.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you prefer a specific course?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u0639\u064a\u0646\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0645\u0639\u064a\u0646\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you prefer a specific course?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The swimming course starts in the summer.",
      "back": "\u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629 \u062a\u0628\u062f\u0623 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629 \u062a\u0628\u062f\u0623 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u064a\u0641",
      "back": "The swimming course starts in the summer.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You must repeat this lesson.",
      "back": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u062c\u0628 \u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "back": "You must repeat this lesson.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you repeat this?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631 \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631 \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Can you repeat this?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I can repeat the numbers.",
      "back": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0631\u0642\u0627\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0627\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0631\u0642\u0627\u0645",
      "back": "I can repeat the numbers.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How do you know this?",
      "back": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0647\u0630\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "How do you know this?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How do you do that?",
      "back": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0630\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u062a\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0630\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "How do you do that?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How can I get to the airport?",
      "back": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0648\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0627\u0631\u061f",
      "back": "How can I get to the airport?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you translate this sentence?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Can you translate this sentence?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I will try to translate this text.",
      "back": "\u0633\u0623\u062d\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0635",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u0623\u062d\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0635",
      "back": "I will try to translate this text.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How can I translate this book?",
      "back": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645\u0629 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645\u0629 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628\u061f",
      "back": "How can I translate this book?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I translate books from English to Arabic.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u062a\u0628 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629 \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "I translate books from English to Arabic.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I love to translate poetry.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0639\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0639\u0631",
      "back": "I love to translate poetry.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can I translate this article?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0627\u0644\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0627\u0644\u061f",
      "back": "Can I translate this article?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What is the correct meaning of this word?",
      "back": "\u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u062d\u064a\u062d \u0644\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u062d\u064a\u062d \u0644\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0645\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "What is the correct meaning of this word?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I have a different meaning.",
      "back": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649 \u0645\u062e\u062a\u0644\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u062f\u064a \u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649 \u0645\u062e\u062a\u0644\u0641",
      "back": "I have a different meaning.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you explain the meaning?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0634\u0631\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0643 \u0634\u0631\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649\u061f",
      "back": "Can you explain the meaning?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(The restaurant) serves the best food.",
      "back": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645) \u064a\u0642\u062f\u0645 \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0639\u0645\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645) \u064a\u0642\u062f\u0645 \u0623\u0641\u0636\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0637\u0639\u0645\u0629",
      "back": "(The restaurant) serves the best food.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(The restaurant) is a great place for dinner.",
      "back": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645) \u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639 \u0644\u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0634\u0627\u0621",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645) \u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639 \u0644\u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0634\u0627\u0621",
      "back": "(The restaurant) is a great place for dinner.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(The restaurant) is famous for its delicious dishes.",
      "back": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645) \u0645\u0634\u0647\u0648\u0631 \u0628\u0623\u0637\u0628\u0627\u0642\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645) \u0645\u0634\u0647\u0648\u0631 \u0628\u0623\u0637\u0628\u0627\u0642\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630\u0629",
      "back": "(The restaurant) is famous for its delicious dishes.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The book is beautiful.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0640 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0640 \u0643\u062a\u0627\u0628 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "back": "The book is beautiful.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The theater is amazing.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0640 \u0645\u0633\u0631\u062d \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0640 \u0645\u0633\u0631\u062d \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "back": "The theater is amazing.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The restaurant here is famous.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0640 \u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0634\u0647\u064a\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0640 \u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645 \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0634\u0647\u064a\u0631",
      "back": "The restaurant here is famous.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(The food) here is delicious.",
      "back": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645) \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645) \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "back": "(The food) here is delicious.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(The food) at this place is good.",
      "back": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645) \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645) \u0641\u064a \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "back": "(The food) at this place is good.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(The food) at the restaurant is amazing.",
      "back": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645) \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645 \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645) \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645 \u0631\u0627\u0626\u0639",
      "back": "(The food) at the restaurant is amazing.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This product is made in Egypt.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c \u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644 \u0641\u064a \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c \u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644 \u0641\u064a \u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "back": "This product is made in Egypt.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Handmade.",
      "back": "\u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644 \u064a\u062f\u0648\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644 \u064a\u062f\u0648\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "Handmade.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you know where this is made?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0645\u0646 \u0623\u064a\u0646 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "back": "Do you know where this is made?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I love meat.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "back": "I love meat.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can I get some meat?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0644\u062d\u0645\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0644\u062d\u0645\u061f",
      "back": "Can I get some meat?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The meat is very delicious.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u062d\u0645 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "The meat is very delicious.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Is this possible?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646\u061f",
      "back": "Is this possible?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What are the possible options?",
      "back": "\u0645\u0627 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0627 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0648\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "What are the possible options?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Everything is possible.",
      "back": "\u0643\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646",
      "back": "Everything is possible.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you want some tea?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0634\u0627\u064a\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0634\u0627\u064a\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Do you want some tea?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Tea helps to relax.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u064a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0633\u062a\u0631\u062e\u0627\u0621",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u064a\u0633\u0627\u0639\u062f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0633\u062a\u0631\u062e\u0627\u0621",
      "back": "Tea helps to relax.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I like to drink mint tea.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u0634\u0627\u064a\u064b\u0627 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0634\u0631\u0628 \u0634\u0627\u064a\u064b\u0627 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "back": "I like to drink mint tea.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you like black coffee?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u062f\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u062f\u0627\u0621\u061f",
      "back": "Do you like black coffee?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The dress is black.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0633\u062a\u0627\u0646 \u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0633\u062a\u0627\u0646 \u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "back": "The dress is black.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The moon shines in the black sky.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0645\u0631 \u0644\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0645\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u062f\u0627\u0621",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0645\u0631 \u0644\u0627\u0645\u0639 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0645\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0648\u062f\u0627\u0621",
      "back": "The moon shines in the black sky.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is the color black.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0648\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "back": "This is the color black.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The car is black in color.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0644\u0648\u0646\u0647\u0627 \u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0644\u0648\u0646\u0647\u0627 \u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "back": "The car is black in color.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The dog is black.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0628 \u0644\u0648\u0646\u0647 \u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0628 \u0644\u0648\u0646\u0647 \u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "back": "The dog is black.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Mint adds a refreshing flavor.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639 \u064a\u0636\u064a\u0641 \u0646\u0643\u0647\u0629 \u0645\u0646\u0639\u0634\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639 \u064a\u0636\u064a\u0641 \u0646\u0643\u0647\u0629 \u0645\u0646\u0639\u0634\u0629",
      "back": "Mint adds a refreshing flavor.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Mint tea is delicious.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639 \u0644\u0630\u064a\u0630",
      "back": "Mint tea is delicious.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you have mint?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643 \u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639\u061f",
      "back": "Do you have mint?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can I get tea with mint?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0634\u0627\u064a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0635\u0648\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u0634\u0627\u064a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639\u061f",
      "back": "Can I get tea with mint?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This drink is prepared with mint.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0628 \u0645\u0639\u062f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0628 \u0645\u0639\u062f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "back": "This drink is prepared with mint.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I like tea with mint.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0627\u064a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "back": "I like tea with mint.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am full from the food.",
      "back": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645",
      "back": "I am full from the food.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I got full quickly.",
      "back": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a \u0628\u0633\u0631\u0639\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a \u0628\u0633\u0631\u0639\u0629",
      "back": "I got full quickly.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I can't eat more, I am full.",
      "back": "\u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0632\u064a\u062f\u060c \u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u062a\u0646\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0632\u064a\u062f\u060c \u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a",
      "back": "I can't eat more, I am full.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am full from the meal.",
      "back": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062c\u0628\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0648\u062c\u0628\u0629",
      "back": "I am full from the meal.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The verb can be strong.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0623\u0646 \u064a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0642\u0648\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0623\u0646 \u064a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0642\u0648\u064a\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "The verb can be strong.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How do you know the verb?",
      "back": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062a\u0639\u0631\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u061f",
      "back": "How do you know the verb?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is a difficult verb.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0635\u0639\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0635\u0639\u0628",
      "back": "This is a difficult verb.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Indeed, that is true.",
      "back": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u060c \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0635\u062d\u064a\u062d",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u060c \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0635\u062d\u064a\u062d",
      "back": "Indeed, that is true.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you really believe it will happen?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u062a\u0642\u062f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u0647 \u0633\u064a\u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u062a\u0639\u062a\u0642\u062f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u0647 \u0633\u064a\u062d\u062f\u062b\u061f",
      "back": "Do you really believe it will happen?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Indeed, that is interesting.",
      "back": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u060c \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0645\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0644\u0644\u0627\u0647\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u060c \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0645\u062b\u064a\u0631 \u0644\u0644\u0627\u0647\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "back": "Indeed, that is interesting.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We take the bus.",
      "back": "\u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u0641\u0644\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u0641\u0644\u0629",
      "back": "We take the bus.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We take coffee.",
      "back": "\u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "back": "We take coffee.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We take the decision.",
      "back": "\u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0631\u0627\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0631\u0627\u0631",
      "back": "We take the decision.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "We will meet tomorrow.",
      "back": "\u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "We will meet tomorrow.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Tomorrow will be a sunny day.",
      "back": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0633\u064a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u0645\u0634\u0645\u0633\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0633\u064a\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u064a\u0648\u0645\u064b\u0627 \u0645\u0634\u0645\u0633\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "Tomorrow will be a sunny day.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Tomorrow is a holiday.",
      "back": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0637\u0644\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0648\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0637\u0644\u0629",
      "back": "Tomorrow is a holiday.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I present to you this gift.",
      "back": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "I present to you this gift.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I present to them the plan.",
      "back": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0647\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0637\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0647\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0637\u0629",
      "back": "I present to them the plan.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I present to me the project.",
      "back": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639",
      "back": "I present to me the project.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I present to you this gift.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643 \u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u062f\u064a\u0629",
      "back": "I present to you this gift.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I present to you my thanks.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0643\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u0643\u0631",
      "back": "I present to you my thanks.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I present to you a new opportunity.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643 \u0641\u0631\u0635\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643 \u0641\u0631\u0635\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "back": "I present to you a new opportunity.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This phone is new.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u0627\u062a\u0641 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u0627\u062a\u0641 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "back": "This phone is new.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you have new products?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643\u0645 \u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u0627\u062a \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0644\u062f\u064a\u0643\u0645 \u0645\u0646\u062a\u062c\u0627\u062a \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Do you have new products?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This project is new and exciting.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0648\u0645\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639 \u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f \u0648\u0645\u062b\u064a\u0631",
      "back": "This project is new and exciting.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is the new car.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u064a\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "back": "This is the new car.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "New opportunities always come.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0631\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u062a\u0623\u062a\u064a \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0631\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u062a\u0623\u062a\u064a \u062f\u0627\u0626\u0645\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "New opportunities always come.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The new one has a beautiful design.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u0644\u0647\u0627 \u062a\u0635\u0645\u064a\u0645 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629 \u0644\u0647\u0627 \u062a\u0635\u0645\u064a\u0645 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "back": "The new one has a beautiful design.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am tired.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0628",
      "back": "I am tired.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I got tired from work.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0628\u062a \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0628\u062a \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "back": "I got tired from work.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can I sit down to rest? I am tired.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633 \u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633 \u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0628",
      "back": "Can I sit down to rest? I am tired.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am tired.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "back": "I am tired.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am very tired from work.",
      "back": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646 \u062c\u062f\u064b\u0627 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644",
      "back": "I am very tired from work.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can I sit down to rest? I am tired.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633 \u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646\u0646\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0644\u0648\u0633 \u0644\u0644\u0631\u0627\u062d\u0629\u061f \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "back": "Can I sit down to rest? I am tired.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How are you? And you?",
      "back": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643\u061f \u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643\u061f \u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u061f",
      "back": "How are you? And you?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am fine, and you?",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062e\u064a\u0631\u060c \u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062e\u064a\u0631\u060c \u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u061f",
      "back": "I am fine, and you?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "And you, how do you feel?",
      "back": "\u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u060c \u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062a\u0634\u0639\u0631\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u060c \u0643\u064a\u0641 \u062a\u0634\u0639\u0631\u061f",
      "back": "And you, how do you feel?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I love Sunday morning.",
      "back": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062d\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062d\u0628 \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062d\u062f",
      "back": "I love Sunday morning.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Beautiful morning.",
      "back": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "back": "Beautiful morning.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is the good.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "back": "This is the good.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Good work takes time.",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062f \u064a\u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0648\u0642\u062a\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u064a\u062f \u064a\u062a\u0637\u0644\u0628 \u0648\u0642\u062a\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "Good work takes time.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I want to do something good.",
      "back": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0631\u064a\u062f \u0623\u0646 \u0623\u0641\u0639\u0644 \u0634\u064a\u0626\u064b\u0627 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u064b\u0627",
      "back": "I want to do something good.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "He closes the door.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0628",
      "back": "He closes the door.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Does he close the window?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Does he close the window?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "He closes the store at night.",
      "back": "\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "back": "He closes the store at night.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "He closes the door.",
      "back": "\u0647\u0648 \u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0648 \u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0628\u0627\u0628",
      "back": "He closes the door.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Does he close the window?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0648 \u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0647\u0648 \u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0627\u0641\u0630\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Does he close the window?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "He closes the store at night.",
      "back": "\u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062a\u062c\u0631 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a\u0644",
      "back": "He closes the store at night.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "When will you come back?",
      "back": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0633\u062a\u0639\u0648\u062f\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0633\u062a\u0639\u0648\u062f\u061f",
      "back": "When will you come back?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "When will you graduate?",
      "back": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u062a\u062e\u0631\u062c\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u062a\u062e\u0631\u062c\u061f",
      "back": "When will you graduate?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "When will we meet again?",
      "back": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0633\u0646\u0644\u062a\u0642\u064a \u0645\u0631\u0629 \u0623\u062e\u0631\u0649\u061f",
      "back": "When will we meet again?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I have homework.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641",
      "back": "I have homework.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Are you ready to do the homework?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f \u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f \u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "back": "Are you ready to do the homework?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You have to finish the homework before the deadline.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641 \u0642\u0628\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641 \u0642\u0628\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "back": "You have to finish the homework before the deadline.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I have homework.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641",
      "back": "I have homework.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Are you ready to do the homework?",
      "back": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f \u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0644 \u0623\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0633\u062a\u0639\u062f \u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "back": "Are you ready to do the homework?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "You have to finish the homework before the deadline.",
      "back": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641 \u0642\u0628\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0644\u064a\u0643 \u0623\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641 \u0642\u0628\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0639\u062f",
      "back": "You have to finish the homework before the deadline.",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Will you go to school tomorrow?",
      "back": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629 \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u0631\u0633\u0629 \u063a\u062f\u064b\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Will you go to school tomorrow?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Will you go to work today?",
      "back": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u064a\u0648\u0645\u061f",
      "back": "Will you go to work today?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Will you go to the city?",
      "back": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062f\u064a\u0646\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Will you go to the city?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " here",
      "back": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "back": " here",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " good",
      "back": "\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "back": " good",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I will pay",
      "back": "\u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "back": " I will pay",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " what",
      "back": "\u0627\u0634",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0634",
      "back": " what",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " cash",
      "back": "\u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "back": " cash",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "back": " I",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I want",
      "back": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632",
      "back": " I want",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I sing",
      "back": "\u0623\u063a\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u063a\u0646",
      "back": " I sing",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " the song",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629",
      "back": " the song",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " can",
      "back": "\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "back": " can",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " you can",
      "back": "\u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "back": " you can",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " work",
      "back": "\u0634\u063a\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0634\u063a\u0644",
      "back": " work",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " you work",
      "back": "\u062a\u0634\u063a\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0634\u063a\u0644",
      "back": " you work",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " air conditioner",
      "back": "\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "back": " air conditioner",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " the air conditioner",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "back": " the air conditioner",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I will be able to",
      "back": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "back": " I will be able to",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " to pay",
      "back": "\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "back": " to pay",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I pay",
      "back": "\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "back": " I pay",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " visa",
      "back": "\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "back": " visa",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " with a visa",
      "back": "\u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "back": " with a visa",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " understood",
      "back": "\u0641\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0641\u0627",
      "back": " understood",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " understanding",
      "back": "\u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645",
      "back": " understanding",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " Arabs",
      "back": "\u0639\u0631\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0631\u0628",
      "back": " Arabs",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " my car",
      "back": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a",
      "back": " my car",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " bad (masculine)",
      "back": "\u0633\u064a\u0626",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u064a\u0626",
      "back": " bad (masculine)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " bad (feminine)",
      "back": "\u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "back": " bad (feminine)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " very",
      "back": "\u062c\u062f\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062c\u062f\u0627",
      "back": " very",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " very",
      "back": "\u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "back": " very",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " you're welcome",
      "back": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u0627",
      "back": " you're welcome",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " you're welcome",
      "back": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627",
      "back": " you're welcome",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " to learn",
      "back": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "back": " to learn",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I am learning",
      "back": "\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "back": " I am learning",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " Arabic (language)",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "back": " Arabic (language)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " to repeat",
      "back": "\u0643\u0631\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u0631\u0631",
      "back": " to repeat",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " you repeat it",
      "back": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627",
      "back": " you repeat it",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " to speak",
      "back": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "back": " to speak",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " you speak",
      "back": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "back": " you speak",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " slowly",
      "back": "\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "back": " slowly",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " slowly",
      "back": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "back": " slowly",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " remain",
      "back": "\u0636\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0636\u0644",
      "back": " remain",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " please",
      "back": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "back": " please",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " say",
      "back": "\u0642\u0648\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0642\u0648\u0644",
      "back": " say",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " you say it",
      "back": "\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627",
      "back": " you say it",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " English",
      "back": "\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632",
      "back": " English",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " in English",
      "back": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "back": " in English",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " you speak",
      "back": "\u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "back": " you speak",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " English (adjective)",
      "back": "\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a",
      "back": " English (adjective)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " what",
      "back": "\u0625\u064a\u0647",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u064a\u0647",
      "back": " what",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " in Arabic",
      "back": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "back": " in Arabic",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " someone",
      "back": "\u062d\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062d\u062f",
      "back": " someone",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " one",
      "back": "\u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f",
      "back": " one",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " self",
      "back": "\u0646\u0641\u0633",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u0641\u0633",
      "back": " self",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " thing",
      "back": "\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "back": " thing",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " the thing",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "back": " the thing",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " hey",
      "back": "\u064a\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0627",
      "back": " hey",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " for me",
      "back": "\u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "back": " for me",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " vegetarian (masculine)",
      "back": "\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a",
      "back": " vegetarian (masculine)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " vegetarian (feminine)",
      "back": "\u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a",
      "back": " vegetarian (feminine)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " at",
      "back": "\u0639\u0646\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0646\u062f",
      "back": " at",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " you have",
      "back": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643",
      "back": " you have",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " list",
      "back": "\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645",
      "back": " list",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " the list",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "back": " the list",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " hot (masculine)",
      "back": "\u062d\u0627\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062d\u0627\u0631",
      "back": " hot (masculine)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " hot (feminine)",
      "back": "\u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "back": " hot (feminine)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " very",
      "back": "\u062a\u064a\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u064a\u0631",
      "back": " very",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " a lot",
      "back": "\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631",
      "back": " a lot",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " two (masculine)",
      "back": "\u0625\u062a\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u062a\u0646",
      "back": " two (masculine)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " two (feminine)",
      "back": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646",
      "back": " two (feminine)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " coffee",
      "back": "\u0642\u0647\u0648",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0642\u0647\u0648",
      "back": " coffee",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " coffee",
      "back": "\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "back": " coffee",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " leave",
      "back": "\u062a\u0631\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0631\u0643",
      "back": " leave",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " Turkish",
      "back": "\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629",
      "back": " Turkish",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " light (masculine)",
      "back": "\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641",
      "back": " light (masculine)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " light (feminine)",
      "back": "\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "back": " light (feminine)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " what",
      "back": "\u0634\u0648",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0634\u0648",
      "back": " what",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " a little",
      "back": "\u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "back": " a little",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " sugar",
      "back": "\u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "back": " sugar",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " card",
      "back": "\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642",
      "back": " card",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " with a card",
      "back": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "back": " with a card",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " bill",
      "back": "\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631",
      "back": " bill",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " the bill",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "back": " the bill",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " every",
      "back": "\u0643\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u0644",
      "back": " every",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " food",
      "back": "\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "back": " food",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "",
      "back": "(\u0641\u062d\u0635",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(\u0641\u062d\u0635",
      "back": "",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "",
      "back": "\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646)",
      "back": "",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " (security)",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646)",
      "back": " (security)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " thing",
      "back": "\u062d\u0627\u062c",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062d\u0627\u062c",
      "back": " thing",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " thing",
      "back": "\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629",
      "back": " thing",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " okay",
      "back": "\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "back": " okay",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " okay",
      "back": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "back": " okay",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " just",
      "back": "\u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f",
      "back": " just",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " remain",
      "back": "\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "back": " remain",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " here you go",
      "back": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "back": " here you go",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "",
      "back": "(\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "back": "",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "",
      "back": "\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629)",
      "back": "",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " (swimming)",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629)",
      "back": " (swimming)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " which",
      "back": "\u0623\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u064a",
      "back": " which",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " what",
      "back": "\u0623\u064a\u0647",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u064a\u0647",
      "back": " what",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " places",
      "back": "\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646",
      "back": " places",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " the places",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646",
      "back": " the places",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " empty",
      "back": "\u0641\u0627\u0636",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0641\u0627\u0636",
      "back": " empty",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " the empty ones",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "back": " the empty ones",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " until",
      "back": "\u0644\u062d\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u062d\u062f",
      "back": " until",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " when",
      "back": "\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "back": " when",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " open",
      "back": "\u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d",
      "back": " open",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " bring",
      "back": "\u062c\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062c\u0628",
      "back": " bring",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " my duty",
      "back": "\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "back": " my duty",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " duty",
      "back": "\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628",
      "back": " duty",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " rooms",
      "back": "\u063a\u0631\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u063a\u0631\u0641",
      "back": " rooms",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " the room",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "back": " the room",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " where",
      "back": "\u064a\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0646",
      "back": " where",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " where",
      "back": "\u0641\u064a\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0641\u064a\u0646",
      "back": " where",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " need",
      "back": "\u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "back": " need",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " bathroom",
      "back": "\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "back": " bathroom",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " the bathroom",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "back": " the bathroom",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " morning",
      "back": "\u0635\u0628\u062d",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0635\u0628\u062d",
      "back": " morning",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " you become",
      "back": "\u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d",
      "back": " you become",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " on",
      "back": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "back": " on",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " goodness",
      "back": "\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "back": " goodness",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " how",
      "back": "\u0625\u0632",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0632",
      "back": " how",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " how are you",
      "back": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643",
      "back": " how are you",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " fine",
      "back": "\u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "back": " fine",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " good",
      "back": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "back": " good",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " live",
      "back": "\u062a\u0633",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0633",
      "back": " live",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " you live",
      "back": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646",
      "back": " you live",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " Cairo (the capital of Egypt)",
      "back": "\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631",
      "back": " Cairo (the capital of Egypt)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " Cairo (the capital of Egypt)",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "back": " Cairo (the capital of Egypt)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " pleased to meet you",
      "back": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641",
      "back": " pleased to meet you",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " pleased to meet you (response)",
      "back": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a",
      "back": " pleased to meet you (response)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " know",
      "back": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641",
      "back": " know",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " with your knowledge",
      "back": "\u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643",
      "back": " with your knowledge",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " name",
      "back": "\u0625\u0633\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0633\u0645",
      "back": " name",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " your name",
      "back": "\u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643",
      "back": " your name",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " cost",
      "back": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641",
      "back": " cost",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " cost",
      "back": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629",
      "back": " cost",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " remember",
      "back": "\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631",
      "back": " remember",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " ticket",
      "back": "\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629",
      "back": " ticket",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " to",
      "back": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "back": " to",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " with",
      "back": "\u0627\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0645",
      "back": " with",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " how much",
      "back": "\u0643\u0627\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u0627\u0645",
      "back": " how much",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " lesson",
      "back": "\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "back": " lesson",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I study",
      "back": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "back": " I study",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " mosque",
      "back": "\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639",
      "back": " mosque",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " university",
      "back": "\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "back": " university",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " Egypt",
      "back": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "back": " Egypt",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " Egyptian (feminine)",
      "back": "\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629",
      "back": " Egyptian (feminine)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " bring",
      "back": "\u062c\u064a\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062c\u064a\u0628",
      "back": " bring",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I bring",
      "back": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628",
      "back": " I bring",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " price",
      "back": "\u0633\u0639\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u0639\u0631",
      "back": " price",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " bus",
      "back": "\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "back": " bus",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " the bus",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "back": " the bus",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " it goes",
      "back": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "back": " it goes",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " it goes",
      "back": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "back": " it goes",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " tired",
      "back": "\u0645\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u062a",
      "back": " tired",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I slept",
      "back": "\u0646\u0645\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u0645\u062a",
      "back": " I slept",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " eat",
      "back": "\u062a\u0627\u0643\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0627\u0643\u0644",
      "back": " eat",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " this",
      "back": "\u062f\u0647",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062f\u0647",
      "back": " this",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " we want",
      "back": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646",
      "back": " we want",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " have lunch",
      "back": "\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "back": " have lunch",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " we have lunch",
      "back": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "back": " we have lunch",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " that",
      "back": "\u0625\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0646",
      "back": " that",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " you",
      "back": "\u0625\u0646\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0646\u062a",
      "back": " you",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " hungry",
      "back": "\u062c\u0648\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062c\u0648\u0639",
      "back": " hungry",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " hungry",
      "back": "\u062c\u0648\u0639\u0627\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062c\u0648\u0639\u0627\u0646",
      "back": " hungry",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " let",
      "back": "\u062e\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062e\u0644",
      "back": " let",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " you let me",
      "back": "\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a",
      "back": " you let me",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " go down",
      "back": "\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "back": " go down",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I get off",
      "back": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "back": " I get off",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " stop",
      "back": "\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "back": " stop",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " you stop",
      "back": "\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641",
      "back": " you stop",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " about me",
      "back": "\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "back": " about me",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " it means",
      "back": "\u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a",
      "back": " it means",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " Arabic",
      "back": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a",
      "back": " Arabic",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I didn't understand",
      "back": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634",
      "back": " I didn't understand",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " pleasing",
      "back": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628",
      "back": " pleasing",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I like",
      "back": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a",
      "back": " I like",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " music",
      "back": "\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642",
      "back": " music",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " your music",
      "back": "\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643",
      "back": " your music",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " acceptable",
      "back": "\u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644",
      "back": " acceptable",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I will go down",
      "back": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644",
      "back": " I will go down",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I have",
      "back": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a",
      "back": " I have",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " music",
      "back": "\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "back": " music",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " the music",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649",
      "back": " the music",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " beautiful",
      "back": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644",
      "back": " beautiful",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " beautiful (feminine)",
      "back": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "back": " beautiful (feminine)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " don't be upset",
      "back": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634",
      "back": " don't be upset",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I worked",
      "back": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a",
      "back": " I worked",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " anything",
      "back": "\u0632\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0632\u0627",
      "back": " anything",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " acceptable (feminine)",
      "back": "\u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629",
      "back": " acceptable (feminine)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " sure",
      "back": "\u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f",
      "back": " sure",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " who",
      "back": "\u0644\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u064a",
      "back": " who",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " who",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a",
      "back": " who",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " you mean",
      "back": "\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f",
      "back": " you mean",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " you mean it",
      "back": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647",
      "back": " you mean it",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " sorry",
      "back": "\u0622\u0633\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0622\u0633\u0641",
      "back": " sorry",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " noisy",
      "back": "\u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634",
      "back": " noisy",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " good (feminine)",
      "back": "\u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "back": " good (feminine)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " look for",
      "back": "\u062f\u0648\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062f\u0648\u0631",
      "back": " look for",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " course",
      "back": "\u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "back": " course",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " how",
      "back": "\u0631\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0631\u0631",
      "back": " how",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " how",
      "back": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a",
      "back": " how",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " translate",
      "back": "\u0631\u062c\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0631\u062c\u0645",
      "back": " translate",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I translate",
      "back": "\u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645",
      "back": " I translate",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " meaning",
      "back": "\u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649",
      "back": " meaning",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " (the restaurant)",
      "back": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645)",
      "back": " (the restaurant)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " the",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u0640",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u0640",
      "back": " the",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " (the food)",
      "back": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645)",
      "back": " (the food)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " made",
      "back": "\u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644",
      "back": " made",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " meat",
      "back": "\u062d\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062d\u0645",
      "back": " meat",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " meat",
      "back": "\u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0644\u062d\u0645",
      "back": " meat",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " delicious",
      "back": "\u0645\u0645",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0645",
      "back": " delicious",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " possible",
      "back": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646",
      "back": " possible",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " tea",
      "back": "\u0634\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0634\u0627",
      "back": " tea",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " tea",
      "back": "\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0634\u0627\u064a",
      "back": " tea",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " black",
      "back": "\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "back": " black",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " black (feminine)",
      "back": "\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f",
      "back": " black (feminine)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " mint",
      "back": "\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "back": " mint",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " with mint",
      "back": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639",
      "back": " with mint",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I am full",
      "back": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639",
      "back": " I am full",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I am full",
      "back": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a",
      "back": " I am full",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " action",
      "back": "\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "back": " action",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " indeed",
      "back": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644",
      "back": " indeed",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " we take",
      "back": "\u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f",
      "back": " we take",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " tomorrow",
      "back": "\u063a\u062f\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u063a\u062f\u0627",
      "back": " tomorrow",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " present",
      "back": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644",
      "back": " present",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " I present to you",
      "back": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643",
      "back": " I present to you",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " new",
      "back": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f",
      "back": " new",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " the new one",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "back": " the new one",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " exhausted",
      "back": "\u0639\u0628",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0639\u0628",
      "back": " exhausted",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " exhausted (masculine)",
      "back": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646",
      "back": " exhausted (masculine)",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " and you",
      "back": "\u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a",
      "back": " and you",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " morning",
      "back": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "back": " morning",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " goodness",
      "back": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "back": " goodness",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " it closes",
      "back": "\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644",
      "back": " it closes",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " it closes",
      "back": "\u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644",
      "back": " it closes",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " when",
      "back": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "back": " when",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " cliff",
      "back": "\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641",
      "back": " cliff",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " assignment",
      "back": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641",
      "back": " assignment",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " you will go",
      "back": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "\u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "back": " you will go",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following word:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you let me out here?",
      "back": " \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u062a\u062e\u0644\u064a\u0646\u064a \u0623\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Can you let me out here?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can you stop here?",
      "back": " \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u062a\u0648\u0642\u0641 \u0647\u0646\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Can you stop here?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What does ... mean?",
      "back": " ... \u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " ... \u064a\u0639\u0646\u064a \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "back": "What does ... mean?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Could you repeat that in English?",
      "back": " \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Could you repeat that in English?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I study Arabic",
      "back": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a",
      "back": "I study Arabic",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I didn't get that",
      "back": " \u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0645\u0641\u0647\u0645\u062a\u0634",
      "back": "I didn't get that",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I like your music",
      "back": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a \u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u062c\u0628\u0646\u064a \u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0627\u0643",
      "back": "I like your music",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I would like to pay cash",
      "back": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "back": "I would like to pay cash",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Is cash ok?",
      "back": " \u0643\u0627\u0634 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0643\u0627\u0634 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u061f",
      "back": "Is cash ok?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I will get out here",
      "back": " \u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0647\u0646\u0632\u0644 \u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "back": "I will get out here",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I have cash",
      "back": " \u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "back": "I have cash",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "The music is great",
      "back": " \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0642\u0649 \u062c\u0645\u064a\u0644\u0629",
      "back": "The music is great",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Do you mind turning on the AC?",
      "back": " \u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634 \u0644\u0648 \u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u062a\u0632\u0639\u0644\u0634 \u0644\u0648 \u0634\u063a\u0644\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "back": "Do you mind turning on the AC?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Is VISA ok?",
      "back": " \u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Is VISA ok?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am not sure what you mean",
      "back": " \u0645\u0634 \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a \u0625\u0646\u062a \u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0645\u0634 \u0645\u062a\u0623\u0643\u062f \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a \u0625\u0646\u062a \u0628\u062a\u0642\u0635\u062f\u0647",
      "back": "I am not sure what you mean",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Sorry, I am confused",
      "back": " \u0622\u0633\u0641\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0622\u0633\u0641\u060c \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u0634\u0648\u0634",
      "back": "Sorry, I am confused",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "My Arabic is not good",
      "back": " \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a \u0645\u0634 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a \u0645\u0634 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u0629",
      "back": "My Arabic is not good",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Sorry",
      "back": " \u0622\u0633\u0641",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0622\u0633\u0641",
      "back": "Sorry",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I am taking an Arabic course",
      "back": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u062f\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a",
      "back": "I am taking an Arabic course",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Repeat, please",
      "back": " \u0643\u0631\u0631\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0643\u0631\u0631\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "back": "Repeat, please",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "A bit slower, please",
      "back": " \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621 \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "back": "A bit slower, please",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What is that in English?",
      "back": " \u0625\u064a\u0647 \u062f\u0647 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0625\u064a\u0647 \u062f\u0647 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "What is that in English?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "How do I translate ... ?",
      "back": " \u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 ... \u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0625\u0632\u0627\u064a \u0623\u062a\u0631\u062c\u0645 ... \u061f",
      "back": "How do I translate ... ?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "What is the meaning of ... ?",
      "back": " \u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649 ... \u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0645\u0639\u0646\u0649 ... \u061f",
      "back": "What is the meaning of ... ?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I would like the ...",
      "back": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 ...",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 ...",
      "back": "I would like the ...",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(Restaurant) For me, the ...",
      "back": " (\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645) \u0644\u064a\u0627\u060c \u0627\u0644\u0640...",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " (\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0637\u0639\u0645) \u0644\u064a\u0627\u060c \u0627\u0644\u0640...",
      "back": "(Restaurant) For me, the ...",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I want the same",
      "back": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "back": "I want the same",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(Food) What is this made of?",
      "back": " (\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645) \u062f\u0647 \u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644 \u0645\u0646 \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " (\u0627\u0644\u0637\u0639\u0627\u0645) \u062f\u0647 \u0645\u0639\u0645\u0648\u0644 \u0645\u0646 \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "back": "(Food) What is this made of?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Is this meat?",
      "back": " \u062f\u0647 \u0644\u062d\u0645\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u062f\u0647 \u0644\u062d\u0645\u061f",
      "back": "Is this meat?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Could I have ... ?",
      "back": " \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 ...",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 ...",
      "back": "Could I have ... ?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I'd like the menu",
      "back": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "back": "I'd like the menu",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Not too spicy for me",
      "back": " \u0645\u0634 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0645\u0634 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631 \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "back": "Not too spicy for me",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "One black tea with mint, please",
      "back": " \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f \u0634\u0627\u064a \u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f \u0634\u0627\u064a \u0623\u0633\u0648\u062f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0639\u0646\u0627\u0639\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "back": "One black tea with mint, please",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Is VISA alright?",
      "back": " \u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627 \u0645\u0642\u0628\u0648\u0644\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Is VISA alright?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I want to pay",
      "back": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "back": "I want to pay",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "(Security Check) All good?",
      "back": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u0643\u0644 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u0643\u0644 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "back": "(Security Check) All good?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Are you full already?",
      "back": " \u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0627\u062a\u0634\u0628\u0639\u062a \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0639\u0644\u061f",
      "back": "Are you full already?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Should we get lunch?",
      "back": " \u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f \u063a\u062f\u0627\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0646\u0627\u062e\u062f \u063a\u062f\u0627\u061f",
      "back": "Should we get lunch?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Can I offer you some?",
      "back": " \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u0623\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "back": "Can I offer you some?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Are you from New Cairo?",
      "back": " \u0625\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0625\u0646\u062a \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062c\u062f\u064a\u062f\u0629\u061f",
      "back": "Are you from New Cairo?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I'm a bit tired, and you?",
      "back": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646\u060c \u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u062a\u0639\u0628\u0627\u0646\u060c \u0648\u0625\u0646\u062a\u061f",
      "back": "I'm a bit tired, and you?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Good morning",
      "back": " \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "back": "Good morning",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "When does it close?",
      "back": " \u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0628\u064a\u0642\u0641\u0644 \u0625\u0645\u062a\u0649\u061f",
      "back": "When does it close?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "This is my homework",
      "back": " \u062f\u0647 \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u062f\u0647 \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "back": "This is my homework",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Is there an assignment?",
      "back": " \u0641\u064a \u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0641\u064a \u062a\u0643\u0644\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "back": "Is there an assignment?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "I can't find room ...",
      "back": null,
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": null,
      "back": "I can't find room ...",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": "Are you going to ... ?",
      "back": " \u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 ... \u061f",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    },
    {
      "id": "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb",
      "front": " \u0647\u062a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 ... \u061f",
      "back": "Are you going to ... ?",
      "type": "flashcard",
      "prompt": "Translate the following sentence:"
    }
  ],
  "mainSentences": [
    {
      "id": "2f7b4b0c-a8ee-4b3c-9495-ec7148e766c6",
      "english": "Here is good",
      "arabic": " \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "children": [
        "ee9801f3-ed70-4673-8a5a-0b0149ba9d65",
        "f56d2698-502f-4367-8596-0c4e245ffb5a",
        "33727ac4-fe07-4081-8dd6-eb032efa07da",
        "b25895af-e5dd-4766-9c5e-80902e4f23a7",
        "0918dea6-14b5-4b2b-85b9-e2c3348c6a20",
        "6bd08208-edaa-4206-a918-f72a5cbdb70e",
        "6ecb1dbd-a6d1-4c48-9b10-9546dac49a52",
        "75147d3f-59d6-457c-a796-7a48ab82f299",
        "2a8ce45c-ca5c-4d5b-b4e4-61eefab1b5d4",
        "a28c4f10-a39e-4606-b4d0-671a375ab7d8",
        "7a2cda7b-741c-4f49-98fe-98a3070d756f",
        "bdc85176-e307-4056-8a6b-0a3e3e927306",
        "2ad764d5-7f92-4c81-b443-ec1900abe922",
        "50bb47cf-6e5f-4953-99dd-9d4f6132d0a3",
        "b8869142-c92a-4e4e-b705-d3387a64275a",
        "ae1277d6-6a6e-4e81-8326-98599e8aa3be",
        "7b470174-c8e4-42f1-9bea-5374c4c2bc15",
        "39b8a586-65b1-4b08-b5d8-74b5871e4b8a",
        "88876ae0-1761-4b84-b9d6-7410862813e0",
        "3c2fe989-0d8f-49e1-be31-6c37b4debacb",
        "85160bf7-9c01-4779-8805-1fef39daa1c1",
        "7101af0e-6810-4d17-9c8a-382567e63e36",
        "a932c393-2152-4a5f-8dbf-87e139b7c8b8",
        "5052d96e-a0b7-4ed7-b618-0699e3b70093",
        "e5171ffb-3778-4773-bea7-c280e0b66cde",
        "52a48a73-7c73-4048-bffe-62fc692a0c93",
        "e9ba383d-b737-44c2-82a4-efcb9fff0fc5",
        "d4bbc963-0140-4ab7-9c12-629ef79e4746",
        "9a65dc39-d79f-49d9-9826-747929354839",
        "b0f9e9f0-37e2-467f-b89e-45f255cc26ba",
        "589a2793-5550-4b5d-8019-a054ae205a57",
        "68cd7737-591d-4d88-b20b-0759d757133b",
        "a069585f-26f4-4704-994a-3b7c7fb1156e",
        "929f96e9-d46e-44ad-9664-68875e2df1ee",
        "4ae3ee16-8982-40c0-a6de-c034dcbe843f",
        "07378735-11ef-4ae7-872d-f33555ae1d22",
        "81e0234c-0ffa-47d7-98ce-99881248089b",
        "45c19c74-5e2b-4b7c-a344-f4cb25ab117e",
        "a6b09abb-8084-4528-a1f7-85b58085b875",
        "0053feb2-6a3f-4685-852f-21c38fa588f0",
        "08cd324f-ea04-4a68-94df-9096d8f38dee",
        "304dcec1-7cf7-4415-803a-8e4e376f2116",
        "a63b28ae-9b5c-47cb-9e51-7c908c9c8cd8",
        "e2828dac-2847-44a1-a10f-a9e9c8d6512d",
        "a51494fa-69f9-40a9-9fc0-63fa58b8dc1f",
        "93f1f46d-fe60-4db9-8ed8-a8e799828c18",
        "77cb7e1e-7d1d-44f2-b429-cefc9685ad46",
        "d4ade86c-d60a-447c-ba8a-fb3808588cba",
        "f40bac4d-6fc3-4e88-bcc8-271c51b8baa7",
        "6d876a92-1a46-400b-b275-723d424fab1d",
        "7e66f80b-b3a6-4fb5-8466-b058b2616996",
        "fabe7078-526a-4776-99c8-a3a0506ec250",
        "bbdef1f3-e997-469c-b0e0-c23c08e3e7b6",
        "5848acb5-0b32-433e-9c9f-9e005289884f",
        "33611c29-aa22-4521-975a-16f19232714c",
        "a9b80ae4-1188-4645-921b-5a1ad59cfb63",
        "150d8044-5919-4e8e-aab3-e943962c762d",
        "c71c0818-73a2-4a94-82ed-fe4297a0b2ba",
        "43cfb368-6a2f-47a1-9865-b9d4e0524aa5",
        "d1972f34-917e-4c05-b8f7-cab576728219",
        "683c9f1b-21dc-488b-bc91-e2473c3940f8",
        "9342f087-fe12-4502-a496-c9adf4ce3b69",
        "a825d5fa-d695-4f88-ba5c-eb9b759bf620",
        "cd0095f3-61f3-443f-8a60-27d120217f5b",
        "c95e277e-aaa2-4ece-a5c0-61577bd3f12e",
        "fdbd3543-dfcd-4a38-894f-c44f78ea5124",
        "8ebd48cc-9c47-4ef4-8b3c-e6126ff98550",
        "33a50d3a-47eb-42bf-b6bf-a679c1bd0bbf",
        "27a1e70b-8a85-4e24-b265-f7dc4fadbf55",
        "adb3834f-5a5c-4389-b181-1f0c50f34247",
        "6372979d-0ff3-4081-9f14-67d852dc1dd0",
        "1d69599e-82e1-49b8-b4a2-d8111b6cd71f",
        "007142e8-7fdf-467e-8aba-d88b17d2e03a",
        "45e006de-e7bd-4f76-a3d7-e7b9a0cab1b4",
        "7cd40e88-3426-484b-927f-4466e3010637",
        "8731b15b-4493-434f-b4ea-0ab23ec4d0c4",
        "ba6fcc24-173d-4687-8576-e2d5f3427013",
        "026a7924-89db-46a2-b15f-2a204580d7ca",
        "e30cdf7e-d374-455f-bf8c-857e498b96e4",
        "d43483a7-cb9e-4dcf-82d7-f52578078f38",
        "7272690b-6c42-44bb-b725-c9124d91a851",
        "8e446d1b-47ad-4e08-8e3b-020c054f28cc",
        "f03b1dce-b5c0-4ce5-bb2f-cf6cc7b34b00",
        "e2f92aff-f3a1-4579-b205-2334ab393672",
        "223f020a-414d-4168-a703-4d3f23e861b0",
        "fbea475f-c147-4dc5-a1e4-a061db7b2ead",
        "6107962b-b4a0-4a6b-9054-05de1790fbe4",
        "a6fea985-fa37-4a2c-bc25-8298da186b11",
        "a710c24f-2a50-4b51-8e1d-1b7e278855d4",
        "f602d119-5c58-42b3-a39e-1f342437a016",
        "76f88ad6-0611-4628-9adb-dacd17651c34",
        "512fa555-f312-4cba-9c26-14003be70a97",
        "c488a39d-5bf0-4b89-8b7c-89858251d3f0",
        "405dddf3-1ddd-401a-8ab3-69c88e17e842",
        "4b9f2c9a-0663-44c7-a7c3-3a202a985812",
        "5728d7aa-b2a2-4916-91d7-2eb6b096d3fa",
        "53e6c425-7789-4ba3-8f7f-6a688efdfdef",
        "ce3fd6f2-113d-4338-b885-a5a72b4c57ea",
        "f7c5fc89-8221-420f-a61a-f949089339b3",
        "5a9941d8-52c2-4fe3-af8b-9557eaf79538",
        "7aeb8b12-b633-4f46-9986-d484f66d5b6b",
        "8a4108bc-e433-480a-a964-4467c9fac26b",
        "4b85634a-59c9-476c-b312-4ea19112b64c",
        "73246712-3fa7-4857-a1be-2006c07fd7bd",
        "ccbe90c2-af5a-4242-a0f8-7d7338315646",
        "c4ccdb1e-cab4-479e-907c-ec5e47c2b532",
        "6e82efb9-f115-4a3f-b3d7-9c09fd76c9f9",
        "c87e4c90-1340-4802-9d9b-78bf14936b4e",
        "2730b9ab-fc69-4b6d-b0be-98f118baee18",
        "4a491a7d-5117-4503-bb52-0c0b817a7a7a",
        "77bfd5a8-387e-41c0-b319-6c05eac58a3f",
        "f56d2698-502f-4367-8596-0c4e245ffb5a",
        "33727ac4-fe07-4081-8dd6-eb032efa07da",
        "b25895af-e5dd-4766-9c5e-80902e4f23a7",
        "0918dea6-14b5-4b2b-85b9-e2c3348c6a20",
        "6bd08208-edaa-4206-a918-f72a5cbdb70e",
        "6ecb1dbd-a6d1-4c48-9b10-9546dac49a52",
        "75147d3f-59d6-457c-a796-7a48ab82f299",
        "2a8ce45c-ca5c-4d5b-b4e4-61eefab1b5d4",
        "a28c4f10-a39e-4606-b4d0-671a375ab7d8",
        "7a2cda7b-741c-4f49-98fe-98a3070d756f",
        "bdc85176-e307-4056-8a6b-0a3e3e927306",
        "2ad764d5-7f92-4c81-b443-ec1900abe922",
        "50bb47cf-6e5f-4953-99dd-9d4f6132d0a3",
        "b8869142-c92a-4e4e-b705-d3387a64275a",
        "ae1277d6-6a6e-4e81-8326-98599e8aa3be",
        "7b470174-c8e4-42f1-9bea-5374c4c2bc15",
        "39b8a586-65b1-4b08-b5d8-74b5871e4b8a",
        "88876ae0-1761-4b84-b9d6-7410862813e0",
        "3c2fe989-0d8f-49e1-be31-6c37b4debacb",
        "85160bf7-9c01-4779-8805-1fef39daa1c1",
        "7101af0e-6810-4d17-9c8a-382567e63e36",
        "a932c393-2152-4a5f-8dbf-87e139b7c8b8",
        "5052d96e-a0b7-4ed7-b618-0699e3b70093",
        "e5171ffb-3778-4773-bea7-c280e0b66cde",
        "52a48a73-7c73-4048-bffe-62fc692a0c93",
        "e9ba383d-b737-44c2-82a4-efcb9fff0fc5",
        "d4bbc963-0140-4ab7-9c12-629ef79e4746",
        "9a65dc39-d79f-49d9-9826-747929354839",
        "b0f9e9f0-37e2-467f-b89e-45f255cc26ba",
        "589a2793-5550-4b5d-8019-a054ae205a57",
        "68cd7737-591d-4d88-b20b-0759d757133b",
        "a069585f-26f4-4704-994a-3b7c7fb1156e",
        "929f96e9-d46e-44ad-9664-68875e2df1ee",
        "4ae3ee16-8982-40c0-a6de-c034dcbe843f",
        "07378735-11ef-4ae7-872d-f33555ae1d22",
        "81e0234c-0ffa-47d7-98ce-99881248089b",
        "45c19c74-5e2b-4b7c-a344-f4cb25ab117e",
        "a6b09abb-8084-4528-a1f7-85b58085b875",
        "244dedbc-e010-4086-9aad-e2f0c3ce7e62",
        "601e241c-e275-4def-acd1-a24d6b8bce39",
        "8b137026-9d47-455a-b2b6-3695376e7f00",
        "963ddd4a-8828-4049-ae06-34641219d1b0",
        "5bb37809-9ee8-4d08-9726-18819910d576",
        "94530930-85f0-4ce8-a2bf-7af52c5a17f7",
        "ad1bddab-bd47-427e-ba20-e9b4ee88f579",
        "0e7cedf6-3544-44b3-be76-d48312bdeb6b",
        "d6e8dd76-606a-48c1-96d0-996621423203",
        "49aab547-d058-43fe-9983-b41760618989",
        "d907e7a4-f17c-4525-8ae3-78dac2d9a6be",
        "0a27ec64-df10-45ff-bde7-b4789c9c7b6c",
        "3927b364-0c7d-4119-8d97-b2c9446a7d25",
        "138a7869-5606-468c-b7fa-673b52ed70d8",
        "ae5d46fd-d3e6-4662-909f-5b79c9fa4b57",
        "087bf831-f50b-4e1e-befe-7ee63cd7d581",
        "9f548f0a-647b-455c-bbbd-2d5f17aafedf",
        "8b618dab-2a10-46d8-b6bf-5f8ae3cd667e",
        "ee761625-1af1-42d0-b50f-1ba319565db1",
        "4b865b9b-10a6-46ea-a67c-30fa8561c88c",
        "8b28acf0-2537-4529-9c87-e6e6b59019ec",
        "34abe79a-7589-4c50-9b84-b8c6446860f1",
        "fcd75668-69f8-43b8-a8f3-3856bfe699ce",
        "37d3e88f-b37e-45a7-8e74-4237e2b63a7d",
        "ebf24193-647a-40f5-9de4-fb0bc80a30a2",
        "36177a49-0710-4dcf-9fb7-a235b38cd236",
        "a323a1df-967b-4ef2-9e5a-f076efe9cf1c",
        "e57c7d77-b3a5-474b-90df-ddbf3bb88412",
        "53e6c425-7789-4ba3-8f7f-6a688efdfdef",
        "ce3fd6f2-113d-4338-b885-a5a72b4c57ea",
        "f7c5fc89-8221-420f-a61a-f949089339b3",
        "5a9941d8-52c2-4fe3-af8b-9557eaf79538",
        "7aeb8b12-b633-4f46-9986-d484f66d5b6b",
        "8a4108bc-e433-480a-a964-4467c9fac26b",
        "4b85634a-59c9-476c-b312-4ea19112b64c",
        "73246712-3fa7-4857-a1be-2006c07fd7bd",
        "ccbe90c2-af5a-4242-a0f8-7d7338315646",
        "c4ccdb1e-cab4-479e-907c-ec5e47c2b532",
        "6e82efb9-f115-4a3f-b3d7-9c09fd76c9f9",
        "c87e4c90-1340-4802-9d9b-78bf14936b4e",
        "2730b9ab-fc69-4b6d-b0be-98f118baee18",
        "4a491a7d-5117-4503-bb52-0c0b817a7a7a",
        "9d0f031d-ba61-442e-9287-9a3bf81b5b5b",
        "30f03dd9-a2c8-4136-9c90-e9a975791e1f",
        "7059ad5e-d390-4506-b16a-e8b8d72bb20f",
        "ebd10fb1-36f4-40ff-9fe2-a9be69a505e8",
        "4309f6d8-e44d-4756-a76d-7008fc43bba2",
        "05460dac-94de-4137-bc4a-f60b3a95a5dc",
        "491d4dfb-2415-431d-8880-52f82da75458",
        "8d2b3314-78ed-4874-848f-c17e1124b8e0",
        "a62e07de-22f8-4314-b850-db8a9b4c4e14",
        "9ec9cd86-dab1-44f5-8431-394c3293af6a",
        "dc9b6e0d-f346-48b0-9f2d-b890f21fde27",
        "53e6c425-7789-4ba3-8f7f-6a688efdfdef",
        "ce3fd6f2-113d-4338-b885-a5a72b4c57ea",
        "f7c5fc89-8221-420f-a61a-f949089339b3",
        "5a9941d8-52c2-4fe3-af8b-9557eaf79538",
        "7aeb8b12-b633-4f46-9986-d484f66d5b6b",
        "8a4108bc-e433-480a-a964-4467c9fac26b",
        "4b85634a-59c9-476c-b312-4ea19112b64c",
        "73246712-3fa7-4857-a1be-2006c07fd7bd",
        "ccbe90c2-af5a-4242-a0f8-7d7338315646",
        "c4ccdb1e-cab4-479e-907c-ec5e47c2b532",
        "6e82efb9-f115-4a3f-b3d7-9c09fd76c9f9",
        "c87e4c90-1340-4802-9d9b-78bf14936b4e",
        "2730b9ab-fc69-4b6d-b0be-98f118baee18",
        "4a491a7d-5117-4503-bb52-0c0b817a7a7a"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "b204b289-1443-4e8d-8c9f-2894fa2ddca0",
      "english": "I will pay cash",
      "arabic": " \u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "children": [
        "16b0adfe-7ce4-4ddf-8610-bae7d932817e",
        "12e43bcf-53e5-46cd-b915-79c360541118",
        "a7745e5a-0b59-47c9-9f62-bad69ab673c0",
        "4b325b2e-0619-4f85-95cf-7bae7136cd70",
        "6da2c303-a1a7-4f16-89cc-3ccfa615b481",
        "c9e33926-cde9-46f9-a2c7-35aabc371bd1",
        "e2290930-2439-400e-ad37-fc41b244b746",
        "62ddf8f4-524f-40d9-9983-6eaa86a005d4",
        "05ad2b72-31a7-4242-a5dc-8e5e0e6e698a",
        "6f81e444-67b1-45e2-9d95-121c8894994d",
        "ae6f3822-1e8a-4ae3-8eaa-a339b692fccb",
        "33fce108-8e9c-4ca0-a4a4-d459d0566ce7",
        "4aaccfe3-4d20-4ea7-9eb8-dc868c019ee7",
        "19c1f66c-09fd-4adb-ab6c-4fcb73de61b9",
        "ad263a6d-d116-4c27-a822-4e7eb574077f",
        "010a7e2f-64e8-4613-817f-fd29ec7ac48c",
        "aaa5f69c-6964-49b4-94a1-d99091152ee7",
        "a33f97cb-dc13-4dbd-913c-9dd6578c002c",
        "c6936187-374d-44bb-b7fb-58cc4d278256",
        "7687c3c6-9c0b-4340-902d-d369b9f45ade",
        "37d5c2a4-1d2b-4213-b50b-8f4918ad727c",
        "6557e65c-4146-4196-a5a1-586d15ace8fa",
        "b49274d4-3e3c-4d66-af08-de0678dc32c7",
        "6d75f594-f708-4bd6-b319-8e46853cf8b8",
        "940a677c-8139-4301-8711-76cfc7fdd423",
        "6702e4f5-f4e1-400d-9a94-d0690cf353aa",
        "cb3875b9-79f5-4c73-adff-7de9cd485710",
        "2a484b5a-b823-45e3-b070-7db54eb7f8fe",
        "45574aba-a704-4518-8a68-78316b8c1d3e",
        "5a760890-d7c1-4511-a4d1-988d47ed7320",
        "3a2d9f13-8b6d-4f6c-b527-7872033548f5",
        "beca6df3-75e3-4a7f-b2cf-b3d9f404a798",
        "ebc9de4a-5b5c-4ef3-b98a-79f4f97ba346",
        "ba22a28d-88da-46c7-8236-1c7397de4084",
        "9029015a-96fa-462f-aecf-ad4f8dd7c5e1",
        "2d106bc0-5fd2-42b3-ae49-d358b62be7e3",
        "0f971e44-c1f0-4cf9-944a-35e4406c56cc",
        "83135127-c438-4864-bf44-80c3f6a76355",
        "0c205725-6e12-47c5-a0ae-81a54c42f5be",
        "c806f0c0-8493-44b0-b4e1-ea4767b0f209",
        "13151a37-3b0a-4da1-ba3b-b0036205e60d",
        "7679137c-d224-4c40-92a7-a57df36d6866",
        "f2ce7f95-dfca-48c7-becb-7f347925cad8",
        "ae2abe80-d129-4028-84c8-79b0544e91a3",
        "fa22eff9-3ea4-4f23-97c9-d2e75fcad101",
        "d903fa46-5ce9-43a0-a6d9-68aaac6137fd",
        "ab6b2d68-3783-4ddf-8499-751f7d7242f6",
        "080ce7a0-0901-4ee7-ad58-5eed90e1cf4f",
        "859fdaa1-005e-4e50-a8e9-2ee6f44844b5",
        "b1236dd6-66fe-4290-a64a-385c71a2a423",
        "a194a149-5d9c-45df-9efe-80f571c7bed8",
        "13ca5d84-6cb9-4726-9aec-a8c9b84916cb",
        "ec99b1d7-a9bb-42d9-8f59-6f675ace2b1c",
        "ecc792a7-5069-4dd0-80e2-bc7d61a56e6d",
        "93bd9a0e-ef6e-4dfb-8199-792dd072c191",
        "6157bead-6cbd-42bf-85fe-dc355b938efb",
        "4c8ed226-2739-432b-b2ed-1e80d55090dc",
        "b12e1853-6546-4c35-b095-c2d1f99089dd",
        "8709e304-23c5-4ed3-a877-f764af3a4779",
        "a916bd29-bf6b-41ca-94e1-832297eeeb58",
        "32de6ab5-061a-4868-8927-c561cf0cd445",
        "e0aec2f2-26b8-4d5b-a989-c0bfd87867a3",
        "b96bdfcf-44e4-4557-9762-1bf3d884296e",
        "6aa88b19-5bf3-41c6-9b62-81e5a94c662d",
        "f513aa1b-fba3-49d6-bfa7-6605cbe1ee01",
        "76383f23-27b9-4300-b591-d8ab13b2ef9e",
        "6ffc63d6-efd3-43dd-a992-4b2517a489a7",
        "dfd5cb3f-29bc-4d8a-8b6c-e9a9904717a7",
        "feb5ff31-be79-4a6f-9d93-27d5f78ffda8",
        "721a18f2-f8ae-4f19-81b2-a892d9a3aca5",
        "db85c36e-cdc0-495a-a7f2-4bb661723102",
        "c6a8423d-5bb8-4502-8c2e-ccf2d3467ffd",
        "88d8f12c-9ee4-4eac-8e27-f6844a637d9b",
        "3f0b73c0-5767-4e94-acdf-59af90be11f6",
        "2efdebde-2e7d-4c68-a46c-b11cf13a67a8",
        "e13f423e-7c12-4173-9e5a-ff450865bb25",
        "3bc63edd-8b24-440f-939f-d9edef16a095",
        "d60a7310-07ba-4b53-9cd1-6314d06d0bbf",
        "ede19c22-8844-4695-90bb-a53a654a3cbd",
        "d8d13212-d305-449d-a495-38d7d1aff885",
        "24ec1b39-2569-4274-9235-fb45adcbcbb1",
        "79d8155c-862a-422e-adb3-1369453ede23",
        "e63f1fcc-3151-4310-b4f3-e7aea9ba0470",
        "f145eda6-4514-496c-8f2c-248a04b528c4",
        "6a5dfbc2-458f-478b-897f-00c50ad0637e",
        "a916bd29-bf6b-41ca-94e1-832297eeeb58",
        "32de6ab5-061a-4868-8927-c561cf0cd445",
        "e0aec2f2-26b8-4d5b-a989-c0bfd87867a3",
        "b96bdfcf-44e4-4557-9762-1bf3d884296e",
        "6aa88b19-5bf3-41c6-9b62-81e5a94c662d",
        "f513aa1b-fba3-49d6-bfa7-6605cbe1ee01",
        "76383f23-27b9-4300-b591-d8ab13b2ef9e",
        "6ffc63d6-efd3-43dd-a992-4b2517a489a7",
        "dfd5cb3f-29bc-4d8a-8b6c-e9a9904717a7",
        "feb5ff31-be79-4a6f-9d93-27d5f78ffda8",
        "721a18f2-f8ae-4f19-81b2-a892d9a3aca5",
        "db85c36e-cdc0-495a-a7f2-4bb661723102",
        "c6a8423d-5bb8-4502-8c2e-ccf2d3467ffd",
        "88d8f12c-9ee4-4eac-8e27-f6844a637d9b",
        "3f0b73c0-5767-4e94-acdf-59af90be11f6",
        "2efdebde-2e7d-4c68-a46c-b11cf13a67a8",
        "e13f423e-7c12-4173-9e5a-ff450865bb25",
        "3bc63edd-8b24-440f-939f-d9edef16a095",
        "d60a7310-07ba-4b53-9cd1-6314d06d0bbf",
        "ede19c22-8844-4695-90bb-a53a654a3cbd",
        "d8d13212-d305-449d-a495-38d7d1aff885",
        "24ec1b39-2569-4274-9235-fb45adcbcbb1",
        "79d8155c-862a-422e-adb3-1369453ede23",
        "e63f1fcc-3151-4310-b4f3-e7aea9ba0470",
        "f145eda6-4514-496c-8f2c-248a04b528c4",
        "2d7db614-3240-4bb1-8986-820d68062a89",
        "a5b01e8b-41fb-499c-beab-2a842c2a0352",
        "5a468a01-6269-436d-88f2-8d92407a0d10",
        "c9f1ba78-9ba1-4537-91da-666e146851f0",
        "9480a08e-edc0-4505-8746-2aca978150f2",
        "cf128f85-06f0-408e-8538-db391fc7b3a2",
        "581ef9ef-29ff-4a18-9aa6-4761899504a3",
        "cbf4b3b0-ce73-4ea9-bf6d-ed311f22ddd9",
        "d36aecd5-13d0-4494-be24-50a33c437a03",
        "621f6e88-7c82-4cbc-ba57-f3f6511990f2",
        "6f7b3286-bdb7-4571-86b5-7f5c291d683c",
        "40145da4-a294-4a8a-a8bf-94db09efbde7",
        "fcc4b8fd-5e8f-4e0b-91b7-ff2238a8d09a",
        "5ac5878a-7f8d-4fa8-a9c1-1e20aeac5034",
        "b78f3dc3-6319-4d72-8f30-97cf020e9826",
        "397ea277-756f-416d-a7a7-4ede3ca36e6e",
        "c4c80c47-8797-4a81-9545-d3d09fbd7a57",
        "a84ca763-d965-4bd2-b761-911678641652",
        "9f25d846-f35b-4b9a-ac45-6ae59e403d9e",
        "ef28929c-9ec9-4102-930c-a9cc7f03c61f",
        "53f5c10b-90a7-458e-ada3-c3e4e3bd6702",
        "2e115027-cbc0-4bde-a6ea-f9e7c6cc589c",
        "f53469ba-5949-4114-b68c-9a3844d1482b",
        "e6fbae4d-4674-4498-85ee-c1191e56787f",
        "f24e2386-6515-464a-8a09-24e4a3a5032a",
        "e8839639-c4fd-4fb0-b756-f3973985a6ff",
        "c75a1b19-5876-4b23-a099-83e97ff58df3",
        "cdb6151d-acf0-4b88-bbec-77f9cc43e36a",
        "8fabd909-ecf7-4bc8-b05b-4db39f5d14e9",
        "ef4920a9-5697-46f5-8d3c-5d8aa93edd5f",
        "70a7b5ec-41d8-42ea-8a90-8c11bac5eeec",
        "d6d76ac9-89f2-45d8-b165-70b9f0a6f218",
        "7e2d9831-190b-4926-98bc-e93c93e0ade1",
        "32fc7bcd-1483-4c1a-b391-75ac3ecdf065",
        "e3824cf0-8663-4ed4-9afd-832b5aa0ccea",
        "6fa5b755-15ad-4a43-81dd-685ddf8d0cc1",
        "5ca1d6f1-22b2-4d19-9f3c-368b3edaa48a",
        "b0021485-c035-4d56-a2a9-9ebcf9d89d3e",
        "ad8b8c04-ebb1-4955-add5-2ce6a6bf0ee8",
        "c815cdc5-8bc5-4aa9-b75d-230aaa1a595f",
        "6ecc5d81-e47d-4840-a380-05d7711b66d5",
        "1dbf1bef-aa22-4880-be07-88547873575d",
        "cbec221a-17ef-4f48-8115-56e08a9881bc",
        "de047692-b084-40cc-bc98-01c750a30725",
        "b2b14ffc-f07a-416c-803f-592c41bf6aab",
        "a916bd29-bf6b-41ca-94e1-832297eeeb58",
        "32de6ab5-061a-4868-8927-c561cf0cd445",
        "e0aec2f2-26b8-4d5b-a989-c0bfd87867a3",
        "b96bdfcf-44e4-4557-9762-1bf3d884296e",
        "6aa88b19-5bf3-41c6-9b62-81e5a94c662d",
        "f513aa1b-fba3-49d6-bfa7-6605cbe1ee01",
        "76383f23-27b9-4300-b591-d8ab13b2ef9e",
        "6ffc63d6-efd3-43dd-a992-4b2517a489a7",
        "dfd5cb3f-29bc-4d8a-8b6c-e9a9904717a7",
        "feb5ff31-be79-4a6f-9d93-27d5f78ffda8",
        "721a18f2-f8ae-4f19-81b2-a892d9a3aca5",
        "db85c36e-cdc0-495a-a7f2-4bb661723102",
        "c6a8423d-5bb8-4502-8c2e-ccf2d3467ffd",
        "88d8f12c-9ee4-4eac-8e27-f6844a637d9b",
        "3f0b73c0-5767-4e94-acdf-59af90be11f6",
        "2efdebde-2e7d-4c68-a46c-b11cf13a67a8",
        "e13f423e-7c12-4173-9e5a-ff450865bb25",
        "3bc63edd-8b24-440f-939f-d9edef16a095",
        "d60a7310-07ba-4b53-9cd1-6314d06d0bbf",
        "ede19c22-8844-4695-90bb-a53a654a3cbd",
        "d8d13212-d305-449d-a495-38d7d1aff885",
        "24ec1b39-2569-4274-9235-fb45adcbcbb1",
        "79d8155c-862a-422e-adb3-1369453ede23",
        "e63f1fcc-3151-4310-b4f3-e7aea9ba0470",
        "f145eda6-4514-496c-8f2c-248a04b528c4"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "ee784868-8497-4c0b-9244-6a18c0e48dcf",
      "english": "I like the music",
      "arabic": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u062f\u064a",
      "children": [
        "079f0182-8d96-42a1-892a-af92ec17b81a",
        "12e43bcf-53e5-46cd-b915-79c360541118",
        "a7745e5a-0b59-47c9-9f62-bad69ab673c0",
        "4b325b2e-0619-4f85-95cf-7bae7136cd70",
        "6da2c303-a1a7-4f16-89cc-3ccfa615b481",
        "c9e33926-cde9-46f9-a2c7-35aabc371bd1",
        "e2290930-2439-400e-ad37-fc41b244b746",
        "62ddf8f4-524f-40d9-9983-6eaa86a005d4",
        "05ad2b72-31a7-4242-a5dc-8e5e0e6e698a",
        "6f81e444-67b1-45e2-9d95-121c8894994d",
        "ae6f3822-1e8a-4ae3-8eaa-a339b692fccb",
        "33fce108-8e9c-4ca0-a4a4-d459d0566ce7",
        "4aaccfe3-4d20-4ea7-9eb8-dc868c019ee7",
        "19c1f66c-09fd-4adb-ab6c-4fcb73de61b9",
        "c51d00cd-75b1-483a-b9b3-490573dde36a",
        "959878c5-49cf-4407-9e84-5b8ceca7f83f",
        "380e6477-e8de-46b8-86cb-fe1fc351428a",
        "33537c0b-8a50-4d83-880a-e31445c23459",
        "cd79156e-8377-4f36-aefb-b6b708a503de",
        "c136107a-071f-4313-afb6-258845a68097",
        "20d740c9-167b-4b9b-8232-b9eba6b800e0",
        "ec47fb39-8734-41f2-a9b0-c55d67c72f40",
        "601cdbe8-e720-47e2-96ce-51dc2c296334",
        "38b25050-8268-4e6c-9af5-9c46b9c9ef47",
        "193b753d-16b2-4040-991a-c5eb069c1ddf",
        "b7f5d912-4424-4fde-bb6f-32ed9f6354da",
        "abec6792-7959-4e39-877d-bd70399fdced",
        "62bffc64-1e75-49eb-8578-fdcc5c600653",
        "c281b3c3-85f2-4a3f-b660-809e0ab317ee",
        "f2bf2dd2-7b4a-43ba-b5a3-574027b931ac",
        "7cb1892a-4c0a-4458-a279-fa5fd1336554",
        "f287bde4-5356-478c-82dc-8e65f5b38613",
        "aadd2909-02b7-4df1-8e93-5f54abc638fc",
        "49c218b0-f752-4721-ae20-f8ef0f051573",
        "17212eb9-77a5-47ab-ba21-1a297d286ba0",
        "925e0a50-a924-4451-8879-e106c96bb204",
        "212eea1c-4215-47f0-a3b6-ddbf39141fa6",
        "40fe8374-6fb2-45a4-9b8d-af6198db51cf",
        "8ede00cf-7eb3-4581-807e-a8e4ce1a41f4",
        "5f9e51da-91d0-4bd0-b737-033b6283f798",
        "fcd2d6a6-6841-48f6-91d2-ffb54afe0754",
        "ede9b064-34a7-477b-9ec1-8954f74c72ac",
        "654bd624-5a5d-4dc3-a572-cbd0fc636eb7",
        "8c7636ca-4487-46b4-9309-510fad0ac4bf",
        "fcc33c92-98d1-4743-8f19-439084f97f55",
        "c9d660cd-6027-4766-ba8c-10239077f325",
        "7852a04a-c15b-43ca-9f67-c2f7fa07a107",
        "20bd5839-cb56-49a8-99d2-392de01ae616",
        "059c2bb4-5666-4ec4-ae5e-568023ce460d",
        "b70ced45-7362-474e-80c3-dc0d33e16a18",
        "17c61bdc-8c2e-4d0a-9143-4656b13bfa8e",
        "93617ccd-ec7c-4081-9333-37d15de1190a",
        "cf351248-8965-4094-8afa-bc85bdf220ca",
        "be763308-d9f6-4351-96b2-0761bb027069",
        "a76e73c9-a42b-40f9-85b2-a64f33fda87f",
        "61f2e09c-ad96-414b-90ba-8eb0297f67d9",
        "458e91f1-64d4-49c0-8be1-fbe028ceb539",
        "199c3b40-d054-4e09-b014-8bf5368777eb",
        "e1d684d5-e66d-4166-bd61-955c077c8056",
        "845d1740-1d4b-4b91-b187-8b08d4ea0691",
        "e34ff0c0-76d4-47e3-8df5-f090ac754ae1",
        "ed564e0c-2d99-4084-802c-dd2647f4a926",
        "8c522c19-e15f-425b-b382-6c3319201c34",
        "27195773-603f-421a-a3d1-b7314510ea5d",
        "c3da97bc-dc2a-43e8-8147-8d9c0c989ec6",
        "0468c11e-6edf-4554-a129-28299aef12e7",
        "dcccd0ec-6893-4870-82b2-13d1c2b53a6e",
        "a431ce5d-5e10-4eab-a696-9aad808b2bfb",
        "01652d00-f1b2-4a47-b19d-a05e55e29262",
        "907f2f5c-fa0b-475c-b5c4-adbd400a6285",
        "146914cc-188e-4e71-bb8f-d781950b3e08",
        "bffa5692-8539-45e3-aa77-262a8db87963",
        "14e92131-5cce-442e-b9cc-2566a9cec3c6",
        "f6a7d173-ffb0-4a03-9e68-7f572b404e15",
        "bc817300-fbf4-4b8b-8a58-4575c5900ba7",
        "2a9d7365-2fc9-4908-b30a-64f95e4462b7",
        "ad266b71-3bb1-4cfb-ba2d-751cc528b93d",
        "4e8c4da9-a8c0-4ae1-8689-922db53df9bc",
        "f230c257-5ca0-4e83-8224-5e13dd0b4964",
        "2f0a42f0-cabf-4190-9099-3ea22740a127",
        "ee314ab5-ef06-41e4-a5a2-3009d256b898",
        "af6212ee-6ca0-43de-896b-df9dcad35f15",
        "faaba88b-a9d1-4edc-bcad-a75266fe4938",
        "c5d0f24e-50a4-4fb2-92ae-9590a739daba",
        "4d99fe1c-0c60-4f92-9908-54de9ba0fbd8",
        "9bde3d66-f63f-4290-882b-191381675ca6",
        "75ce03a0-38ea-4d94-bd84-9fc0732bf409",
        "65151164-b8f4-40fb-ae2f-ea2165b33238",
        "18d230ed-6fd7-4edb-aa48-527a8b9ab382",
        "d57b1224-eb4b-484f-9116-66da00c66602",
        "a49c6968-8339-4758-bd36-18672f8b4e99",
        "5881512c-ba57-441e-86b7-ce2e89255df0",
        "510fb190-9c80-42ff-b7b4-38ee4d8641db",
        "af841f7b-1e87-4517-94ca-248b78e5b3dd",
        "659cb5d0-0d45-4888-bb9d-0cafd88879eb",
        "604e6c90-b47f-4e66-941e-af43b3193bd7",
        "8e206c17-e4b4-4181-82b2-a97424c0905f",
        "f182f0fa-99b2-4f7f-996f-8d1352dcf670",
        "985a4a82-a726-4b1c-a0cb-9b3a40c51f50",
        "cb579573-7b21-4189-a7aa-196c96d7c65b",
        "09923479-1949-4907-bb29-a8172287daa0",
        "3b5e8a01-c58a-41ee-b239-c40c3a6541d3",
        "e8fd37fd-48e0-43b9-990a-6c344b4fbddc",
        "22e03c35-3eab-4424-94d0-ce35892a1fc1",
        "21553d75-7fc3-4140-ae33-3667d2424bc2",
        "e207c880-21d5-4973-9b5f-842262224652",
        "88573793-1348-4cdc-8b45-c24c3856b4e6",
        "bd08015f-75a7-46a4-b207-8781f2a3c1eb",
        "e65ac863-5d21-4cc0-a9bd-5cd187e627e2",
        "0a78c569-3074-4bc3-84b8-59a4b19c77d1",
        "647503eb-3543-4648-91f1-0696823c62da",
        "b14c13f9-68fc-44cb-ae43-d886be8761bd",
        "7cd1e590-c92c-4259-93e8-33fafc677e1b"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "cc8f8ce9-a65f-4f61-93ee-fab7e05fb64e",
      "english": "Can you turn on the AC?",
      "arabic": " \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "children": [
        "155cb8f4-b7ce-42de-ae63-ad229ac9a3b9",
        "b0376c82-823d-44da-b82c-237de995821b",
        "65bd7be6-c00a-40c7-b58a-8ccf6e4ff68d",
        "508aac8d-f588-4ed6-80e8-31b8213d21b5",
        "b98c9214-9688-46b7-a90a-a12270514231",
        "59971d3e-5310-489f-af09-44530928d8ba",
        "ee1330fa-66ee-4faf-8097-36f99a6089d5",
        "7c582f66-6d86-4730-898d-8af4feac4102",
        "db078fbd-c1e5-4003-aabc-a1ffb0e2b998",
        "fe55e498-3a94-4787-a58b-9aa8eb0cb977",
        "78f5835b-63c8-43d1-83e1-d94e6a36498d",
        "4ab4b8e5-2a1a-483d-86e0-6177de94da4e",
        "15230205-a58f-4493-a4b9-0e18f7819551",
        "88c7ddda-e661-4490-af84-b55b699025c9",
        "ca0e56a6-f766-4c14-944a-3c1140a704dd",
        "cbeb642f-f8d2-4ddd-9606-b7f837ffb64c",
        "096468cf-316e-4ca3-9742-91b44718b1ce",
        "dfa89712-b46f-4754-9d0c-61fef5f9c399",
        "c16af346-1c61-45a9-a4e1-df90ec84c199",
        "37fe5455-aba3-48a8-ae12-b195b084cda6",
        "30ff75c3-d006-4ce2-8d7e-fa49f3b72922",
        "da6a59aa-4ba1-48d5-995a-2b7406deabd3",
        "df4af371-cd14-48c9-8789-40676762f1e1",
        "2f724a5e-30a5-4e2e-9bad-57916385a9cd",
        "7294384e-2ffc-4cfe-a73a-b95931b9ccfa",
        "d4abee13-d38d-4db6-8b42-87ff26b87359",
        "aa00cf74-df10-4bfa-9915-ad09bd597409",
        "33953c1e-b0de-4212-a338-ccd03b7e243b",
        "5bdc6b23-40e7-4968-8677-b8e1ac8dd5cb",
        "a23c4f85-edb7-4ea1-b610-ab95f9882b15",
        "a868b8fe-1d8b-4bfa-9f40-f7bf3ac01141",
        "d9a86927-385e-4af5-93a5-887db946d7fc",
        "c7da4f74-d373-4271-bc21-a7118b9e4366",
        "bdf9438e-59bf-49e8-a2dd-ae2424986a70",
        "895927ef-ae56-4308-b318-aa9e80b77a4b",
        "a92c0782-bfa8-4c04-8572-d4eed633368d",
        "5fdf8a69-e625-4b31-a8b6-4c97116f3cf6",
        "18c394a4-2bc4-4ddf-8a03-6ce6cd3dc80b",
        "e00d46fe-81c0-458a-8ee4-da73d685b851",
        "2f241b66-037a-4a9d-afa7-01b3d292891a",
        "96a83d21-9431-44e8-b8bc-02baee3c65c6",
        "6afdf062-e7ba-4bd8-a5eb-596fd1643b11",
        "6fa8cd05-9b7f-4f4e-a72a-904520d75445",
        "02cf1016-b369-42c4-b2f8-57930141faa6",
        "d57d9a5e-ade1-44a0-bb44-a48738c1deca",
        "45f9afcf-0e9a-4923-a873-79b722065f14",
        "5771b0dc-b7f6-4ce0-a08c-a84c2bc14c6f",
        "023950b1-c27b-472e-97c0-660b067b9627",
        "f5b2d918-df70-49a0-a799-92b93d40966c",
        "08bc20ab-dd0a-4bd5-b863-26aa874644d4",
        "0b25d9d8-864e-42fa-8097-e57c16499022",
        "8dae7852-39e9-48f2-aba1-af8a5e85200b",
        "6ff0a4f7-8e77-48ee-84a9-1736d2801039",
        "c0f01cc9-8464-4474-8850-cdf5feec55a2",
        "c3feaab1-e24b-4ac0-ba51-790f27b74704",
        "7f6be87f-e442-46f1-a4f8-cd23fccde5d7",
        "3a29e9d8-900e-490a-bab9-af4f15fb29a4",
        "e1d3083a-1061-48d8-818f-969336c09751",
        "9dda8d47-cf6d-46b2-a761-0c0291173a52",
        "67a84383-33ff-4adf-b6c2-846313df8064",
        "ad929814-285d-4092-857e-70e902912231",
        "5c107064-b947-4a91-b724-86cff14727cf",
        "53abbac2-180e-4a8b-b6f7-c9ab828ed665",
        "1480ee5a-10d3-43e5-a67a-68cf7fd38a05",
        "045037d3-c918-40d2-81bb-c22afd3a96ba",
        "44c2ad71-449f-428a-be22-1daa116cc04e",
        "b91f737e-1424-48c1-9b51-8088f3cbab9b",
        "9f2ac41c-f4ad-4850-9a9c-52e3a3573bcd",
        "fd9f6ba1-3849-43ad-8c9c-86d095e94fa4",
        "b6899609-4e41-4bcf-b87b-f1d82ebf2266",
        "ee09a78a-4c90-443d-8f85-dae192bd025e"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "0a56325f-eea8-48d2-a1e2-b60e5b0278d9",
      "english": "Can I pay with VISA?",
      "arabic": " \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627\u061f",
      "children": [
        "c8da53dc-0f24-4ba9-8496-ee10dd32bdb8",
        "7d583371-74c0-47ee-bd2b-4df91563991f",
        "fbec6129-2662-4921-983f-5f59c305b5ac",
        "a0bcfd68-73ed-4ead-b743-381def17eb4e",
        "7cf2ea67-73b4-4144-b7c2-6e969c17306f",
        "baaec0e1-d29e-4ba8-90f2-5094afeef096",
        "85e27fd7-d349-408d-a51b-324fd57b4ec1",
        "3eaa92a7-9fe2-4709-9188-cc7c0210b985",
        "4479813f-a76a-4f5c-9d44-e3d36eace4aa",
        "c5c4de1f-907c-42d4-bc8b-05e1f107bdfc",
        "898303a9-ff0c-41cf-b5d7-cb569430f626",
        "d9b44e40-e3f9-4ca0-9d06-23f37be919da",
        "2b934a62-2413-4c95-9799-4daf8e7be00c",
        "eec08ed3-c439-47ae-bf60-44dd85795631",
        "4d4a766a-6522-45be-a906-7e78e2c685cc",
        "5a493d28-e658-4da2-b985-3d0a130871a7",
        "bf9e9dd1-eaee-4eb9-a909-e4d1aa0fb57d",
        "9c90d283-06ef-4683-b746-13ea89e16e86",
        "6c885a0f-711c-469f-aed6-8dc17622366b",
        "dd72ba81-795d-494a-8407-fb975bc45f88",
        "96174e4c-0410-493f-902d-3ee8ed594a83",
        "76ae5e6f-74ee-49e3-844f-5764354996c6",
        "f209da71-5aae-448e-87e4-7cfe77a799c2",
        "6d862cae-5bf4-41d5-abb8-d87e73544933",
        "86d16023-f81a-4ec7-b62b-9ec389f16e6e",
        "1616c3a0-8875-4152-b710-b35a9506e016",
        "5cb018d0-5594-467a-a65e-0638d5ce8552",
        "40ab5bc9-a834-46e1-a5cb-36877df6174d",
        "ab1d78ec-c048-41e2-a824-55130a997e2d",
        "2d7db614-3240-4bb1-8986-820d68062a89",
        "a5b01e8b-41fb-499c-beab-2a842c2a0352",
        "5a468a01-6269-436d-88f2-8d92407a0d10",
        "c9f1ba78-9ba1-4537-91da-666e146851f0",
        "9480a08e-edc0-4505-8746-2aca978150f2",
        "cf128f85-06f0-408e-8538-db391fc7b3a2",
        "581ef9ef-29ff-4a18-9aa6-4761899504a3",
        "cbf4b3b0-ce73-4ea9-bf6d-ed311f22ddd9",
        "d36aecd5-13d0-4494-be24-50a33c437a03",
        "621f6e88-7c82-4cbc-ba57-f3f6511990f2",
        "6f7b3286-bdb7-4571-86b5-7f5c291d683c",
        "40145da4-a294-4a8a-a8bf-94db09efbde7",
        "fcc4b8fd-5e8f-4e0b-91b7-ff2238a8d09a",
        "5ac5878a-7f8d-4fa8-a9c1-1e20aeac5034",
        "d7f2ac73-23b1-4aaa-b1f1-d787ebef1891",
        "d2917554-609a-405b-8df7-c7deb79f3b6d",
        "6325bf61-232f-49e8-bf09-dba537a62ac8",
        "baa7380b-4b0f-4abe-90b9-9d23376e4784",
        "7aed4a76-b29b-4d5c-89a4-35a7c1636809",
        "9c7a9806-00ae-4123-b471-c70b5e7a0dd9",
        "792b6fff-db1e-4d1e-8d15-fd76c2ec423e",
        "3d878202-0bb6-45d2-87ff-50291b230659",
        "48d12307-b549-4967-925e-e687c63dd1be",
        "a9270363-16e9-4a0c-a61c-95f87d6979ce",
        "40ac5c19-5e05-4a21-a559-ead568069177",
        "68e783a8-414d-4d73-94e0-562de757a8a6",
        "2b29ad60-a095-4255-b3ec-8db120b1ec14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "21d326d2-7186-47bd-97c9-9253a6e64bd8",
      "english": "I don't understand",
      "arabic": " \u0645\u0634 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645",
      "children": [
        "7ab715bc-40ad-4c4a-a643-14beebc23ff5",
        "5868a4f5-f8f1-4b5c-9377-432cf0982e43",
        "208ca19a-b01c-46ad-a0eb-cb71925b1c4c",
        "7cb9ecb9-5603-40e0-ae83-7593a45ea100",
        "a9291f16-a1e3-4a46-9828-81d6f18ec322",
        "f9e8e6c8-5eec-4252-b98d-7c34e9d3e8f3",
        "c0e8a7e7-e5d8-4378-a5ed-4a34e41e777e",
        "8291cb6e-c04a-4fa9-9fc6-44521435c562",
        "f51c8707-82cd-4c73-b9be-c54d4e27b2a4",
        "8e9771f7-5c9c-410c-8566-10550480dd6d",
        "df5fd565-48c9-4597-9df8-d2468e8f8c88",
        "acbe9350-50d4-4faf-9ca0-53e63e5e78f3",
        "2699893b-a048-49c9-9ece-b376a3382965",
        "1c132681-0f9a-42cd-8196-ce99b2cca585",
        "898807b4-c184-4876-ab5a-45ea71facde7",
        "ecc0c1c1-aaca-493e-9371-a04ea8dca376",
        "4992a1f8-b3a7-4093-84dc-926a35f14dc1",
        "021ede47-84f1-45f9-a827-0a9dd717ec57",
        "ab9b9213-0d17-4b5d-a7c0-884b5d2b9c9e",
        "be09a062-f979-4d57-a5a3-76ed7e525c50",
        "44c35529-2a57-42d1-9ec6-5f73ccd9c722",
        "cbe2c5ba-a738-4ceb-a789-726e207374f7",
        "0982231c-eb70-4720-8599-8ae3cef29fed",
        "101f6547-e7eb-41b0-bfb2-6ecce878bd6b",
        "77ccfd38-9a1b-4a28-acb6-91c793e07aa6",
        "b374662a-986d-40f8-b709-7dd6f06e0e14",
        "785848c5-8fcb-4906-bc44-0f78c2626c21",
        "5a637630-3603-404d-b3e5-371d26184ef7",
        "b949c5e8-6cdf-4b4c-bf97-2ec9bc288109",
        "a2c759ae-e58e-4709-b6fe-673ef2db9187",
        "b69fc219-1b46-410a-a468-033189de2256",
        "c0d59b9f-291b-4123-bb2d-d5ee986fcf86",
        "77c02a6f-6afe-443c-8982-d2ac229a63ad",
        "2be91972-414f-4b5b-ad31-f8b9549737b8",
        "e1a8212f-249b-4d87-af5b-dae6614c3c71",
        "f92024b6-a968-47ef-a505-d151367c8463",
        "cc4a39ed-385f-445d-8faa-831247ba26fa",
        "50540245-2db4-4543-b005-008947b175f4",
        "2d9968c2-fb35-4853-b719-2e149ff7c87b",
        "d7e26243-40cf-4373-b08d-9095c6d66a24",
        "68b558f4-f164-438e-b11e-9c1861d5aabf",
        "174403f2-2a02-47c8-87fe-4092b5784f80",
        "23514dd2-f3f3-4247-91ba-7517dcc49c88",
        "98a0f79c-c0d7-4008-aca7-69e00c0afaa1",
        "fe3c4c25-7e04-4508-87b1-8132d6c22f2a",
        "1ac1fb54-44a3-4b17-aad3-23c2deb99d98",
        "d6114108-3042-464f-8121-c3270eb2a5d2",
        "2cd8179e-cbb6-4b31-a58d-84e825946565",
        "24ea5080-9a7c-43e8-a308-cbb4b7df93a2",
        "7761c147-dac8-4be6-b0ba-5e4adb8626de",
        "1c34dcf7-30d2-4c11-b066-2e4c42fb0422",
        "9ce143b5-d7f3-47be-9b63-7a9370cca5d1",
        "6240d690-cb9c-4c55-b1ee-02e5db315568",
        "1d9c042a-aaec-4964-b5fd-8362df13c18d",
        "b0fc75f0-775d-41b1-95a8-86acd2e78ef2",
        "b4ac19ac-c56b-49a5-9af5-17c9c55caa8f",
        "4fcd2278-7796-427a-8962-2ef830d3b42d",
        "1162ce71-ad63-4cb8-8adf-78abb32016ec",
        "102e9d06-2feb-409c-a6d7-5a634eee0ba1",
        "b4c3c716-f29c-4632-bb54-dd6d176c1d51",
        "eeec873a-c8ab-41d6-b6b1-9e5159b485f7",
        "8159f7d2-3f17-474d-8e0c-b9cda3323b47",
        "9ef3d24b-9735-4bbe-a09e-8d939cb717b2",
        "046f5313-26cc-472f-a2d8-a69df17e9333",
        "9a9229c5-06b3-43cd-ad95-575b4722a781",
        "e48a0e03-35fd-4719-b090-57a51f8e9515",
        "77cdb879-9ec5-40b8-be5c-95b253b8763a",
        "6ea8b4ec-0148-4722-bdec-889273783c5f",
        "cf47eaa0-5d88-476f-b73a-d4799b85646e",
        "6364fea7-f886-463d-8c8e-19d8bf69ce84",
        "983946d9-6c4a-4306-b56d-f20c081cb87a",
        "1d633edc-a187-4dd0-9da0-1cb99eb64050",
        "c3dbb607-1f19-484b-a926-deee039905be",
        "33134866-a5c9-40d6-8479-809e50c16f08",
        "bce11038-9a2c-427f-837b-dcb547d0ed03",
        "a116a600-a85e-4e10-81a0-50d4b6a33072",
        "b9f86f3e-9844-41eb-be22-4c38739f6838",
        "c5a33e6a-9df6-4fb1-a397-9f8b4eaea842",
        "5a0fe30c-7eb1-419f-bfac-0481e0c5a6a4",
        "c084093c-535f-4422-b0b6-15adb5e0eff0",
        "a3272a07-1451-484e-967f-a2ea9036b55b",
        "cd28a209-aca7-4125-91b0-38bca64c39e5",
        "cc0a370e-607b-4e1a-815b-033099773513",
        "339a01ee-8fb1-4e57-93de-b4b21420ec64",
        "05aae646-791e-4758-82e8-68d28ca4730f",
        "d868dfc4-7abf-4457-8130-548955a83aac",
        "d8e2e582-0cd4-42aa-9f3d-91fb47cbccb6",
        "ea317fd5-df6d-4ae9-b5d4-6a26794d1a71",
        "68250f3f-16f6-4348-8613-832709ac56d0",
        "1d1553a8-d572-4edd-bdc3-9d5b2ac246f9",
        "d48c30fd-5307-4a19-8523-fa79f861a97b",
        "0ba8bedf-42b8-400c-b683-d57f0f9d076c",
        "15cadef3-9ae9-4c6b-b197-1eb601af1e2b",
        "71cdc487-0eef-4917-80fc-45299b7d438e",
        "d9cfc97f-fdce-4efa-a039-536b0fae8e8a",
        "14628462-9966-4d57-8172-9380870c54a4",
        "79d64bb1-b971-4c1c-87f7-b28792010f1c",
        "d8af3767-c759-4102-80e4-9e8515f1b758",
        "6cb87a41-6044-4d96-a2bc-7c1505e19a5b",
        "1a057275-1001-42b0-af44-59fa53776985",
        "b4b8cf90-abb0-4e20-b50c-beeabc9ce842",
        "8c793ebb-1f2f-47a0-8cc6-6f576b93f0dc",
        "b4c9ae09-af34-44b6-acb4-93e5f05bd0dd",
        "6e7cb07b-1c01-4296-befb-16b374d0d83c",
        "4b01333a-c629-4eae-a182-c2f47df377c3",
        "1dfca1cb-142e-49c7-bf28-17228685cdca",
        "6a37f41a-d385-410a-acae-181984e016cc",
        "1599a9dd-dab9-42aa-86af-9abab4f1eed8",
        "bf15e0e4-57d0-407c-b046-71a10f7fdda2",
        "e563c668-5e8e-40b6-b840-3a766d78c7ae",
        "13def411-3ea9-4aa0-93e1-ec5705a16dae",
        "503ff495-a383-4124-a247-5fb02b0c4bc5",
        "506d39ca-f69d-4212-8ded-8cf011c98aec",
        "2f69ade7-3367-4d4d-9ec8-856773bbb3fe",
        "2cfa0f1f-30e1-49a4-9e1b-b1dda897b075",
        "14d354e7-f34f-4e54-89bb-df93c56cfbca",
        "c0f105de-2fee-471e-8710-9f134918c73d",
        "be2b1e1d-6b07-42d7-8367-578546b0519e",
        "9cd0bad9-317e-46b5-9d3f-ea11c98948de",
        "1cbcb01c-0d2c-445b-b37f-4089f1153f01",
        "ea4ded1b-15c6-4161-b7d6-b97aa678e35a",
        "461ab2b1-2e6a-4f3e-b244-3c3b8141e1c7",
        "3dbe0a9f-6a38-4871-8089-4fa2ab786995",
        "596ec90a-7e4a-4caa-819a-6ae940a85739",
        "967ca9f9-e8a1-4ef6-9205-281415a1ba79",
        "2fb014a2-e7dd-45d6-b6ad-926f875bf54c",
        "40c537c2-79d2-44d2-8ede-febde8aa0bcf",
        "12e43bcf-53e5-46cd-b915-79c360541118",
        "a7745e5a-0b59-47c9-9f62-bad69ab673c0",
        "4b325b2e-0619-4f85-95cf-7bae7136cd70",
        "6da2c303-a1a7-4f16-89cc-3ccfa615b481",
        "c9e33926-cde9-46f9-a2c7-35aabc371bd1",
        "e2290930-2439-400e-ad37-fc41b244b746",
        "62ddf8f4-524f-40d9-9983-6eaa86a005d4",
        "05ad2b72-31a7-4242-a5dc-8e5e0e6e698a",
        "6f81e444-67b1-45e2-9d95-121c8894994d",
        "ae6f3822-1e8a-4ae3-8eaa-a339b692fccb",
        "33fce108-8e9c-4ca0-a4a4-d459d0566ce7",
        "4aaccfe3-4d20-4ea7-9eb8-dc868c019ee7",
        "19c1f66c-09fd-4adb-ab6c-4fcb73de61b9",
        "348bdc75-6d88-471a-aedc-983a7a71fa69",
        "b0628547-23cb-4658-b478-741100542564",
        "aa48a66a-6146-49c5-9afb-dccbaa0d580c",
        "baff3e58-d79b-4107-9037-76565b8ad9da",
        "6c00ce06-8bf4-4e20-af40-1e3c3fcc5a98",
        "b223f13e-d194-4c55-a85e-68f314b6eb68",
        "894e2adf-2c86-435a-bfc6-8d587a5b940e",
        "6c8f8979-d72c-4986-9f44-3874cb37000a",
        "a8302d0f-3a6f-4cef-99d4-5e399d75c5ef",
        "3c0c831d-303a-47bf-88cd-6f77eb3dcffe",
        "56cae1ca-a7b1-48e2-8b6e-7c12e76f0a9e",
        "c834bda7-3a27-4b29-9307-a6bb0d221ed5",
        "84d0ab66-c5a0-43fe-a675-a3216850b38a"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "6cf65d56-a798-488a-a58d-50c5e0f7e332",
      "english": "My Arabic is very bad",
      "arabic": " \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "children": [
        "c853fb93-c136-4b37-ab7d-bb8b13c94ca5",
        "d1592002-f013-44ce-bf04-c57382c1e039",
        "f2567d05-30c4-4cd3-9c5d-d66bf8273b4b",
        "0ca76401-b303-484d-88da-cac9c5d795e3",
        "223534d6-1b5b-4979-be9b-1cb1f8c01dfc",
        "86646551-b2af-488d-88f8-e6f8c343f770",
        "e4568ccb-d1ff-430f-85ac-bc56b71e917b",
        "9e4dd3ef-db4b-4e16-8015-866b7666d448",
        "401dcbef-953e-4bc3-b274-7ec7e1bad2df",
        "fd98d553-28a6-433f-b6f6-d8a12cf0da6c",
        "77daead9-c818-4c2d-ad3d-e54313878e17",
        "fafe8eb5-61df-4e84-987e-927e16b404a1",
        "5a124aa7-d344-44ef-902b-29de7c613320",
        "4d95dbeb-cf99-46d8-b1f9-0be8b86d31ae",
        "fdf9ff89-59ac-4d57-8377-a155390ec3cd",
        "8d00d48e-672a-4438-bc60-6ba6e19ef90e",
        "264e5cae-a2ce-4069-958e-21c213d83b2e",
        "9249ef71-a47e-43dc-a2f7-2dd3da5d9cf1",
        "41a78f6c-a40b-4a01-baf5-c14460818367",
        "63b4f160-4849-4747-a128-448b3982b551",
        "75b3bdd4-d972-4f2e-9fc4-d56a077fd855",
        "0befe968-b9d9-4ff0-8c4d-9b7c556394a9",
        "aa87167a-85b3-4ba0-a4f6-54248e4b03c3",
        "7b965d46-12f6-4273-9eee-3730341d7aaf",
        "5c848462-eabf-40cd-9c39-09fe18cb48f3",
        "fd72e55f-38c6-4a41-ac1c-0c1f1d0f29c0",
        "7ea94a02-d86c-4464-babf-855a8e05cdd2",
        "b9e8e101-b5ce-489a-85af-4c473a573fff",
        "e7a30be1-ee9d-42af-b4c2-bc5491ec0422",
        "98c260c8-00a1-4490-a07b-b02f728c0cab",
        "877ed118-5975-412e-8548-3ff68c56f0c9",
        "903849d2-0862-4cbc-9d96-b1efb36ba4d6",
        "1d626bb7-ca55-41a7-a24b-c9504c5cb61a",
        "ce1c494d-2342-450c-9deb-285a4f581c9f",
        "7782fde1-6397-4e4d-89fa-4b0a279d7b30",
        "601b839f-0d06-4ca2-b878-db6fa453f981",
        "a2284303-72f4-4ca7-a6a8-70bcb47e6875",
        "e77bb3b6-567e-461f-a917-56751a4d0cb5",
        "c4e33e04-9099-4411-8f0e-d5a6d46fdaa1",
        "903bfc0a-066d-4d3a-87ba-4f28a7fd0ae3",
        "2218ce65-d4eb-41eb-a83d-673ec32a34ed",
        "0faee2d2-a8f1-461c-9dfa-1f981110a6d1",
        "ba59799f-f8e5-4fae-902c-224cbc72c007",
        "2c965e08-32a4-447d-bde6-313d107c6e1b",
        "52ad34ab-1aea-466e-bc18-6993ea9fbb04",
        "7a61789e-7959-467b-878c-4bade42c9c8f",
        "8b1669ec-ff29-4850-a373-e49a576bdcfc",
        "df973b18-800c-48c9-9a48-c5c1361c2de0",
        "3ed0e34e-f318-4033-b37d-6158e243f896",
        "d5697128-342a-4070-a6d1-82b6fa2400b8",
        "02e90f71-76c9-4f7f-816d-933313b3d15b",
        "3f8c6899-1114-4331-a9b5-734ce8e2de42",
        "925d83d4-1f79-435f-8eff-2874d2bf947f",
        "7c7dedfb-29a1-4856-833f-6d56736843e0",
        "829249c6-c90d-4c7e-b4a0-ee163701ed91",
        "f54ed0ad-9960-45b7-86cc-b44b94577b73",
        "a1a46dfe-a31f-4abc-8d98-4b3899349744",
        "5b1695ba-5311-4c21-8440-962aaac27c71",
        "8761b38a-6443-446d-a6df-97974828e7ea",
        "0d6c03b5-c7a7-4325-8e21-2de4eedaeb6c",
        "f1f3fe39-40db-4705-8ee8-ffbf692ae6b7",
        "ec1d3e80-3c61-47ee-b877-7dd6e710c13a",
        "30eec318-12f9-4f58-a055-0f4afdad40db",
        "8a93b092-79ea-42b7-9a50-78ab3bbea7c6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "6eddc770-186d-40d6-98cc-c22c8ef5885e",
      "english": "Excuse Me",
      "arabic": " \u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627",
      "children": [
        "7caed1ec-ce87-4f1b-a230-c00a2e5a509c",
        "2f69ade7-3367-4d4d-9ec8-856773bbb3fe",
        "2cfa0f1f-30e1-49a4-9e1b-b1dda897b075",
        "14d354e7-f34f-4e54-89bb-df93c56cfbca",
        "c0f105de-2fee-471e-8710-9f134918c73d",
        "be2b1e1d-6b07-42d7-8367-578546b0519e",
        "9cd0bad9-317e-46b5-9d3f-ea11c98948de",
        "1cbcb01c-0d2c-445b-b37f-4089f1153f01",
        "ea4ded1b-15c6-4161-b7d6-b97aa678e35a",
        "461ab2b1-2e6a-4f3e-b244-3c3b8141e1c7",
        "3dbe0a9f-6a38-4871-8089-4fa2ab786995",
        "596ec90a-7e4a-4caa-819a-6ae940a85739",
        "967ca9f9-e8a1-4ef6-9205-281415a1ba79",
        "2fb014a2-e7dd-45d6-b6ad-926f875bf54c",
        "40c537c2-79d2-44d2-8ede-febde8aa0bcf"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "f8649eae-a5be-4078-8362-0044380c3ab3",
      "english": "I'm learning Arabic",
      "arabic": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "children": [
        "41eaba26-6f9d-4ecf-afbe-6d966032b424",
        "12e43bcf-53e5-46cd-b915-79c360541118",
        "a7745e5a-0b59-47c9-9f62-bad69ab673c0",
        "4b325b2e-0619-4f85-95cf-7bae7136cd70",
        "6da2c303-a1a7-4f16-89cc-3ccfa615b481",
        "c9e33926-cde9-46f9-a2c7-35aabc371bd1",
        "e2290930-2439-400e-ad37-fc41b244b746",
        "62ddf8f4-524f-40d9-9983-6eaa86a005d4",
        "05ad2b72-31a7-4242-a5dc-8e5e0e6e698a",
        "6f81e444-67b1-45e2-9d95-121c8894994d",
        "ae6f3822-1e8a-4ae3-8eaa-a339b692fccb",
        "33fce108-8e9c-4ca0-a4a4-d459d0566ce7",
        "4aaccfe3-4d20-4ea7-9eb8-dc868c019ee7",
        "19c1f66c-09fd-4adb-ab6c-4fcb73de61b9",
        "d2ccf3ba-67de-4c65-b09e-cf1ce9f55d9d",
        "c4f479b7-ab05-4720-81e0-3d8640d6ee1f",
        "a36b3493-7d62-4c9c-8859-b544d2779a62",
        "a0cf9a4b-051a-44c5-9f5c-60380874860e",
        "0d549794-e5da-4759-a14f-e5a08c873679",
        "9d1c0c96-9c0c-446c-a4d1-e3bcc2a8478a",
        "b8302ea5-ca55-4e34-8371-bfebf2614909",
        "5a9aec6b-ca54-4700-bf65-4cc3479d6720",
        "d67576c7-af57-4915-8223-7a7afceeef7d",
        "b8e49285-7098-4b7a-9f5e-57414da1f229",
        "74ef5230-aaf3-4be5-8ed4-e23791c5046f",
        "7470b08a-1c0e-4607-bb32-64deaed6db28",
        "23bd653d-5679-4d4b-b6c6-372fd4fc1035",
        "cf4bc712-6b35-406e-9a85-1c56d9fafe40",
        "0f09e92e-f991-4b62-a8e2-168cceb1a793",
        "c9f3d106-c012-4e34-a675-2be7da3ac491",
        "38d84ee3-d18d-48fc-86ad-741d69e465aa",
        "3aa3c1d3-7ceb-4be3-8c6e-850b3fee9f53",
        "93e55116-4e3f-4a5f-915b-8fdf365360d5",
        "be03d61d-f8fb-47a7-9dbf-f6f76771d47f",
        "d40b14c3-a3cd-43f2-8b95-bcc7cbb7ee19",
        "dfad9279-fbad-4ed0-bffe-ba628ea2d8b9",
        "9265af3a-47e1-4687-8be3-a028eb23dc9d",
        "06dafc2a-c11c-4c14-bc09-71ca3b92152c",
        "6461a7e8-3d1d-460c-9476-7c2310d4d8de",
        "ed69afdb-f808-4fdc-8e52-624031844559",
        "fa007a2d-990a-4547-a92e-a4190d35fb61",
        "94936bc1-a10f-4302-8bb3-f3808c2191b6",
        "d1592002-f013-44ce-bf04-c57382c1e039",
        "f2567d05-30c4-4cd3-9c5d-d66bf8273b4b",
        "0ca76401-b303-484d-88da-cac9c5d795e3",
        "223534d6-1b5b-4979-be9b-1cb1f8c01dfc",
        "86646551-b2af-488d-88f8-e6f8c343f770",
        "e4568ccb-d1ff-430f-85ac-bc56b71e917b",
        "9e4dd3ef-db4b-4e16-8015-866b7666d448",
        "401dcbef-953e-4bc3-b274-7ec7e1bad2df",
        "fd98d553-28a6-433f-b6f6-d8a12cf0da6c",
        "77daead9-c818-4c2d-ad3d-e54313878e17",
        "fafe8eb5-61df-4e84-987e-927e16b404a1",
        "5a124aa7-d344-44ef-902b-29de7c613320",
        "4d95dbeb-cf99-46d8-b1f9-0be8b86d31ae",
        "fdf9ff89-59ac-4d57-8377-a155390ec3cd",
        "8d00d48e-672a-4438-bc60-6ba6e19ef90e",
        "264e5cae-a2ce-4069-958e-21c213d83b2e",
        "d7639ef4-f85d-4bac-8123-67f76fdef3e0",
        "8ee5c6f8-b35c-45d0-b4eb-4f901c583609",
        "43190010-98ed-46fa-8650-420c9124cf5c",
        "2674868e-708b-47f2-8a60-db7da6547598",
        "00416c18-cc34-4795-819a-5e6c1b20081e",
        "ea41bf9a-d6ff-4a21-ac66-e4c81e6110b0",
        "680f0dca-ffb8-4097-94f4-ab1b691eabab",
        "d212fc26-dc32-4cf3-9776-37dbed643140",
        "6deb611e-5c4d-4b66-b0e4-1c3fde66eb68",
        "aa0778ac-a063-4abd-9386-83311f571452",
        "2ac4b700-982f-4be0-9493-465b1ec5c2da",
        "f26b30aa-c1f8-47a5-ae6d-0031520b64da",
        "a9d604c5-b075-4753-808f-02cb8f11bf86",
        "d9a6450b-0cd8-4967-b8cb-e35e9a2e8b24",
        "12e43bcf-53e5-46cd-b915-79c360541118",
        "a7745e5a-0b59-47c9-9f62-bad69ab673c0",
        "4b325b2e-0619-4f85-95cf-7bae7136cd70",
        "6da2c303-a1a7-4f16-89cc-3ccfa615b481",
        "c9e33926-cde9-46f9-a2c7-35aabc371bd1",
        "e2290930-2439-400e-ad37-fc41b244b746",
        "62ddf8f4-524f-40d9-9983-6eaa86a005d4",
        "05ad2b72-31a7-4242-a5dc-8e5e0e6e698a",
        "6f81e444-67b1-45e2-9d95-121c8894994d",
        "ae6f3822-1e8a-4ae3-8eaa-a339b692fccb",
        "33fce108-8e9c-4ca0-a4a4-d459d0566ce7",
        "4aaccfe3-4d20-4ea7-9eb8-dc868c019ee7",
        "19c1f66c-09fd-4adb-ab6c-4fcb73de61b9",
        "d2ccf3ba-67de-4c65-b09e-cf1ce9f55d9d",
        "c4f479b7-ab05-4720-81e0-3d8640d6ee1f",
        "a36b3493-7d62-4c9c-8859-b544d2779a62",
        "a0cf9a4b-051a-44c5-9f5c-60380874860e",
        "0d549794-e5da-4759-a14f-e5a08c873679",
        "9d1c0c96-9c0c-446c-a4d1-e3bcc2a8478a",
        "b8302ea5-ca55-4e34-8371-bfebf2614909",
        "5a9aec6b-ca54-4700-bf65-4cc3479d6720",
        "d67576c7-af57-4915-8223-7a7afceeef7d",
        "b8e49285-7098-4b7a-9f5e-57414da1f229",
        "74ef5230-aaf3-4be5-8ed4-e23791c5046f",
        "7470b08a-1c0e-4607-bb32-64deaed6db28",
        "23bd653d-5679-4d4b-b6c6-372fd4fc1035",
        "cf4bc712-6b35-406e-9a85-1c56d9fafe40",
        "0f09e92e-f991-4b62-a8e2-168cceb1a793",
        "c9f3d106-c012-4e34-a675-2be7da3ac491",
        "38d84ee3-d18d-48fc-86ad-741d69e465aa",
        "3aa3c1d3-7ceb-4be3-8c6e-850b3fee9f53",
        "93e55116-4e3f-4a5f-915b-8fdf365360d5",
        "be03d61d-f8fb-47a7-9dbf-f6f76771d47f",
        "d40b14c3-a3cd-43f2-8b95-bcc7cbb7ee19",
        "dfad9279-fbad-4ed0-bffe-ba628ea2d8b9",
        "9265af3a-47e1-4687-8be3-a028eb23dc9d",
        "06dafc2a-c11c-4c14-bc09-71ca3b92152c",
        "6461a7e8-3d1d-460c-9476-7c2310d4d8de",
        "ed69afdb-f808-4fdc-8e52-624031844559",
        "fa007a2d-990a-4547-a92e-a4190d35fb61",
        "94936bc1-a10f-4302-8bb3-f3808c2191b6",
        "1c555440-f02f-4079-b45c-3ff5b687c46e",
        "4f08f327-ae92-4d26-8382-42499a5a8f38",
        "5df98254-e0fb-4f25-902e-47b8811e7156",
        "d202fc7e-1df7-4f36-8017-f3682e3a2597",
        "8654eae3-4ed1-45a6-887c-def8230f8e96",
        "36d23755-5d65-4512-9a74-99ac33207b97",
        "8af04ca8-8e49-4c55-ae9e-e10c1eb0bb33",
        "791cc5b1-91a9-4666-8c19-ffc3eb2ce3d0",
        "0058ff8d-f694-4d64-b1a4-b1d4fab6ad0a",
        "59093138-12de-4e76-a16f-b902aa17ce0b",
        "bddf89fb-be5b-450c-8ac2-5a34b7a53305",
        "6800bbad-21b3-4907-91a1-4515a640aca4",
        "a9023d6b-ee3a-4b25-aee3-4cba9efcee0d",
        "7196300f-ca61-4941-b356-aff816941f7f",
        "75bdcfcd-4799-477a-9724-1ac4f95eb3d5",
        "6162a109-92cd-4246-b374-8a3d53aa9e1a",
        "bab9d347-9e13-4d85-aec4-d96e03afb206",
        "f6d00440-d82b-445f-9632-400ae84a59d7",
        "f9767561-b24f-49e3-ab9f-25407f182463",
        "a4f62e97-26d4-434a-b061-da5d340892ee",
        "77c205ba-f0a6-4f7b-ad3b-be0b2789cfa2",
        "2a56734a-6ed5-4851-8c0a-d6fe21c833f8",
        "a92443a8-d07b-4d46-a21f-6cfa2f065b4f",
        "7d8a54dd-0e29-4234-b645-c3257beecdbb",
        "6df1e2aa-df61-441a-8cad-6f1d1c57a48e",
        "b9d9cad2-d6c0-490c-a7f8-47f6f0cd7294",
        "16301036-5521-47e9-a4f0-e48b798c1ac5",
        "d1592002-f013-44ce-bf04-c57382c1e039",
        "f2567d05-30c4-4cd3-9c5d-d66bf8273b4b",
        "0ca76401-b303-484d-88da-cac9c5d795e3",
        "223534d6-1b5b-4979-be9b-1cb1f8c01dfc",
        "86646551-b2af-488d-88f8-e6f8c343f770",
        "e4568ccb-d1ff-430f-85ac-bc56b71e917b",
        "9e4dd3ef-db4b-4e16-8015-866b7666d448",
        "401dcbef-953e-4bc3-b274-7ec7e1bad2df",
        "fd98d553-28a6-433f-b6f6-d8a12cf0da6c",
        "77daead9-c818-4c2d-ad3d-e54313878e17",
        "fafe8eb5-61df-4e84-987e-927e16b404a1",
        "5a124aa7-d344-44ef-902b-29de7c613320",
        "4d95dbeb-cf99-46d8-b1f9-0be8b86d31ae",
        "fdf9ff89-59ac-4d57-8377-a155390ec3cd",
        "8d00d48e-672a-4438-bc60-6ba6e19ef90e",
        "264e5cae-a2ce-4069-958e-21c213d83b2e",
        "d7639ef4-f85d-4bac-8123-67f76fdef3e0",
        "8ee5c6f8-b35c-45d0-b4eb-4f901c583609",
        "43190010-98ed-46fa-8650-420c9124cf5c",
        "2674868e-708b-47f2-8a60-db7da6547598",
        "00416c18-cc34-4795-819a-5e6c1b20081e",
        "ea41bf9a-d6ff-4a21-ac66-e4c81e6110b0",
        "680f0dca-ffb8-4097-94f4-ab1b691eabab",
        "d212fc26-dc32-4cf3-9776-37dbed643140",
        "6deb611e-5c4d-4b66-b0e4-1c3fde66eb68",
        "aa0778ac-a063-4abd-9386-83311f571452",
        "2ac4b700-982f-4be0-9493-465b1ec5c2da",
        "f26b30aa-c1f8-47a5-ae6d-0031520b64da",
        "a9d604c5-b075-4753-808f-02cb8f11bf86"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "709c9eff-3882-46e6-bce7-e9cf8f880a66",
      "english": "Can you repeat that?",
      "arabic": " \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "children": [
        "ce8a631a-fe2e-492d-baa6-9416f0e8684f",
        "8d54ec3e-ec1f-40c9-ab7e-3888acb09229",
        "8cd236e9-fdab-42e6-b1df-39ce8169c244",
        "6540416c-4bef-40fd-b44c-46750af7d1f3",
        "182ce089-c0cc-41d3-9380-a0d590516a0b",
        "42c5b1e7-dcb6-46d3-aeb3-34daf535f495",
        "7da204af-65a6-48d8-bd7b-27e067ed43c9",
        "bab21445-fd81-49cd-9c5b-5053a8b4d9db",
        "33ff89f8-9e49-401c-9f86-6e27394a6f24",
        "aea900d7-19ae-4f50-9bc6-dff2e15d4a57",
        "c84bb00f-f4dc-4a43-a235-049386b7f0dc",
        "75cdfd6c-75e5-4f47-8f09-156daa829922",
        "fd74fc37-3761-44f6-a94f-faa870802a23",
        "1c3b3e9b-a32a-4d0a-88f7-3a229240b34d",
        "26e66e72-5db6-4b8b-8afd-5172376e24ac",
        "30747093-ad31-4b3b-8afb-fa2716d29f4a",
        "317b6633-6f75-4dbc-a72d-2f17635a881a",
        "d135e880-1d59-45ad-93a3-5d2b56bd298d",
        "a9216955-3ca0-4733-bb84-70ea73022ceb",
        "f501cc54-6bca-400d-b4f2-ae0bee01a600",
        "b6c8b3e5-3e6d-4a54-a28e-ad2fbca3372b",
        "417255ca-0b7c-4413-94cb-276b038cf835",
        "20e7519b-d484-4639-b546-fa91cc0360e8",
        "91000105-aa6d-4f13-9c58-0f5b51c3ce3d",
        "fbf2f4e3-7427-4246-8d80-1bafec6a4c21",
        "aa31ff2b-3aab-4f2e-977d-6c08adc86e0b",
        "542bc51f-01ed-4947-bb5c-0c417e9f4746",
        "054cc5bc-d8c7-4254-9107-00d81d1c5b93",
        "62af7b8e-502d-4b45-b7ab-06aca55c7b19",
        "405d839d-de51-4925-9d17-dea81f3efa2e",
        "b5c3df99-722b-486f-a4a6-a27284d1c57f",
        "a4f603a8-0f06-4907-8577-d542a3bd089d",
        "839760cb-6b17-4d4f-bfc9-569f2eab8c9d",
        "dc1df630-85ca-46d7-9820-ee4821232e69",
        "88c138ee-87c9-4217-a85f-25e2357cc4fb",
        "d2fbfa5f-4b87-4d1c-932b-9201bacaa32e",
        "3889091a-0924-41b1-9bdc-74565770a741",
        "9f341784-6c7e-4baa-bc2c-4084b901f1ab",
        "4b8c42a7-946c-4dad-8478-aba00d2c8c5c",
        "31c2e442-5419-4c60-bd68-0f32bffd5483",
        "7c2935e9-f634-4635-9e86-cc22923c0356",
        "1fd79693-4fc3-4a2a-bccb-f2a6604c278b",
        "17211823-15fc-480e-925f-5e2b16f0b339",
        "98a2d2c2-c152-4626-85d8-12d3a3d25741",
        "bd4fc18f-d6db-43b3-b1cd-895a1f468f89",
        "f2f0b7b8-d777-4af9-be95-a61b32b2bc6b",
        "8c3b7e11-6ad1-4598-8727-a025b38e86c7",
        "a69c1d2d-35dc-4b49-a024-b0eb21ca76c8",
        "a7f9ea89-be46-494c-805b-50beb4b490ae",
        "e4a0b43d-214b-45d3-9f80-a02b85484517",
        "e1126da9-621a-400c-8236-7ab970a3273c",
        "ac87f172-2e9f-494d-b09f-1d5d04924b80",
        "9031ec1a-694c-4238-bf3d-d69a6a063edf",
        "86bb105d-37e4-4c9a-86d1-2235f49e6546",
        "d9d0634a-deae-4625-bd97-08dbaae12865",
        "44927631-7437-4d22-aa8d-061314084d6b",
        "76be179a-5b6f-490d-aed0-f3665992d71e",
        "2ee7429c-50e7-4bfe-a945-6f42396b3779",
        "c9a94318-57a7-46db-89a3-76c4e0fb94a6",
        "8f8b507c-6f3b-4c04-b9bb-e9844e4bf4bc",
        "d06750bf-a881-41d6-ab28-aa055bc20179",
        "4f900f85-fea8-49e2-971a-362484603171",
        "04c6e74a-638f-49cc-83fc-2278e93d93a5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "f59a2fdf-0d82-47ec-a070-7aad6072d042",
      "english": "Can you speak slower, please?",
      "arabic": " \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "children": [
        "d565126d-e575-4c79-b563-acb378484e67",
        "3200beef-430f-4f2e-a7d2-d330be2c58c2",
        "2331c539-04f6-4445-a2f6-0cf52b4abff3",
        "86106da7-7f16-43bc-b8cc-262a7495c540",
        "4f9ffb20-de24-4a98-bdbc-c023f480dc81",
        "7d5768bf-e654-44d1-94bc-6f411f3c80aa",
        "66e7d9c8-0905-4b02-9786-aea5582ab723",
        "0f730b75-54ff-43be-aeb8-812d3cea468d",
        "fae59967-5f65-47b4-9ab2-2708b93e1d27",
        "68ec3b16-a07e-4b54-8133-b32ba1b29d25",
        "724ee4ce-ef3b-4afd-9597-7835d24f99f1",
        "ecc6d61e-b69c-49ea-90d6-d0aabd55bcc8",
        "56116c59-0f4e-408d-8cc5-c29c23ca2762",
        "8855554a-866f-4604-be79-19f2cde682e4",
        "4d9e56bb-4bd5-4a22-86d5-45ae0f3390ef",
        "d97b88e3-9178-4146-abb7-9c86258202e6",
        "a5a3a549-db9f-4037-a16e-82cacb1e9026",
        "a23846ae-3899-4865-bec7-4ed5c5bd5d60",
        "f2556ddf-7abe-4fc5-a070-59e51fedb78f",
        "02bdfdb0-caa0-4176-98ce-bb2df16feefc",
        "11cb9c54-ef00-4b99-b0cc-0bcc6f84dde0",
        "27b45dd6-e052-450e-87a4-199f206a7e9d",
        "948e097b-304e-406e-b540-3d331a1512e5",
        "513baec2-aa49-4822-8b7d-da979800094a",
        "3c95a515-e412-4955-abe9-b68b93f11354",
        "086ae7b9-4109-4965-a608-0526aa66c951",
        "d65efc5a-13e8-4f34-b708-f208b322f033",
        "58f5c4b2-4c21-48ba-bfcb-923e5b1100af",
        "658e88d9-bd39-4cca-9a4a-ded5542280c6",
        "4d0d8cf2-f9c9-4afd-a74a-74d8f3408fac",
        "3b4e4f39-ffb5-4921-887b-1eeda0cf0eef",
        "7f1916fe-9e0c-411e-8174-37e5e7a46c42",
        "e8751c8e-e7b4-46fe-820b-80a5c7ba489a",
        "486e467d-aec9-4ef6-aa8a-5bc65a437589",
        "900287f7-2231-4cd5-b5af-59968546f370",
        "16bd9584-6e9f-4f12-9221-40486793c5c9",
        "36ebfbae-778f-4ba5-9e09-ecb9431ce5fc",
        "0ee7fdee-003a-4a52-95e1-cef3ea66a4e3",
        "61d6dd26-6189-41f4-b9d6-9ad3619bae9c",
        "fc8b03ec-9a8c-4b03-8028-cbc5405f75d8",
        "16c9e766-ebe6-4153-8034-bb60ea4f037d",
        "2df8d2ca-bb61-4ec8-92e6-9d8b581eb751",
        "6fa0e6b9-80a7-469e-a23a-e5e11b32d61a",
        "fb172ace-d17e-4893-8b8a-34004dc3ca61",
        "7bafe214-935d-44f0-a9e4-f52f9b5898f0",
        "91149ba9-240c-4a32-9b94-3949704eb782",
        "4b108959-d47f-4af1-8678-bc9d94afc08a",
        "3eed3367-5aee-42e4-bd74-328d1f82bf03",
        "9fbc3081-729a-4695-ada0-0d9612564232",
        "75535b82-8dce-4031-ac4a-8710bfce9b22",
        "5cb1f78b-bc5f-459f-9b45-0faac0ee46b5",
        "3177106b-967d-4edd-8bd2-738efdfb58d9",
        "2071638b-3d44-48a6-b765-ba25f8e42c28",
        "30b76478-46b7-4157-ac9c-075e81c0d1bb",
        "25829079-9271-4480-9581-6411bf960227",
        "cd21b596-f6f0-4425-8a99-f7284b76fef3",
        "f3b69960-be80-459c-a230-fbbb5fcd3e2e",
        "43522e6d-e844-47ba-9950-3baac1fd84c3",
        "7b63537c-706a-4a8e-87d8-3550cc31f182",
        "9953378f-400b-4103-84fd-b12af68b6f2c",
        "d4494d3e-8b58-4da0-8db1-cb7e87459ba1",
        "b0ecca4c-267b-4500-ac53-356e5c9a05a6",
        "d2fbfa5f-4b87-4d1c-932b-9201bacaa32e",
        "3889091a-0924-41b1-9bdc-74565770a741",
        "9f341784-6c7e-4baa-bc2c-4084b901f1ab",
        "4b8c42a7-946c-4dad-8478-aba00d2c8c5c",
        "31c2e442-5419-4c60-bd68-0f32bffd5483",
        "7c2935e9-f634-4635-9e86-cc22923c0356",
        "1fd79693-4fc3-4a2a-bccb-f2a6604c278b",
        "17211823-15fc-480e-925f-5e2b16f0b339",
        "98a2d2c2-c152-4626-85d8-12d3a3d25741",
        "bd4fc18f-d6db-43b3-b1cd-895a1f468f89",
        "f2f0b7b8-d777-4af9-be95-a61b32b2bc6b",
        "8c3b7e11-6ad1-4598-8727-a025b38e86c7",
        "a69c1d2d-35dc-4b49-a024-b0eb21ca76c8",
        "a7f9ea89-be46-494c-805b-50beb4b490ae",
        "e4a0b43d-214b-45d3-9f80-a02b85484517",
        "e1126da9-621a-400c-8236-7ab970a3273c",
        "ac87f172-2e9f-494d-b09f-1d5d04924b80",
        "9031ec1a-694c-4238-bf3d-d69a6a063edf",
        "86bb105d-37e4-4c9a-86d1-2235f49e6546",
        "d9d0634a-deae-4625-bd97-08dbaae12865",
        "44927631-7437-4d22-aa8d-061314084d6b",
        "76be179a-5b6f-490d-aed0-f3665992d71e",
        "2ee7429c-50e7-4bfe-a945-6f42396b3779",
        "c9a94318-57a7-46db-89a3-76c4e0fb94a6",
        "8f8b507c-6f3b-4c04-b9bb-e9844e4bf4bc",
        "d06750bf-a881-41d6-ab28-aa055bc20179",
        "4f900f85-fea8-49e2-971a-362484603171",
        "04c6e74a-638f-49cc-83fc-2278e93d93a5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "43106dbb-d57c-4432-af11-b639e34af068",
      "english": "Can you say that in English?",
      "arabic": " \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "children": [
        "cdd814f0-f297-4117-a1b2-72d8de71f7e6",
        "f56d2698-502f-4367-8596-0c4e245ffb5a",
        "33727ac4-fe07-4081-8dd6-eb032efa07da",
        "b25895af-e5dd-4766-9c5e-80902e4f23a7",
        "0918dea6-14b5-4b2b-85b9-e2c3348c6a20",
        "6bd08208-edaa-4206-a918-f72a5cbdb70e",
        "6ecb1dbd-a6d1-4c48-9b10-9546dac49a52",
        "75147d3f-59d6-457c-a796-7a48ab82f299",
        "2a8ce45c-ca5c-4d5b-b4e4-61eefab1b5d4",
        "a28c4f10-a39e-4606-b4d0-671a375ab7d8",
        "7a2cda7b-741c-4f49-98fe-98a3070d756f",
        "bdc85176-e307-4056-8a6b-0a3e3e927306",
        "2ad764d5-7f92-4c81-b443-ec1900abe922",
        "50bb47cf-6e5f-4953-99dd-9d4f6132d0a3",
        "b8869142-c92a-4e4e-b705-d3387a64275a",
        "ae1277d6-6a6e-4e81-8326-98599e8aa3be",
        "7b470174-c8e4-42f1-9bea-5374c4c2bc15",
        "39b8a586-65b1-4b08-b5d8-74b5871e4b8a",
        "88876ae0-1761-4b84-b9d6-7410862813e0",
        "3c2fe989-0d8f-49e1-be31-6c37b4debacb",
        "85160bf7-9c01-4779-8805-1fef39daa1c1",
        "7101af0e-6810-4d17-9c8a-382567e63e36",
        "a932c393-2152-4a5f-8dbf-87e139b7c8b8",
        "5052d96e-a0b7-4ed7-b618-0699e3b70093",
        "e5171ffb-3778-4773-bea7-c280e0b66cde",
        "52a48a73-7c73-4048-bffe-62fc692a0c93",
        "e9ba383d-b737-44c2-82a4-efcb9fff0fc5",
        "d4bbc963-0140-4ab7-9c12-629ef79e4746",
        "9a65dc39-d79f-49d9-9826-747929354839",
        "b0f9e9f0-37e2-467f-b89e-45f255cc26ba",
        "589a2793-5550-4b5d-8019-a054ae205a57",
        "68cd7737-591d-4d88-b20b-0759d757133b",
        "a069585f-26f4-4704-994a-3b7c7fb1156e",
        "929f96e9-d46e-44ad-9664-68875e2df1ee",
        "4ae3ee16-8982-40c0-a6de-c034dcbe843f",
        "07378735-11ef-4ae7-872d-f33555ae1d22",
        "81e0234c-0ffa-47d7-98ce-99881248089b",
        "45c19c74-5e2b-4b7c-a344-f4cb25ab117e",
        "a6b09abb-8084-4528-a1f7-85b58085b875",
        "a9216955-3ca0-4733-bb84-70ea73022ceb",
        "f501cc54-6bca-400d-b4f2-ae0bee01a600",
        "b6c8b3e5-3e6d-4a54-a28e-ad2fbca3372b",
        "417255ca-0b7c-4413-94cb-276b038cf835",
        "20e7519b-d484-4639-b546-fa91cc0360e8",
        "91000105-aa6d-4f13-9c58-0f5b51c3ce3d",
        "fbf2f4e3-7427-4246-8d80-1bafec6a4c21",
        "aa31ff2b-3aab-4f2e-977d-6c08adc86e0b",
        "542bc51f-01ed-4947-bb5c-0c417e9f4746",
        "054cc5bc-d8c7-4254-9107-00d81d1c5b93",
        "62af7b8e-502d-4b45-b7ab-06aca55c7b19",
        "405d839d-de51-4925-9d17-dea81f3efa2e",
        "b5c3df99-722b-486f-a4a6-a27284d1c57f",
        "a4f603a8-0f06-4907-8577-d542a3bd089d",
        "839760cb-6b17-4d4f-bfc9-569f2eab8c9d",
        "dc1df630-85ca-46d7-9820-ee4821232e69",
        "88c138ee-87c9-4217-a85f-25e2357cc4fb",
        "ef25d976-ed8c-4895-9a62-651c8268563e",
        "afa1bc4a-997e-482c-a78f-aa5227aa5020",
        "14a37393-021a-4373-a6d3-6d6e149cb700",
        "b3683698-91e5-4c00-8d93-04b4caa61f46",
        "0fe9a2e7-84c7-4b5f-84c4-bb5a3325351a",
        "9429011a-99ed-4d91-b14c-00fd4e43f8a8",
        "73a5c1e2-7628-494f-8cba-96407fcaf16f",
        "53bf5a08-7b15-43cb-af97-a29603cbd406",
        "72505115-f9fa-4d57-a7f9-2e9ad7b62f86",
        "698f57a5-a530-4558-a747-80a7d0155451",
        "6abfdced-eae2-4557-b706-2e18ae9d4db7",
        "23a16a3e-e7a9-46b8-9ba7-eee5f6fd5656",
        "1a94559f-f492-4b5a-8608-e63de34dbc44",
        "c3c01bc0-57bc-4d01-bf17-cebcd28d4ad4",
        "2577525d-f6c2-4e76-b0c5-6a3260d87fcf",
        "32b4112f-726f-461b-8988-7d68a25e33f4",
        "b785bed3-71aa-49db-805f-977286afac9d",
        "bdea96e2-1d09-4caf-82d2-f04c44fb7441",
        "097f9758-1635-41b9-8b4e-d0b3ea6504a6",
        "ec18fff7-fda3-4c22-9273-3b1cb6408145",
        "4b6534d3-51d6-4c40-9e75-421815f5dd92",
        "26d2318b-85bb-40ba-a1bf-13ae625e2966",
        "d2a52ce4-7ca3-4b74-b2e2-841b4a7425d8",
        "f2232848-5cc5-49cf-8ec0-4d6786b7e126",
        "747d3ccd-cfcd-4bca-93cb-4615073cab56",
        "eeb37462-e43c-4b05-9c63-c3bb6c34eede",
        "3c6c3806-1dbb-488b-b52b-33dc47eb7248",
        "baaea14a-3101-4c05-bd13-899ac933c7b7",
        "24bbcdfc-7370-4348-a112-2635a01801c4",
        "70ffa7ad-6e88-49e5-b833-ab102083e88d",
        "341b7523-599b-4e43-b058-0ef2ec71918d",
        "044d5e6e-1b77-4a8b-aa07-e6b0ca140391",
        "557ced1a-84b0-4dea-92db-e786f85847f5",
        "0164ed97-8e6f-41a2-b1f2-a1bab95e0b6d",
        "8fce2dbe-57d2-49d2-bc0a-caf12cf8c36f",
        "cedddbcd-da6e-44ef-8c4f-bf5743423171",
        "af1ff483-f2f9-40aa-996f-03eb167c16d2",
        "882db295-79ea-4626-ade6-294d90824c20",
        "4f78b3da-a0f9-4acf-aa28-eb122bfe1dbb",
        "5ef861ff-abab-4c28-90d0-0117c6432a87",
        "9c52d54d-ed92-4258-89ff-4194c8621bd1",
        "6d03fa3b-aa23-40ea-8da9-82c7699efbb6",
        "206e3e1d-798d-4144-8753-51f6363cce31",
        "d1576014-04c1-4c39-aa1d-0613effac8c4",
        "14fd6641-62cd-4fc1-b189-653255b1c55f",
        "0a1e55d1-cbd1-42d8-ba67-71af390903bc",
        "ad39853e-2f1d-4e0c-93d9-7bf0510aa79d",
        "b3cb3aa6-6c5e-4e3a-9d58-403969ef1bcb",
        "81b1a3b0-8cbd-4e46-9ba9-a31a640a2247",
        "f9052a42-2a9b-4f95-8000-921f62847bb0",
        "166fd7f4-5636-43db-831d-a4ab9305f3a9",
        "72c8de6a-0092-4156-a1c6-4b8550f6ca0d",
        "ca456cb5-ea1b-47e9-8a02-7579efd2a33e",
        "cba6dcf6-2156-49d6-959d-8b95ba0d8ef8",
        "1a628bc0-312f-495c-8461-67aa85c42aac",
        "b785bed3-71aa-49db-805f-977286afac9d",
        "bdea96e2-1d09-4caf-82d2-f04c44fb7441",
        "097f9758-1635-41b9-8b4e-d0b3ea6504a6",
        "ec18fff7-fda3-4c22-9273-3b1cb6408145",
        "4b6534d3-51d6-4c40-9e75-421815f5dd92",
        "26d2318b-85bb-40ba-a1bf-13ae625e2966",
        "d2a52ce4-7ca3-4b74-b2e2-841b4a7425d8",
        "f2232848-5cc5-49cf-8ec0-4d6786b7e126",
        "747d3ccd-cfcd-4bca-93cb-4615073cab56",
        "eeb37462-e43c-4b05-9c63-c3bb6c34eede",
        "3c6c3806-1dbb-488b-b52b-33dc47eb7248",
        "baaea14a-3101-4c05-bd13-899ac933c7b7",
        "24bbcdfc-7370-4348-a112-2635a01801c4",
        "70ffa7ad-6e88-49e5-b833-ab102083e88d",
        "341b7523-599b-4e43-b058-0ef2ec71918d",
        "044d5e6e-1b77-4a8b-aa07-e6b0ca140391",
        "557ced1a-84b0-4dea-92db-e786f85847f5",
        "0164ed97-8e6f-41a2-b1f2-a1bab95e0b6d",
        "8fce2dbe-57d2-49d2-bc0a-caf12cf8c36f",
        "cedddbcd-da6e-44ef-8c4f-bf5743423171",
        "af1ff483-f2f9-40aa-996f-03eb167c16d2",
        "882db295-79ea-4626-ade6-294d90824c20",
        "4f78b3da-a0f9-4acf-aa28-eb122bfe1dbb",
        "5ef861ff-abab-4c28-90d0-0117c6432a87",
        "9c52d54d-ed92-4258-89ff-4194c8621bd1",
        "6d03fa3b-aa23-40ea-8da9-82c7699efbb6",
        "206e3e1d-798d-4144-8753-51f6363cce31",
        "d1576014-04c1-4c39-aa1d-0613effac8c4"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "03a32dcc-5194-4c32-97a5-bc81d4f34e2b",
      "english": "What is ... in Arabic?",
      "arabic": " \u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0647\u0648 ... \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "children": [
        "7ce8045d-a605-436c-bc56-4df158ab1000",
        "abba1854-8d0a-4a48-a471-f27f8d0f2975",
        "2cb78e09-f2ac-4a4f-84f8-ff4debec304c",
        "a489c9b7-74a2-425a-b220-b0958728ba62",
        "89d7768e-0af2-4512-9086-2da98df0ef0a",
        "aa572085-3d52-48d9-b27f-71af741a2184",
        "75998669-0eba-44cc-b554-0e9fd0ee40d0",
        "b24a8c68-c5b7-4c14-9c6c-37d13d595839",
        "70a23f0a-229c-41c2-9d7d-6bf84bbf52ed",
        "2f905307-2024-49a4-a802-5b0a4aa693da",
        "c1f52a0e-9360-4f1c-b48f-cd4d657d1674",
        "de45cede-01b4-4911-89e6-562d6114e26e",
        "842f1fcb-6c7d-4939-951b-4413117d562d",
        "5520ad73-3338-4a34-a03d-3b48af9d37a6",
        "c17c9367-398a-4dfa-8c10-1f0c0589f3c9",
        "93440f42-c247-43e6-a6ec-1b56035347a9",
        "448dbc8f-cf7b-484d-a2dd-1743562dbe25",
        "992382c6-e3ef-4224-9d7c-ff326c47ddd7",
        "85d73bf7-e403-4752-ba92-68c5c506f92e",
        "27ffe04a-2a99-4d1e-bd11-0ea7028f7469",
        "125abce0-98ab-40da-9ce8-d29afa8dfb46",
        "1da8baf0-ae26-493b-81ea-89b3d840f611",
        "154e3050-0d89-4435-bcd6-ca59b0c4e027",
        "4295c0c8-8c92-4b07-b91f-bd503b553ab6",
        "7878defa-bc8d-4feb-8f7a-4ab964ac123f",
        "59d598ea-143a-40f8-960b-712f2ab13e45",
        "f52f2d43-3174-488b-8708-853b936bd709",
        "dac69a4a-b116-4c45-a2e8-f17f0e4ce31b",
        "09ccf0e6-6731-4d1c-bbde-bfe78968c371",
        "70fb6d34-06c6-4c78-9a0f-4e18c88dd98d",
        "4e2a9f7e-f3a6-4206-a297-6df4b5bdfe07",
        "406ca315-43c0-401d-97f9-17dd246c9e4d",
        "d31841d6-961e-4aee-a508-eabeb66b09f0",
        "1a360564-64b8-4d64-8e89-8def52bb7c2f",
        "37dadad6-023d-4114-b7c2-ea77e4c10446",
        "58e2bde4-b8a1-4160-a94c-ab936d83669f",
        "97d8d247-e899-4414-b6b9-cadead86317b",
        "17b498ca-dcd2-486b-969f-683d27a29d6a",
        "7e8de3b0-e698-4ecc-946a-dd5a8cf56a17",
        "ff5008a0-b7ae-4111-82a9-489147b3260c",
        "0959c32b-ec0e-4085-bb44-d86b20d91270",
        "7585342e-c890-4483-b36e-6a37bf98bfa6",
        "01697efc-8d65-4245-8261-543da7a3d74e",
        "c9dd76ff-e28e-4b2f-b540-be63b6da3b02",
        "76441557-ac82-47e3-87b7-efd27c649367",
        "7f99d0a7-bf5a-417b-90d7-b1229e745b6d",
        "2d1a2b3d-7262-465c-abcc-7064448cd4c5",
        "593cce9b-e253-4892-922e-35991f2650e2",
        "12eba276-657b-47c5-94c6-b1ef5fc59d4e",
        "f3ce9254-3c7a-40ab-aa1f-abe518af544e",
        "170363db-c251-4587-b209-e053902a6239",
        "4192089f-cd67-455a-8dbb-198e01c0f268",
        "a681eedc-b4c4-4a09-95f2-0f7ee3f74d06",
        "aa1aa3fc-a093-4e8e-a9d4-5cd13730410c",
        "77d1e3a8-4666-4dc1-b02c-784dd3ea19bf",
        "9cecdeaa-0c60-4e1a-812d-2c161d780345",
        "9f46f1e1-4bab-448a-9c07-9f2b66bac2d5",
        "8d7ac68d-665c-4c38-8f95-aae8308acd57"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "18ee23c2-161b-45f9-b31d-785698c9546b",
      "english": "What is ... in English?",
      "arabic": " \u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0647\u0648 ... \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "children": [
        "46abb951-7519-4239-8801-6e3dc63d531f",
        "5d2f6c5f-c8f7-44ea-87a2-ad16ca551a7d",
        "e4883e48-4f9e-4149-8471-2041ab6b973a",
        "3f5ba6d2-11c8-4a9d-964b-67ebf911cde4",
        "0d07ea02-1a30-43e5-8317-4029d9e309ab",
        "6675d699-59f0-4d59-98a0-626f1ebdd7ea",
        "4994378e-0856-4a6a-9e78-41d3413ba8ff",
        "c2977f20-54f8-475a-abbb-7a1493a3fbe1",
        "111a5a8a-7643-4bf2-84f8-457ed6644d4c",
        "dffc2cf3-57fb-4bf5-8ea3-6bdc84fd2548",
        "b90e6263-112a-4773-b388-84d4f6efd215",
        "7e1dad24-5e2f-4c10-a3b3-584f437f3011",
        "03a3c6fc-3588-4c79-aa73-d6b589ec5d8e",
        "1d897a62-2742-487b-af2f-2b02ecec263f",
        "32748d2e-9df6-497b-babb-08829745439e",
        "bfb208ad-77f7-42bf-bffe-403d05979f9f",
        "201c118b-5454-464b-bf8a-70b17f0b4bcb",
        "a7c7ee3e-0f5a-4904-bc22-1e4ce71f2ed9",
        "99054d4e-310d-488f-a0cd-73dff4c93681",
        "df51b213-2bbb-4f76-bd28-deb4e643355f",
        "c051a3a2-aaf2-4e41-ba66-4679513862e8",
        "f0a877ad-7540-4c71-8ad4-25a1e12247cb",
        "a4610104-f62f-47b1-8c2c-52c95f026925",
        "2d126e2b-f6bd-48cd-8850-3404ae90f7c4",
        "ae09f4ed-c1ac-41fe-ba94-e004482d78e1",
        "daf73659-fc0d-439a-83bd-57a65b9500e3",
        "3aa37caf-9bef-490d-a309-3efdbc9b102c",
        "c9644b8b-9230-4b9e-9f18-31a9e8041bfd",
        "03afa37a-b511-46a7-a653-7f72f28521bf",
        "610b1152-bf58-4383-848a-f6852b06884e",
        "745079ae-b523-4581-84d5-d02f2a20d025",
        "0a1e55d1-cbd1-42d8-ba67-71af390903bc",
        "ad39853e-2f1d-4e0c-93d9-7bf0510aa79d",
        "b3cb3aa6-6c5e-4e3a-9d58-403969ef1bcb",
        "81b1a3b0-8cbd-4e46-9ba9-a31a640a2247",
        "f9052a42-2a9b-4f95-8000-921f62847bb0",
        "166fd7f4-5636-43db-831d-a4ab9305f3a9",
        "72c8de6a-0092-4156-a1c6-4b8550f6ca0d",
        "ca456cb5-ea1b-47e9-8a02-7579efd2a33e",
        "cba6dcf6-2156-49d6-959d-8b95ba0d8ef8",
        "1a628bc0-312f-495c-8461-67aa85c42aac",
        "61fb354e-7e70-4058-9297-a26946fe7f9b",
        "0a1e55d1-cbd1-42d8-ba67-71af390903bc",
        "ad39853e-2f1d-4e0c-93d9-7bf0510aa79d",
        "b3cb3aa6-6c5e-4e3a-9d58-403969ef1bcb",
        "81b1a3b0-8cbd-4e46-9ba9-a31a640a2247",
        "f9052a42-2a9b-4f95-8000-921f62847bb0",
        "166fd7f4-5636-43db-831d-a4ab9305f3a9",
        "72c8de6a-0092-4156-a1c6-4b8550f6ca0d",
        "ca456cb5-ea1b-47e9-8a02-7579efd2a33e",
        "cba6dcf6-2156-49d6-959d-8b95ba0d8ef8",
        "1a628bc0-312f-495c-8461-67aa85c42aac",
        "5fc2dbe6-bbe8-4145-a9b0-09dc8ade4e79",
        "52a0c0da-a8e6-46ad-826b-7f69b9a36ac6",
        "0af373e2-5047-4a74-b983-aef92ec69563",
        "e5ac93b3-1535-473a-b02a-74f827a0bb14",
        "8654f473-9e71-49a0-8976-99776adb4bc4",
        "77f224cc-10d5-446e-b240-3e29cf48a475",
        "eac7edd9-03c7-4cfa-9e22-59a3dcddef48",
        "fadf3385-5234-405e-b7e8-5fa317cd7ffe",
        "2290f38a-0df2-4472-b355-46ac9f91db2e",
        "bae31f3b-a56b-462b-91c5-0be4d7169585",
        "b3bc06b4-0299-4b80-980c-9c5549c9af36",
        "c18c81bb-21d8-4049-a74c-112ec016612e",
        "a8ddf2d2-88e8-4acf-8805-99cab4f3f2fa",
        "020d5c5d-d5be-4550-ab6c-5a7363c25cbe"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "fd0bb6c6-486a-4dd2-ae40-5705c83a363e",
      "english": "One ... , please",
      "arabic": " \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f ... \u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "children": [
        "d7fe80ec-4c2b-4e73-97c5-cf7d56bea1e6",
        "12e43bcf-53e5-46cd-b915-79c360541118",
        "a7745e5a-0b59-47c9-9f62-bad69ab673c0",
        "4b325b2e-0619-4f85-95cf-7bae7136cd70",
        "6da2c303-a1a7-4f16-89cc-3ccfa615b481",
        "c9e33926-cde9-46f9-a2c7-35aabc371bd1",
        "e2290930-2439-400e-ad37-fc41b244b746",
        "62ddf8f4-524f-40d9-9983-6eaa86a005d4",
        "05ad2b72-31a7-4242-a5dc-8e5e0e6e698a",
        "6f81e444-67b1-45e2-9d95-121c8894994d",
        "ae6f3822-1e8a-4ae3-8eaa-a339b692fccb",
        "33fce108-8e9c-4ca0-a4a4-d459d0566ce7",
        "4aaccfe3-4d20-4ea7-9eb8-dc868c019ee7",
        "19c1f66c-09fd-4adb-ab6c-4fcb73de61b9",
        "ad263a6d-d116-4c27-a822-4e7eb574077f",
        "010a7e2f-64e8-4613-817f-fd29ec7ac48c",
        "aaa5f69c-6964-49b4-94a1-d99091152ee7",
        "a33f97cb-dc13-4dbd-913c-9dd6578c002c",
        "c6936187-374d-44bb-b7fb-58cc4d278256",
        "7687c3c6-9c0b-4340-902d-d369b9f45ade",
        "37d5c2a4-1d2b-4213-b50b-8f4918ad727c",
        "6557e65c-4146-4196-a5a1-586d15ace8fa",
        "b49274d4-3e3c-4d66-af08-de0678dc32c7",
        "6d75f594-f708-4bd6-b319-8e46853cf8b8",
        "940a677c-8139-4301-8711-76cfc7fdd423",
        "6702e4f5-f4e1-400d-9a94-d0690cf353aa",
        "cb3875b9-79f5-4c73-adff-7de9cd485710",
        "2a484b5a-b823-45e3-b070-7db54eb7f8fe",
        "45574aba-a704-4518-8a68-78316b8c1d3e",
        "ed476b4d-a4bc-4436-a59f-c8d360370174",
        "07592f99-573e-4bf2-8d7c-aa33f2e2a1de",
        "ee032187-c7f9-4df6-95c7-3f9cca472213",
        "60c04de8-8011-4858-a060-7ec13bd18137",
        "76661a07-1416-476d-a758-e6e25fad4a07",
        "89347647-d3ab-42e0-ba61-a62f7f2e2114",
        "5f6bb1e2-c12f-4eea-b5d4-2f1f4ca8934f",
        "d493117d-fdde-4567-ab2a-b51b3a71631c",
        "01d322ed-c121-4d9a-8db3-717e5ae699d3",
        "b5c416d3-3da8-47dd-ac79-4c45d46167a8",
        "dc2a7c11-b3c9-4254-b0b4-a4fc91eaf28c",
        "7083e676-20f9-45cb-a65c-3cb00643b7ad",
        "95c2dabc-03cb-4543-9016-2ff07f598ca1",
        "07a29459-73d6-405a-a884-3c322e8e5e9d",
        "940dafd7-1ed5-4b31-a44e-a2130d705eee",
        "d2874a91-c8d4-4838-be0b-56b22a955101",
        "c7f999a5-d6f7-4379-9759-a928c1becbe7",
        "75278dc1-3c53-4a97-94a8-99f465b88197",
        "39b36f2b-dd62-4b18-b32d-a0dc6664735d",
        "a5728901-1f8f-46aa-a3fc-8702e74fcfd0",
        "ae757f0c-0b4c-41ff-a15e-b779cb61d7ff",
        "270f7fa7-4a0f-4964-b7dc-2f933c595d4f",
        "9951bef9-6c65-4ce4-b914-d9fb9c97242a",
        "c87706b2-1703-48d2-bbaa-966bae68f20b",
        "847e1830-d779-4d4a-8227-3239d9b5c27d",
        "6583cd0f-1188-4ed4-84b3-5a250a452f9a",
        "505456c9-19ff-42da-a670-ca37db1ca471",
        "391608d8-4ae3-4c78-b420-f973cddc8d1e",
        "970f11c1-038c-4a41-a999-35a4dddb8b7a",
        "17b076f2-ce50-4be8-996a-be166ac1b3da",
        "55746fed-1dc4-4778-b789-c6030e3a3af4",
        "91340c39-6e71-4256-8a08-420f643be10b",
        "d2e73a8d-6226-4e88-bd7d-dbd1100bf3e5",
        "4d266f4d-c429-428a-adac-d02bc27855e9",
        "48ab680a-8238-4517-b203-5559648d209f",
        "d553ff74-e298-4895-93db-d1d092478a82",
        "45b35bee-3149-48ed-af8b-0a30078f9ede",
        "10d3b1fe-ff4c-403c-82dc-f1e9d35b6bae",
        "bdd58384-6270-4593-969d-d0f48eadb94a",
        "0d7ed3ca-ac9c-4f04-b6bf-10aa0da98481",
        "b9815fda-0495-44fd-801d-4a1bc35e2e31",
        "1fddf43a-0a5f-48cf-9a8e-615fff9a8024",
        "fe15298f-1dcf-47a3-be61-8a1045e08de8",
        "798c3985-3b82-4ffd-8ac8-8e5e2534ea54",
        "c8f46c62-e2db-471b-9fc9-648dde38e27c",
        "649b9eb6-85d5-4cd1-9ea4-88424c7441a5",
        "f9b6599e-46f9-45f4-acfe-8ff4466b86ee",
        "ed7df428-2d01-46e2-93e6-d67a7021e46c",
        "e8bd8dd8-9c59-4090-9d79-996722fe2e89",
        "c2a7dd9e-c083-4fdb-88d1-3798e8508811",
        "af465a4e-ddeb-4fbd-ab94-89aea36e0715",
        "363b206a-700e-46bc-b928-a400f6396da5",
        "2d53b7e0-8e35-4546-ba03-cca30e150b67",
        "58aea7de-a11f-43b3-a1f7-99bd90f926de",
        "150ded31-152d-4aa6-8b17-f5ff1a1e6768",
        "c99343d0-7e60-4f58-80bc-d93ccd88e5ed",
        "9739c17e-0de9-43e0-9ed7-e8d832ba3ae1",
        "4411437e-c6ef-4856-8410-46d75e017804",
        "6b63585d-ff44-4574-b315-6f845a9065e3"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "7661db80-a9f4-4567-9ea3-6fa09b418715",
      "english": "The same for me",
      "arabic": " \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "children": [
        "3318d6c2-1d7e-45dc-91b9-f8d5a0098316",
        "ad263a6d-d116-4c27-a822-4e7eb574077f",
        "010a7e2f-64e8-4613-817f-fd29ec7ac48c",
        "aaa5f69c-6964-49b4-94a1-d99091152ee7",
        "a33f97cb-dc13-4dbd-913c-9dd6578c002c",
        "c6936187-374d-44bb-b7fb-58cc4d278256",
        "7687c3c6-9c0b-4340-902d-d369b9f45ade",
        "37d5c2a4-1d2b-4213-b50b-8f4918ad727c",
        "6557e65c-4146-4196-a5a1-586d15ace8fa",
        "b49274d4-3e3c-4d66-af08-de0678dc32c7",
        "6d75f594-f708-4bd6-b319-8e46853cf8b8",
        "940a677c-8139-4301-8711-76cfc7fdd423",
        "6702e4f5-f4e1-400d-9a94-d0690cf353aa",
        "cb3875b9-79f5-4c73-adff-7de9cd485710",
        "2a484b5a-b823-45e3-b070-7db54eb7f8fe",
        "45574aba-a704-4518-8a68-78316b8c1d3e",
        "a52af56f-0710-4f2d-bd9d-6cf161a45344",
        "552cb5b1-3792-44af-b94a-eca92e1eccdd",
        "e4c5e858-e858-4694-9097-073caa2e9698",
        "b28f2a81-b1e1-440b-83b2-cea704d84143",
        "971e9aba-b7d0-4bd1-9115-16e7eb62ca02",
        "5c733ac5-5977-4178-8aee-0464e8e87481",
        "efaf8dbf-28e2-4057-a205-ca180623b60b",
        "e8ead551-d61a-4ab2-9f04-dab046a3e4cd",
        "d073c045-526c-45dd-a3bd-f799b779b4fa",
        "e5a8f3ea-1c52-442d-8906-468abecb7a96",
        "d2171589-b990-4ee8-9a04-7ef0ec0c8f98",
        "b69eeaad-7016-4cfc-9e62-a42ebb2ebbab",
        "d308f895-84d9-404a-a2b2-7e4cf3199de0",
        "f05a8761-93e3-44f6-9e5c-ff3af87a3865",
        "af28f19f-87c2-41af-be94-342466d72d67",
        "8b78a4c0-d31d-4d8f-96a9-9e5725be829d",
        "1a45e53b-8560-45eb-86d3-a0606828cf8a",
        "715f46d9-b10d-4148-a96a-d1c4f3103089",
        "ba45115e-c5d5-4c48-b495-b4ed7c724fd6",
        "4f400bad-3dc6-4a36-8180-efa61917728f",
        "59e37fe0-4413-4079-bca2-f0c0c4eb1201",
        "e79dbe6d-9f9f-4caa-a9bd-6141a3b616ac",
        "dd66f122-fa87-4521-9c04-247758b35159",
        "a459beb3-446f-4db2-87bf-f4e65abb13b0",
        "4fc90d78-f104-4db3-a0a9-cdee0fd7cd21",
        "b06419b2-ae01-4c37-bbd6-9e3f664adf81",
        "84826eea-8210-4493-b1b8-ebe5414098e5",
        "0268f77a-7c4b-4d05-b3f7-46f1332c122e",
        "77881060-6953-45a5-818d-4163a7bcd582",
        "705a3b19-36b4-4861-b41c-f5b85bc28e21",
        "cf85c9e2-1c7b-4c09-8975-29990517f04e",
        "c7a697e7-8117-4f86-ac44-448ddc39afdb",
        "36fd33c3-63a4-4eef-8b8f-8e57ce0a276a",
        "f1b18dd2-1890-4f02-bee3-927938c2239d",
        "042de914-b976-4a23-b3f4-45a1888e91f7",
        "994ecca9-c894-4ba6-bf67-2ea771822de9",
        "0b952cf4-6237-4a08-81de-95c00d57eede",
        "6ebd5dd4-8bef-452f-bd53-865f74181b39",
        "0d73dfc3-b27a-4058-a875-ed1ed0a4120e",
        "5b7f4421-eb78-420c-973c-6bd8c76682a7",
        "97532d06-35e9-4e45-83ac-35e4b1ebd28c",
        "da333997-e135-42ea-83f5-468e58390a79",
        "3292c3fb-2719-4c4b-99bb-3b397acb5349",
        "66fc9413-5b5d-4fbe-872c-4bd77a6eb761",
        "47f05ece-79ab-4afa-abcf-d5ae0011b5e5",
        "6f87284c-1ef3-491b-96db-44e83b6f4b03"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "21f7b7ab-0984-4248-9ece-934e7f0bc6ce",
      "english": "What is this?",
      "arabic": " \u062f\u0647 \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "children": [
        "3fb68111-7e76-4eab-8588-ca4b39791107",
        "a9bb672a-d1dd-4345-987f-166f2fa24647",
        "aad02481-1727-4228-b558-01d56d2a9f35",
        "6d060bc2-8fca-46bc-a1bd-953b5e0aa31b",
        "649b1bc4-eef2-468f-a1fd-d61858d38039",
        "40d933d9-0369-4452-bd58-f94dd17f731a",
        "d3574a3e-5fd1-4827-a1af-eb55db0a44ae",
        "759114e7-4b4b-4f4c-9fcc-b2906b33ec0a",
        "e4793cfb-1074-4233-8acf-e40c78b05000",
        "2c125e25-2ae0-4354-be84-966c15c79edd",
        "9fc53424-5fbc-41af-9e9f-a0260fe553e5",
        "f49bc753-df28-4a57-97ad-54c7a0e72f81",
        "472a1efe-cf3a-4e49-8649-243886185319",
        "6bb8afe6-a913-452e-b90c-f7aae08dc9e6",
        "c6a3b457-079f-46d7-941e-ca7a778c1bd4",
        "ddad7bcb-fd41-4890-890e-4d679e9f61f0",
        "37c9fe5f-82bb-4cfa-b838-2448893953bb",
        "79ca4670-53a7-4293-9e7e-8c1e531a7bf1",
        "841c6e03-4818-4e62-a237-f8e533b41186",
        "f0ccd4e4-4985-4fff-a97a-766763fa210d",
        "ce22b371-5008-4be8-9dae-44bc0ea68035",
        "99be3c20-30b4-4028-a8f8-d43ab53cbf76",
        "8e9e9bc4-f9dc-48d5-82d8-beabec9e5242",
        "86038069-a199-447b-a311-2673369ff58c",
        "81da9b53-83b9-402b-889d-3b4470aefe20",
        "930f4a53-8591-4cb9-9897-4cc3223f7b40",
        "adf3b50e-27d5-4582-98a4-e34800a17688",
        "b18fd132-a51a-450f-853f-5860600162ab",
        "3e244cdc-4aa0-4a30-99cb-002ac96ab120",
        "1dd34666-e836-4e2d-87ef-12fbee862962",
        "aad4eaa4-ec37-44d8-8674-9d28107c0498",
        "0a1e55d1-cbd1-42d8-ba67-71af390903bc",
        "ad39853e-2f1d-4e0c-93d9-7bf0510aa79d",
        "b3cb3aa6-6c5e-4e3a-9d58-403969ef1bcb",
        "81b1a3b0-8cbd-4e46-9ba9-a31a640a2247",
        "f9052a42-2a9b-4f95-8000-921f62847bb0",
        "166fd7f4-5636-43db-831d-a4ab9305f3a9",
        "72c8de6a-0092-4156-a1c6-4b8550f6ca0d",
        "ca456cb5-ea1b-47e9-8a02-7579efd2a33e",
        "cba6dcf6-2156-49d6-959d-8b95ba0d8ef8",
        "1a628bc0-312f-495c-8461-67aa85c42aac"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "d5e52908-5f96-49cc-b09a-7056f51d4f1a",
      "english": "Is this vegetarian?",
      "arabic": " \u062f\u0647 \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "children": [
        "390cc566-98bd-4027-8d7d-54ce7d4baa75",
        "eeaa2c68-8951-4c60-9c12-91821eb77af6",
        "81905c8a-5bc7-4dcb-93e8-f25d7744da8c",
        "048b2f00-50a5-4b7d-87d4-dfde7f390cf6",
        "91edf4e3-6809-49e9-9f2f-bcdf151e4ce2",
        "1318f204-9dc9-4d88-ac35-7769b72a4503",
        "b68be37f-13db-4fb1-9776-f96c5a8476e7",
        "9c8ba69e-096b-4489-b840-a11fc9bf76ea",
        "f953f027-7630-4362-95c9-3d6923b43d0a",
        "9d9465e7-56d7-4505-b975-50c81e6b4471",
        "b322c704-a29e-456d-be36-c36e60eae658",
        "2fa90d63-36c4-4a88-9ba1-c83760133ad7",
        "ec97a2b9-38b5-485e-be16-89684fb440ce",
        "6c2b12a3-5a54-4317-b8a3-28eef00e9c33",
        "81905c8a-5bc7-4dcb-93e8-f25d7744da8c",
        "048b2f00-50a5-4b7d-87d4-dfde7f390cf6",
        "91edf4e3-6809-49e9-9f2f-bcdf151e4ce2",
        "1318f204-9dc9-4d88-ac35-7769b72a4503",
        "b68be37f-13db-4fb1-9776-f96c5a8476e7",
        "9c8ba69e-096b-4489-b840-a11fc9bf76ea",
        "f953f027-7630-4362-95c9-3d6923b43d0a",
        "9d9465e7-56d7-4505-b975-50c81e6b4471",
        "b322c704-a29e-456d-be36-c36e60eae658",
        "2fa90d63-36c4-4a88-9ba1-c83760133ad7",
        "ec97a2b9-38b5-485e-be16-89684fb440ce"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "d27930ba-378f-4a08-8ad4-e44e8200ba77",
      "english": "Do you have ... ?",
      "arabic": " \u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643 ... \u061f",
      "children": [
        "8b655adf-2710-446e-90a9-b65d9ee05c01",
        "80b37855-5b70-4e93-9bc1-07642755739a",
        "9432e994-ea73-4e5d-8044-049711a049eb",
        "6a9055ec-6feb-422c-89c8-26803606a40d",
        "c1f49b26-e4c2-42e0-98ac-504b2511b573",
        "994b3126-fe7d-49c5-941c-36886aa336bb",
        "3848c9dc-92af-487f-adc3-9e7e25a2b344",
        "2feaf2d9-1082-4f09-b24c-82c15f20100c",
        "e7b1a435-f5ec-4378-9a29-2c824b4fc2d3",
        "ec75dcd4-27d3-40e7-9ed3-fc18ec93ad75",
        "ede40320-59d5-4c32-99f0-c5b282628538",
        "19e90ecb-5850-433c-b118-0f3c38de1583",
        "b71db25b-6075-4cda-ac57-a4e6ec74c7d7",
        "b86dda0a-08ee-4dc2-9cca-4a956123c23d",
        "332fe340-4528-4032-8b22-9ac07538ac2b",
        "f519aa26-ea79-4bea-9f26-8f3d90f4f9b4",
        "03a353a1-faa8-43d0-84fd-2d5f410a8dc7",
        "293800a7-89b3-4088-b44e-34cd0042a290",
        "6c4075b5-99ed-423f-a0f5-6733f6ebe271",
        "84053b09-3919-41f6-b711-c00a5fa37d3e",
        "969d6c50-59ca-4777-b2d4-e042810dddfc",
        "0fa6115e-7305-4c92-840a-9d802ab8bb94",
        "1a2f64d8-b186-4650-8047-fed1d5b4fefa",
        "fbb3d3ba-0f36-488a-a2ad-11472a47d19a",
        "4100a07f-571b-4182-b3c9-b1cbe0a64a6d",
        "31cda47a-9982-4b8c-9f84-51d21834f57f",
        "cda54dd5-2e5b-482c-a513-eab4e78a94d0",
        "3a76eaeb-cfc0-4a30-aca5-9deba37b1903",
        "0a83391d-582b-468b-ace6-e03cf174db9e",
        "8c19301e-bdba-4b75-b264-44af0a987292",
        "897133b2-1c0c-4008-99de-93b57f0a268f",
        "05e8597d-827c-48d2-8ccb-bd5ec9aebfbc",
        "03b22b38-62ff-4330-b782-a124a249d11c",
        "02612ebc-29a2-4a28-a4a3-0c602a025e5e",
        "2646d72a-2be1-4be7-8ad3-a552dcf8af33",
        "ebf4b2a2-149e-4e8e-a2a5-1e60d34bb618",
        "e29baf21-f219-4a32-ab6b-7079ab335b07",
        "b409e370-37c7-4a11-a998-d2eab2f6646e",
        "78db678c-8599-4c06-8426-542c6458eb9c",
        "57cbf3bf-910f-4471-92d4-123dd972f365",
        "3c0ee624-36ea-461a-ab11-fd57773d00f1",
        "303add07-bcd7-4ffb-b33c-a4cfaf3b86dc",
        "2d6a52b6-19c0-4b9d-8080-aacb630f9e64"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "4cf55960-1887-4f52-8eb7-542b64868c45",
      "english": "The menu, please",
      "arabic": " \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "children": [
        "e779b459-b037-451e-bd19-bd03793d54be",
        "ad263a6d-d116-4c27-a822-4e7eb574077f",
        "010a7e2f-64e8-4613-817f-fd29ec7ac48c",
        "aaa5f69c-6964-49b4-94a1-d99091152ee7",
        "a33f97cb-dc13-4dbd-913c-9dd6578c002c",
        "c6936187-374d-44bb-b7fb-58cc4d278256",
        "7687c3c6-9c0b-4340-902d-d369b9f45ade",
        "37d5c2a4-1d2b-4213-b50b-8f4918ad727c",
        "6557e65c-4146-4196-a5a1-586d15ace8fa",
        "b49274d4-3e3c-4d66-af08-de0678dc32c7",
        "6d75f594-f708-4bd6-b319-8e46853cf8b8",
        "940a677c-8139-4301-8711-76cfc7fdd423",
        "6702e4f5-f4e1-400d-9a94-d0690cf353aa",
        "cb3875b9-79f5-4c73-adff-7de9cd485710",
        "2a484b5a-b823-45e3-b070-7db54eb7f8fe",
        "45574aba-a704-4518-8a68-78316b8c1d3e",
        "848daddf-cd5b-4196-b71a-f5065c6c1940",
        "04377526-2341-4718-9bea-2efbf73374dd",
        "4447920c-5dec-4b0c-a70a-043a79f4fb50",
        "d642e7ba-5056-4b3f-b53c-ed3625011f16",
        "fa916044-fa75-4828-ba9f-d8e53bb8b5b7",
        "f8171dff-a838-4a39-8298-c3f9d4ad8a7e",
        "709d9e89-fc8c-4f82-be32-67a7b6454118",
        "97d4ca36-2100-42f4-8f6e-67f298f7dafe",
        "ea201d47-f39a-46e4-910a-6a3935556ddb",
        "7db137b5-bb33-4527-a9c2-0fd3a9721504",
        "2ade2f85-f80e-4073-9fc0-80401754538b",
        "8f3c09b6-4b18-4740-bfd9-0284dbf844f0",
        "17568eda-f9f6-443b-b026-bf853589cb22",
        "05da2723-ed58-4988-bae8-465889486fcd",
        "fecb87a3-1af6-4b1c-bec7-36f22f105002",
        "1d3fc00f-4075-4b69-bb48-d0647f2b0546",
        "f206d1aa-d11d-4b41-b705-83d41ff68e9c",
        "bba8ca8f-9aed-4c8b-97cc-8d50daa7f7ea",
        "a6b206bf-be0f-49fa-b81d-0beb69548682",
        "2ee83d61-6391-4ce6-910e-a7917d1eac65",
        "85b5adbc-7284-423b-9b53-4e94f4c5a3b2",
        "6fb802f4-a14a-4051-8c17-7155d707d7c7",
        "504a7d62-3dd6-4d31-ac0d-5008c9796f41",
        "f56ce19b-b26e-468b-bdd5-1d2b38c6990a",
        "d7626aef-91a0-4d2c-9d1b-dcc3f69722b8",
        "0f067a9a-95cb-4302-9603-65e62cfd561e",
        "7ab46e55-b7bf-4cbd-9eaa-b068a9ae8e5f",
        "20459c76-5251-4d4f-9a89-ed805b1f3a15",
        "fb04ce47-a91e-455a-874a-c1bc0b7837f2",
        "6652a507-fbd8-4e86-a9d2-7fcc8737f03e",
        "17db4064-c63e-4248-8c1a-9fbba469a70a",
        "4e98b52f-f992-4843-9ae8-82ff54a201fb",
        "89fe76b1-d8b0-43ef-a2fc-14ece42135d7",
        "f0c080d2-7ac0-4a31-97e9-0a215c15f245"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "86a21ac3-b3f6-41b8-8fd6-2aacdf6c582c",
      "english": "Not very spicy, please",
      "arabic": " \u0645\u0634 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "children": [
        "021f7c0e-4fcf-492a-ada2-ad38a002536b",
        "a5928533-9274-47b7-87d1-c43733de2703",
        "683b883e-3a8d-46e3-bd54-7f4d764c4909",
        "9b8a95a6-b389-4fb7-ac1e-087bf05213a0",
        "09789663-aedc-4dc0-a022-c50adcd969fb",
        "6c3b4a9a-5013-428c-aec9-3e8bc724da93",
        "355502c9-ef88-4cb7-90cb-48fb78f93db8",
        "16cf3b0e-6eb2-4113-a4e8-522143b954dc",
        "e226615a-0b6a-425e-b63d-44946ed05a05",
        "4b1f4d8a-bb84-4e14-aefa-dfe694d59311",
        "7e52c4a2-6a30-4584-8b94-f6478bea260c",
        "34ccb016-1136-4604-80da-9d4b3d00bd55",
        "58bc6c0c-cbd4-45b8-aafd-875800e19a28",
        "80751424-2d8f-4f04-94c8-5f90084dbd9a",
        "5092ba8c-3b68-432f-89a9-4622178c4d2d",
        "6c8b613a-134d-44f8-b786-12c98be15da5",
        "cfd27df9-0ff2-4d0a-99c1-bac6593d6387",
        "02d37635-fe6f-49f2-a9dd-07eeaaaf9015",
        "39f76b55-9b11-4f1c-8e3a-688929dafbab",
        "f42678ca-0392-4de3-b597-17b8cb171266",
        "7566862a-bfdf-473a-8d2b-f14810973de3",
        "28643eb8-971c-42c2-8938-da4b655e5f9e",
        "f670a9f3-2b27-49e9-83ea-ec11ad8ca44b",
        "963820fc-22f2-49c2-bfaf-ff43f909371b",
        "ef32f195-bc64-4b9c-b8d9-204dee167c04",
        "e26ebb58-b87a-42c8-8a70-42fea95fa7b2",
        "bda5f8d0-3f67-4616-99b2-223345c87f3a",
        "2be37cc1-0a88-4e61-9717-efec58dcc555",
        "ca137573-4a72-4d61-857f-e76299831a62",
        "cda73416-13ce-495b-9431-00b74fac49c9",
        "b40839a6-f3dd-4b22-81d8-347c853ab09f",
        "528be5df-6e2b-4391-8a57-a6ef617dcd68",
        "18a4567a-9814-4d2a-b425-94bc4eac5b3b",
        "a2a6daed-045f-41cc-b819-f2d1fe1aae78",
        "52794d39-90e5-409b-bdee-50e5bf73d6e0",
        "51e15de3-75ed-4b33-9446-ee306aec2d4d",
        "525198b1-453c-4986-ba08-41a4a1076612",
        "2512f543-135a-4e13-93ba-1f448d75c720",
        "7dcbaf03-6c77-4e25-ac17-fae0d354b81b",
        "c079f1c0-0387-4d6d-97b7-b75fa88693f9",
        "9b2fc5e3-b7d9-469b-8481-951475a2bc66",
        "2fb8d8a5-0e17-41a0-b71a-be4a1066d919",
        "36dd7b52-3ded-4123-be95-72f79022c3ef",
        "52ca3934-2e2d-49c4-84dc-89507ca0d590",
        "b4e1b7c0-8e67-4e35-9ca0-ed7b4318e7bf",
        "9c46ad02-a337-4b1c-be15-ec97dcdc73e4",
        "1db7359d-2955-4e75-bc35-53c22f99402a",
        "30fa2a83-e9ba-4342-8d13-f5b71a6cf66c",
        "ec0e3076-244b-46d6-a042-f9486ab8eb30",
        "e353ad27-3dee-4545-bbea-f2a30db6eccc",
        "94839ded-123f-4cca-84ed-a7df51b16031",
        "6c5a7fbf-0b56-4124-a766-04aa2496ce7b",
        "e21830b7-7f4d-4da2-9a62-8cc50516aacb",
        "5a7ce46c-da1a-483d-b571-f7e3206c1c07",
        "eb2ea473-2624-41e6-9ec0-7347213d3535",
        "23c28e79-0fc2-47f4-a276-210e208f3330",
        "f9ead455-d761-41fd-b416-be313e1a9aa3",
        "c8d002df-4851-4380-917e-eec9e97820cd",
        "f97a2a33-75b2-4651-95ba-e8704f968dfd",
        "977afa2c-1616-4780-ae5a-45029d590228",
        "d2874a91-c8d4-4838-be0b-56b22a955101",
        "c7f999a5-d6f7-4379-9759-a928c1becbe7",
        "75278dc1-3c53-4a97-94a8-99f465b88197",
        "39b36f2b-dd62-4b18-b32d-a0dc6664735d",
        "a5728901-1f8f-46aa-a3fc-8702e74fcfd0",
        "ae757f0c-0b4c-41ff-a15e-b779cb61d7ff",
        "270f7fa7-4a0f-4964-b7dc-2f933c595d4f",
        "9951bef9-6c65-4ce4-b914-d9fb9c97242a",
        "c87706b2-1703-48d2-bbaa-966bae68f20b",
        "847e1830-d779-4d4a-8227-3239d9b5c27d",
        "6583cd0f-1188-4ed4-84b3-5a250a452f9a",
        "505456c9-19ff-42da-a670-ca37db1ca471",
        "391608d8-4ae3-4c78-b420-f973cddc8d1e",
        "970f11c1-038c-4a41-a999-35a4dddb8b7a",
        "17b076f2-ce50-4be8-996a-be166ac1b3da",
        "55746fed-1dc4-4778-b789-c6030e3a3af4",
        "91340c39-6e71-4256-8a08-420f643be10b",
        "d2e73a8d-6226-4e88-bd7d-dbd1100bf3e5",
        "4d266f4d-c429-428a-adac-d02bc27855e9",
        "48ab680a-8238-4517-b203-5559648d209f",
        "d553ff74-e298-4895-93db-d1d092478a82",
        "45b35bee-3149-48ed-af8b-0a30078f9ede",
        "10d3b1fe-ff4c-403c-82dc-f1e9d35b6bae",
        "bdd58384-6270-4593-969d-d0f48eadb94a",
        "0d7ed3ca-ac9c-4f04-b6bf-10aa0da98481",
        "b9815fda-0495-44fd-801d-4a1bc35e2e31",
        "1fddf43a-0a5f-48cf-9a8e-615fff9a8024",
        "fe15298f-1dcf-47a3-be61-8a1045e08de8",
        "798c3985-3b82-4ffd-8ac8-8e5e2534ea54",
        "c8f46c62-e2db-471b-9fc9-648dde38e27c"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "8c0a926e-c41c-4608-ae38-4bc313de215c",
      "english": "Two Turkish coffee, light, with a bit of sugar",
      "arabic": " \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u060c \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0639 \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "children": [
        "8cca6594-5203-43ba-8d82-03a16f36033b",
        "14d257a3-99d9-4738-88e7-d24a2f580091",
        "81017a23-b090-470c-a1dd-7129c5c2d6d1",
        "0cfefa82-ea25-412c-aa7a-11cab42e07dc",
        "fcc87524-327f-49fd-8ba0-f37f7905210a",
        "648f0d07-d0d5-482a-83c2-a58e982d5cbc",
        "2d32fadb-9af1-475c-882a-dc576921ea7f",
        "107e65a1-43d4-412f-85a8-be7aed77a258",
        "eff55821-35c5-4c30-8b63-b02df1c1b554",
        "913b4f9a-1a85-4799-be99-be5f51ba4ec0",
        "2631b052-f8a5-4ec1-8275-9b938579e72e",
        "88b00d91-a378-4d56-95a4-0eee7b6fe9db",
        "532e4c9a-31bd-4e06-83f7-c340a7d3964f",
        "201bc063-e59a-4e5c-a758-5112c8c17023",
        "29674e6f-257e-45d1-9d9f-d8aba8ce816f",
        "455a7baf-3b9b-4caa-a3c9-9a3863ec7e1e",
        "f7808013-a135-4b70-9abf-080b26c0834c",
        "c4bc5305-6a4a-46b6-904e-03effb3a49a4",
        "1de82720-a9ef-4574-be6c-c019d7953732",
        "e56fcd58-ea7c-4676-988e-7180a2ff5599",
        "89898a3f-ebb4-4530-81b3-76810f9efb0e",
        "ef84ac14-6a59-4df4-8ee4-34360f893bf8",
        "bf540a30-2add-468f-a243-cfa5beb82fa0",
        "8acfa1a8-03a9-40c8-b394-58b8df7b88d3",
        "c83cf3da-5bad-403b-868a-bf97447dd510",
        "0e719f5b-2ac1-41aa-8acb-57e806e0173e",
        "974832de-8e8d-4332-8849-51162509b7aa",
        "d1d1a43f-dd41-4ea1-b5a3-e1e684c17d9a",
        "68de1422-7f45-4770-9880-960ce9af30a4",
        "92630a94-ce12-49a0-840e-f5a5ff5e61b6",
        "9413f878-5732-46a1-94de-0c2ccfb9852e",
        "c999b4db-9e37-4b93-98a7-ee9ac2838b4b",
        "475a4664-2ed3-40b9-b101-5ff2315ae95b",
        "112c7bcc-a92d-4187-b7b9-5a4f7c3fbf47",
        "158c696f-04ec-41b7-bb73-6572a9d4d7f1",
        "cf1e738c-d91f-4b68-81ab-d75ea929391d",
        "743bef35-3123-476d-a80c-b9fe8c83ca16",
        "93f7be07-3f8f-432e-bfd1-a2a02bb465bf",
        "46d242e2-a337-4bbb-a640-720e3cea948e",
        "0a217f9b-a1b2-4143-b095-83ae4857b599",
        "a5bcf53a-58b6-4d87-bef4-6e060e95b328",
        "8af322ec-2eee-4e8d-b35f-514f53d9c17b",
        "e5f32463-6e74-44c3-b7c3-9a4397227b9d",
        "c0b8e039-4dca-4dd0-bdb4-991a40d2ccb1",
        "36915304-50ff-4362-9773-0ea1b5ce1ec6",
        "f1f7aad2-6933-41a7-8166-f1732475eaa0",
        "c999b4db-9e37-4b93-98a7-ee9ac2838b4b",
        "475a4664-2ed3-40b9-b101-5ff2315ae95b",
        "112c7bcc-a92d-4187-b7b9-5a4f7c3fbf47",
        "158c696f-04ec-41b7-bb73-6572a9d4d7f1",
        "cf1e738c-d91f-4b68-81ab-d75ea929391d",
        "743bef35-3123-476d-a80c-b9fe8c83ca16",
        "93f7be07-3f8f-432e-bfd1-a2a02bb465bf",
        "46d242e2-a337-4bbb-a640-720e3cea948e",
        "0a217f9b-a1b2-4143-b095-83ae4857b599",
        "a5bcf53a-58b6-4d87-bef4-6e060e95b328",
        "8af322ec-2eee-4e8d-b35f-514f53d9c17b",
        "e5f32463-6e74-44c3-b7c3-9a4397227b9d",
        "c0b8e039-4dca-4dd0-bdb4-991a40d2ccb1",
        "36915304-50ff-4362-9773-0ea1b5ce1ec6",
        "671ac760-a074-4212-9062-8ec503f2add0",
        "b9c1f6fc-08d4-436a-b326-e0ae6a367385",
        "ca84268f-dc5e-4e07-93e1-32764a9b1a83",
        "aefec3fb-2d83-4959-96e0-cc9a713a835a",
        "4eb0b02c-0ba9-47f3-88e4-bfb02467ac72",
        "72eda04f-4c51-4f2b-a991-e8c047d35fc3",
        "8fc30b0c-477f-4a0c-ba2b-22817b917526",
        "3d8406f6-f4e4-4c87-8c4d-a2a7e46fef25",
        "763b33de-77e7-40b5-a7ff-c5a8a038067d",
        "588f01ef-47fb-465a-97a0-c3c9d680ff41",
        "511b6689-2d04-49d6-acb6-4f0a74b2acee",
        "27907774-40d0-4a20-ade0-0339334174c7",
        "4d22edcf-8165-48a2-8128-7c5b04b420c1",
        "b4afb04f-a60d-4a44-b477-37a9a190d705",
        "0fd806b2-8981-42a3-87e8-595c0d5d07c7",
        "f1e93e0f-d63e-44ba-9311-62772e439536",
        "49f859fe-9298-4d49-9472-c5d297664499",
        "b3e0d39b-7db4-4bbf-9221-636fd523b633",
        "28e74620-7196-4b89-a0fd-2868ab4eebca",
        "07f31653-898a-4b77-bcc4-d635d084022b",
        "a5b067f8-c303-4c75-9964-160b8541c518",
        "6cb11e78-4032-4a60-a56e-0c83af78bcc5",
        "2825ad02-b6d2-4628-8693-aaa341b19166",
        "09c491f8-a403-4510-9649-c55616490c8c",
        "3217e271-ca67-4959-a055-2bcd1b21028a",
        "1198ff99-d79f-4d25-bf3a-85f94b980307",
        "a478ee0e-e6ad-498a-b5bc-328a9f397470",
        "fd150bef-874a-41ec-8182-8d16377d2866",
        "ac94c6f5-9402-47f5-9d69-754aa56fd639",
        "c54f2b79-42e7-4089-8133-fd0d758a18ee",
        "8b92c06c-69d9-4a8d-812c-e13979c37fdb",
        "d99ff5a5-6dec-4bb1-9304-f58116742076",
        "652b60f0-05c0-492b-8567-d3bae236c8a3",
        "8852a39d-b902-46c2-ae28-1dd8826d6aa6",
        "1cb782d7-4a37-44cd-9590-937ff548fdf2",
        "83be290d-3e09-40bf-9571-e9dbdede4e14",
        "ea831637-fffb-4b65-850b-38e3a21e7ff7",
        "1c42f9cf-583c-40bd-8961-a1ce8b6c40d3",
        "6b4bf3fd-646d-46ed-a5ef-a452ae3eee2b",
        "09723412-df8f-41cd-9631-c0b1bada3bc6",
        "a3353611-c932-4fe1-ad7c-ba19eae6a6ee",
        "330991c7-c013-424e-a13a-066aa149586e",
        "5e303c0e-0a8e-429c-8c96-77da802bcfa8",
        "692bbae1-3414-4df2-be4f-5d85d69be72a",
        "b4c424e3-8e38-4e6a-a631-4c98990bdc00",
        "e0fcb30d-3a53-450e-ab05-8bc52b54ece4",
        "39448f83-6632-42ea-8b5f-3b5e3222524e",
        "b9765dea-9373-4840-96d0-f6f85862a3a5",
        "89d88f0e-3a3c-42ad-8c94-ffc84b787ed9",
        "d964bb3a-b95b-43af-8145-c2a0e2d32c72",
        "0dd7230e-1d83-4058-86a8-c6d5184602a2",
        "8f087cf2-f44d-4edc-8df9-98666963608b",
        "e7c57532-c3ee-4b5b-9ad9-b8ce0f79cfda",
        "c94647e5-d715-4c46-984a-b2ea70a4fd4e",
        "04d72b54-5795-46c1-b2cb-52ffbe6b11a7",
        "d2fbfa5f-4b87-4d1c-932b-9201bacaa32e",
        "3889091a-0924-41b1-9bdc-74565770a741",
        "9f341784-6c7e-4baa-bc2c-4084b901f1ab",
        "4b8c42a7-946c-4dad-8478-aba00d2c8c5c",
        "31c2e442-5419-4c60-bd68-0f32bffd5483",
        "7c2935e9-f634-4635-9e86-cc22923c0356",
        "1fd79693-4fc3-4a2a-bccb-f2a6604c278b",
        "17211823-15fc-480e-925f-5e2b16f0b339",
        "98a2d2c2-c152-4626-85d8-12d3a3d25741",
        "bd4fc18f-d6db-43b3-b1cd-895a1f468f89",
        "f2f0b7b8-d777-4af9-be95-a61b32b2bc6b",
        "8c3b7e11-6ad1-4598-8727-a025b38e86c7",
        "a69c1d2d-35dc-4b49-a024-b0eb21ca76c8",
        "a7f9ea89-be46-494c-805b-50beb4b490ae",
        "e4a0b43d-214b-45d3-9f80-a02b85484517",
        "e1126da9-621a-400c-8236-7ab970a3273c",
        "ac87f172-2e9f-494d-b09f-1d5d04924b80",
        "9031ec1a-694c-4238-bf3d-d69a6a063edf",
        "86bb105d-37e4-4c9a-86d1-2235f49e6546",
        "d9d0634a-deae-4625-bd97-08dbaae12865",
        "44927631-7437-4d22-aa8d-061314084d6b",
        "76be179a-5b6f-490d-aed0-f3665992d71e",
        "2ee7429c-50e7-4bfe-a945-6f42396b3779",
        "c9a94318-57a7-46db-89a3-76c4e0fb94a6",
        "8f8b507c-6f3b-4c04-b9bb-e9844e4bf4bc",
        "d06750bf-a881-41d6-ab28-aa055bc20179",
        "4f900f85-fea8-49e2-971a-362484603171",
        "04c6e74a-638f-49cc-83fc-2278e93d93a5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "c7939227-b8ba-4c4d-928e-d42d09ca3127",
      "english": "Can I pay with card?",
      "arabic": " \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "children": [
        "9e14f015-465f-42f3-abb3-4de8f2474944",
        "7d583371-74c0-47ee-bd2b-4df91563991f",
        "fbec6129-2662-4921-983f-5f59c305b5ac",
        "a0bcfd68-73ed-4ead-b743-381def17eb4e",
        "7cf2ea67-73b4-4144-b7c2-6e969c17306f",
        "baaec0e1-d29e-4ba8-90f2-5094afeef096",
        "85e27fd7-d349-408d-a51b-324fd57b4ec1",
        "3eaa92a7-9fe2-4709-9188-cc7c0210b985",
        "4479813f-a76a-4f5c-9d44-e3d36eace4aa",
        "c5c4de1f-907c-42d4-bc8b-05e1f107bdfc",
        "898303a9-ff0c-41cf-b5d7-cb569430f626",
        "d9b44e40-e3f9-4ca0-9d06-23f37be919da",
        "2b934a62-2413-4c95-9799-4daf8e7be00c",
        "eec08ed3-c439-47ae-bf60-44dd85795631",
        "4d4a766a-6522-45be-a906-7e78e2c685cc",
        "5a493d28-e658-4da2-b985-3d0a130871a7",
        "bf9e9dd1-eaee-4eb9-a909-e4d1aa0fb57d",
        "9c90d283-06ef-4683-b746-13ea89e16e86",
        "6c885a0f-711c-469f-aed6-8dc17622366b",
        "dd72ba81-795d-494a-8407-fb975bc45f88",
        "96174e4c-0410-493f-902d-3ee8ed594a83",
        "76ae5e6f-74ee-49e3-844f-5764354996c6",
        "f209da71-5aae-448e-87e4-7cfe77a799c2",
        "6d862cae-5bf4-41d5-abb8-d87e73544933",
        "86d16023-f81a-4ec7-b62b-9ec389f16e6e",
        "1616c3a0-8875-4152-b710-b35a9506e016",
        "5cb018d0-5594-467a-a65e-0638d5ce8552",
        "40ab5bc9-a834-46e1-a5cb-36877df6174d",
        "ab1d78ec-c048-41e2-a824-55130a997e2d",
        "2d7db614-3240-4bb1-8986-820d68062a89",
        "a5b01e8b-41fb-499c-beab-2a842c2a0352",
        "5a468a01-6269-436d-88f2-8d92407a0d10",
        "c9f1ba78-9ba1-4537-91da-666e146851f0",
        "9480a08e-edc0-4505-8746-2aca978150f2",
        "cf128f85-06f0-408e-8538-db391fc7b3a2",
        "581ef9ef-29ff-4a18-9aa6-4761899504a3",
        "cbf4b3b0-ce73-4ea9-bf6d-ed311f22ddd9",
        "d36aecd5-13d0-4494-be24-50a33c437a03",
        "621f6e88-7c82-4cbc-ba57-f3f6511990f2",
        "6f7b3286-bdb7-4571-86b5-7f5c291d683c",
        "40145da4-a294-4a8a-a8bf-94db09efbde7",
        "fcc4b8fd-5e8f-4e0b-91b7-ff2238a8d09a",
        "5ac5878a-7f8d-4fa8-a9c1-1e20aeac5034",
        "d7f2ac73-23b1-4aaa-b1f1-d787ebef1891",
        "d2917554-609a-405b-8df7-c7deb79f3b6d",
        "6325bf61-232f-49e8-bf09-dba537a62ac8",
        "baa7380b-4b0f-4abe-90b9-9d23376e4784",
        "7aed4a76-b29b-4d5c-89a4-35a7c1636809",
        "9c7a9806-00ae-4123-b471-c70b5e7a0dd9",
        "792b6fff-db1e-4d1e-8d15-fd76c2ec423e",
        "3d878202-0bb6-45d2-87ff-50291b230659",
        "48d12307-b549-4967-925e-e687c63dd1be",
        "a9270363-16e9-4a0c-a61c-95f87d6979ce",
        "40ac5c19-5e05-4a21-a559-ead568069177",
        "68e783a8-414d-4d73-94e0-562de757a8a6",
        "2b29ad60-a095-4255-b3ec-8db120b1ec14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "c86bd79d-9016-47cf-8f57-3fa28abca881",
      "english": "The bill, please",
      "arabic": " \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "children": [
        "5570b927-0c8b-4f62-9491-6ac4bd82ff62",
        "ad263a6d-d116-4c27-a822-4e7eb574077f",
        "010a7e2f-64e8-4613-817f-fd29ec7ac48c",
        "aaa5f69c-6964-49b4-94a1-d99091152ee7",
        "a33f97cb-dc13-4dbd-913c-9dd6578c002c",
        "c6936187-374d-44bb-b7fb-58cc4d278256",
        "7687c3c6-9c0b-4340-902d-d369b9f45ade",
        "37d5c2a4-1d2b-4213-b50b-8f4918ad727c",
        "6557e65c-4146-4196-a5a1-586d15ace8fa",
        "b49274d4-3e3c-4d66-af08-de0678dc32c7",
        "6d75f594-f708-4bd6-b319-8e46853cf8b8",
        "940a677c-8139-4301-8711-76cfc7fdd423",
        "6702e4f5-f4e1-400d-9a94-d0690cf353aa",
        "cb3875b9-79f5-4c73-adff-7de9cd485710",
        "2a484b5a-b823-45e3-b070-7db54eb7f8fe",
        "45574aba-a704-4518-8a68-78316b8c1d3e",
        "5a760890-d7c1-4511-a4d1-988d47ed7320",
        "3a2d9f13-8b6d-4f6c-b527-7872033548f5",
        "beca6df3-75e3-4a7f-b2cf-b3d9f404a798",
        "ebc9de4a-5b5c-4ef3-b98a-79f4f97ba346",
        "ba22a28d-88da-46c7-8236-1c7397de4084",
        "9029015a-96fa-462f-aecf-ad4f8dd7c5e1",
        "2d106bc0-5fd2-42b3-ae49-d358b62be7e3",
        "0f971e44-c1f0-4cf9-944a-35e4406c56cc",
        "83135127-c438-4864-bf44-80c3f6a76355",
        "0c205725-6e12-47c5-a0ae-81a54c42f5be",
        "c806f0c0-8493-44b0-b4e1-ea4767b0f209",
        "13151a37-3b0a-4da1-ba3b-b0036205e60d",
        "7679137c-d224-4c40-92a7-a57df36d6866",
        "f2ce7f95-dfca-48c7-becb-7f347925cad8",
        "ae2abe80-d129-4028-84c8-79b0544e91a3",
        "fa22eff9-3ea4-4f23-97c9-d2e75fcad101",
        "d903fa46-5ce9-43a0-a6d9-68aaac6137fd",
        "ab6b2d68-3783-4ddf-8499-751f7d7242f6",
        "080ce7a0-0901-4ee7-ad58-5eed90e1cf4f",
        "859fdaa1-005e-4e50-a8e9-2ee6f44844b5",
        "b1236dd6-66fe-4290-a64a-385c71a2a423",
        "a194a149-5d9c-45df-9efe-80f571c7bed8",
        "13ca5d84-6cb9-4726-9aec-a8c9b84916cb",
        "ec99b1d7-a9bb-42d9-8f59-6f675ace2b1c",
        "ecc792a7-5069-4dd0-80e2-bc7d61a56e6d",
        "93bd9a0e-ef6e-4dfb-8199-792dd072c191",
        "6157bead-6cbd-42bf-85fe-dc355b938efb",
        "4c8ed226-2739-432b-b2ed-1e80d55090dc",
        "b12e1853-6546-4c35-b095-c2d1f99089dd",
        "8709e304-23c5-4ed3-a877-f764af3a4779"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "4c848285-37c1-45b4-8a4b-acb584d4e210",
      "english": "(Security Check) Is everything alright?",
      "arabic": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u0643\u0644 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "children": [
        "ff53aa11-b904-4973-aa80-e22e1134b581",
        "455924e0-0540-4f6a-bb05-49d196c52c79",
        "9510f9c6-6eb9-44a0-a768-809a966c84fb",
        "56894edd-50d3-4119-8dde-31fd95153e94",
        "6b803424-6640-4d15-9933-1fbc874cb2aa",
        "3a0cb6da-5a11-43a0-897d-9e81a7b5db17",
        "fbfbc4f8-f7c4-4026-9ac5-2db4ea115e87",
        "0a74b058-e365-42dd-bb8f-7ad7a2d97836",
        "33631635-3e38-4497-983f-123119f20adc",
        "635a8b79-a7c2-4806-85a2-2ff6028ed339",
        "aa6e12d2-deb8-49ec-9a71-63bcb64a1622",
        "99b831c7-dbff-422a-8459-b46539814d45",
        "7bfec21d-ea05-47db-9c6d-63120455b43f",
        "3a2994c7-7378-403d-b43e-39b44a929942",
        "ebdee129-80a6-4d51-9e03-7f4bc343e7f5",
        "89e3ebdd-addb-43e9-b901-8b11276482aa",
        "d2489aa2-d8b2-4c29-9b3a-c8e97317611f",
        "b83b9c91-b50a-40be-905c-19b03c5de0b7",
        "cd8cbe6d-7946-4f3a-b2f5-d0e8b309637b",
        "ab7a8ea2-d531-47a0-befc-adbd3c22ec70",
        "4ca16ede-0509-4dce-b4b5-64cc19f8c7f5",
        "21fa89c0-cafe-4606-be58-15fe9caef1dc",
        "e130ff67-65ec-4809-84b6-5be0e4525b1b",
        "53306c7a-59b1-448c-aa7f-b135493576c9",
        "252da6f9-51cd-4510-a3db-75f5ea348014",
        "79eef191-9b50-4a67-96ae-b0ccc4150e6c",
        "1425d9ff-0230-4722-9b28-163d784ff0c4",
        "fcc5af4e-d8fd-4d58-af6c-19bb44c84e1c",
        "fe6dcade-dd16-4a92-8e66-4d8cf7f79246",
        "83fbc89c-06d0-4486-add1-85013bafc186",
        "cf385a80-130c-4401-97f1-b898e9f03ee2",
        "f0e8aa52-52fe-458f-82f2-428945e58634",
        "84601bb8-e63b-4c59-8562-b5a06358ab93",
        "18dd6860-0f80-4dc7-aecc-5f9f8e2301e0",
        "c53d3377-793c-4f3e-b0d7-c01244887b5f",
        "9c139dba-891c-4505-859c-daff28ccbff2",
        "c79e9574-28df-4af2-beb3-40e2d430cd3c",
        "b57f1bfc-6f49-4504-a2b5-d24993fce76a",
        "a0c3163f-90d0-4018-a251-a21e53de203b",
        "692873d8-3e60-4253-a149-c8af76c431c5",
        "aa661181-101e-40a8-83ad-d2bd9e5c3832",
        "e6cbd457-79e2-4476-b3bf-1d2b723fc38f",
        "ce549529-e9de-48fb-ab91-35af615daa3d",
        "e4bcac24-b8f4-4f81-bda6-d2b7cb497720",
        "2d8e2cd9-072a-4c06-b409-5f8133723dc2",
        "3bfa730b-b1ce-4445-93a0-725035e7608e",
        "8ba2a7ca-182b-4ed3-b871-d95c9bf7dca4",
        "32c01d59-4663-4f49-adad-3b2f9dbe5ff9",
        "c9145829-cec4-44f9-bbfa-e1f45d6b0a3a",
        "e83a65f6-e0b7-4109-b6bf-b38063e0e5e0",
        "82edf743-cefc-44c5-86c8-a20b6d66ce85",
        "be3be402-c14e-4592-9398-7109fcbae700",
        "6c69d486-7a36-4e21-bc36-b5033f924bb6",
        "8a83f63d-ddd5-4337-97cb-b96dead626d8",
        "f41780cc-5d48-4682-abec-53576e12c352",
        "10937206-211f-46b6-aa7e-b22ebee4e069",
        "74fdb164-3cf4-42c7-8fe3-8bbdfe455cab",
        "39e579b7-5028-4eb3-9891-4a17eb01726d",
        "b4e1719f-8898-4ea6-8372-70a3d695dafc",
        "a3a7e2a0-223c-4b6c-ae75-0260cfe1cdfa",
        "d048f1ac-b4ad-40b9-8bd2-4e04245fdf48",
        "ab31c29d-2b7e-46b8-bae1-3aa70ea717cc",
        "67575132-461e-450b-99b9-ffdf71ed0227",
        "e05c1deb-353c-4081-ade6-f068b17882d1",
        "6989f034-84d5-42b5-bd57-898f5ebba071",
        "e154e6cd-a982-4ca7-b86e-3a289fecd80c",
        "f9e61104-fbdf-46b1-9314-4c7b0f556653",
        "497db2e3-66e7-40ac-bbb9-1f096ec528ee",
        "bfd4b4ad-e083-4924-8c4c-6fcebda98b66",
        "2a23d044-41d0-4c8d-9653-d7fc74adda4f",
        "111ee23e-f133-41ba-912b-4310633e70f2",
        "057a0527-b2e7-4361-9163-c9cfe098763a",
        "f418000e-7454-4ce2-afcc-a51b33b7836c",
        "df8289ca-dbfa-4bd3-8f96-bdb1bd47a227",
        "895470d0-46b9-401b-84ab-23f380716549",
        "d38a9672-61d4-45a5-812e-dba31571ec87",
        "2dc39f07-fed6-458a-85e3-12c01b3cc1de",
        "0bda1565-34a7-491c-a41b-c2993c5d9d55",
        "68e0693f-e8d2-4efc-8141-ede2f91d24b8",
        "d1f8b75f-b203-4823-aebb-587ab599d84b",
        "23154b81-c5a7-497c-96ce-fd4eee653413",
        "2ea7ba78-b3a2-4bc7-9f8e-855121e3055b",
        "0accb0d9-4cf4-4e8b-b57e-f50222e2a254",
        "c7c69074-a9b6-401a-9c36-1277eb0e74d6",
        "15269737-ad11-46a2-a99a-8ac599663f2c",
        "a0ba7b54-cdde-47f3-bf40-b11dab56fbc6",
        "85d6b01e-e291-403b-aa10-3be29ff035bc",
        "4abcf597-f338-4fcb-b7d8-6fb846fbc830",
        "67009446-50f6-452b-b33b-bff3fb002c85",
        "61676e2e-4526-4aed-afdc-f60d4b59c59d",
        "935d9802-ff73-457a-af56-51def01f8681",
        "ef09e8bb-1014-44cc-bc6a-c899f64eff90",
        "ee680aa8-231f-43a5-9e7e-3d882424242c",
        "53c05964-eefb-4d97-8e63-2564b5b74ee4",
        "3cf5238f-760e-48b0-9d01-a8293a8fb691"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "0f648ca9-a944-4b05-bf58-ef185146a77f",
      "english": "How long is it open?",
      "arabic": " \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d\u061f",
      "children": [
        "3eafe8c4-929b-4ba6-a5d7-fbeac3cf9b2f",
        "6b2194bd-e552-4149-aab8-87554e3bdc08",
        "292749d7-b9f4-4c99-8be3-b2815c4da8ae",
        "8ceb7ca4-8859-419c-b1b7-6b6fb6eeaa66",
        "14cddf9e-0a2a-4885-9fe6-05b9068c1d4f",
        "749c5ea6-1d20-4ce6-91dc-9e0076f1af5f",
        "d46a3a1f-1cc3-4597-b73f-4d272b35fd11",
        "a3239d55-cb02-4d14-9d7b-b52ea21cf63c",
        "9dff7697-9692-42ba-af2f-1a347f0f503a",
        "8742200c-151b-4859-994e-015ea3a2dd9e",
        "3c48dcd8-4b91-4bf4-b9ad-4d958ccdb209",
        "235c3b42-6000-4382-aaa6-fdbebe1e4795",
        "cafa71a7-f955-4572-9c25-cef20b425c07",
        "a2ea8f3f-28b7-44f5-a2a3-2116d122a1c4",
        "64fcb746-9667-4c53-b0fc-dbf09d14535d",
        "bac18bb1-e6e7-4a34-91b2-e9df9a9bc87d",
        "69d5153d-f382-4a2e-83c0-cf3ae3eb5444",
        "111b7ce4-ebc5-499b-9a1d-6d72a02ca881",
        "c06213e8-7996-49de-a728-d30455320444",
        "7dc7487a-4629-4cde-abea-0e5124e06cea",
        "0aeee53e-b06b-485c-89c7-4c701ff7d8f6",
        "e1239668-3fd5-4e17-9d49-9a66a95bdb2d",
        "51dc86fd-82c2-4d07-acbb-12493f91d89e",
        "159b31b1-4fc2-44a3-95bc-a2e5e80b2c77",
        "78cc9ccb-f7d6-4e14-8745-e0380d8bf31f",
        "fcde2796-f567-43b4-bb4a-1df1e06256b3",
        "86ea046a-8638-434b-94ed-a76af0861177",
        "4dcc40c5-1e9d-4fd3-9ccf-4d4d524f7458",
        "607c210e-0181-442d-a762-b1ef4db18537",
        "1887957a-d1e7-47a4-a00b-bf0f30d01711",
        "97082635-4f75-442b-befb-26e6e439bdc0",
        "394ccf58-3838-433b-b1a6-f2df4708ef45",
        "59053fb0-d052-41ce-8a9e-93b89340d391",
        "31e5e498-653f-4797-a7eb-75a1c63720b2",
        "9883d57c-6b1e-47d4-b16e-6bd93917b892",
        "ebd324eb-c4f4-4509-b861-a72ec89a78ba",
        "97c78612-18b1-4581-8e54-e1fcac7f45b5",
        "ca506ed3-c919-46ce-8e26-d86c9f07371f",
        "64e38ea3-a11e-45e2-85e1-61d9e9853b1d",
        "99194ff8-526d-4c9b-b198-a19cd84bbbe0",
        "00c268f8-360c-4c80-a04d-54fc8ea33a5c"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "00052266-47a6-435d-a904-25f56bb03a2e",
      "english": "Here is my homework",
      "arabic": " \u062f\u0647 \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "children": [
        "75b74283-0e77-4d57-bca5-a2a098360731",
        "dab82414-012e-4666-8204-11d7268ff005",
        "8035b449-9df1-4ceb-b60b-5ab663f99347",
        "3105735e-dfd4-4ee9-928d-e11045a517e8",
        "cf12b789-232d-4e8d-893e-c162431ea8aa",
        "27e0c4a8-5a14-40aa-892c-145a234973b4",
        "80f843a6-a164-4a11-9bf7-f9a1de4e7aa5",
        "340c404a-a2bf-4716-a4f3-191c568e1a87",
        "fcc5aa20-e4f9-4734-9631-023c9da4ceae",
        "a21e6ff3-cc6d-41e1-b5d2-0171c792c1e4",
        "27c0e1fd-b8bb-4834-aa9e-c9c9b2780e4c",
        "72e4a828-b134-40d2-8456-2d165eb9a87f",
        "f2cc391b-586d-45f1-8fdc-8cdc4e035b26",
        "922bcff0-19b4-496c-859f-545ee129e606",
        "c30cd762-4017-4ca7-b64e-8fe9de66bd66",
        "1095d4bc-5f39-4c68-a418-95d2f6a3dafc",
        "25e10674-d0c0-43bc-b874-36bd6399b7b7",
        "0d065db7-2587-4b06-9729-019163d4c051",
        "635da39c-0239-4552-b941-ecf0f1476072",
        "64acecca-c3d2-45f3-8b4b-237742c52d10",
        "1a531482-b938-442e-b861-f999f7843fea",
        "4dbe971c-e42b-47e2-b798-53bb26e61d9c",
        "3e4fffc2-3dc2-4706-b343-19158b7cad84",
        "5ab89b00-7b4c-4fa6-bb27-13f3559939b3",
        "9902c643-6661-49e6-bc0d-82afea3010c8",
        "cfc06888-7f1d-48de-8abb-90a007abd2f0",
        "0e8fa84a-41a7-4d43-9441-6aa399dce848",
        "0143d431-66f4-4e55-a36b-61ac31cb21bd",
        "352710dc-7557-48cf-a687-29b27105a236",
        "2685d3db-0fa7-4687-bf21-960fabc447fe"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "c542ad83-015a-44e7-8b85-34aee8b5f6af",
      "english": "Do we have homework?",
      "arabic": " \u0641\u064a \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u061f",
      "children": [
        "a2af9a68-9c08-4a68-9f68-acf5912c5e79",
        "bf189883-d54f-4c0b-8b0d-5f1df7657381",
        "f2bb0799-dec2-44e5-ba25-b1a6bc90a00f",
        "ef9d7ce4-9ccd-40be-9999-48d9920e8a5b",
        "daa6710a-c610-4959-b3cb-cf09d4f7f161",
        "d0bd242c-cfad-41c4-923d-cfc899db67e5",
        "a95be06a-7a0f-4e5e-a254-6efd9037a4e9",
        "5af4c095-68ed-40db-a143-04b7b34bfe9f",
        "363948d8-fc3d-4fbe-87da-b9b20f9cfc65",
        "850fd4b9-ee72-4e75-99ba-fced5b7e4af2",
        "8670e9b0-306f-4093-aad2-7dde261c2fcd",
        "83ea9131-5119-459f-9a40-b17472e9752e",
        "a3f0cd21-e1e9-4bed-a654-e8676a994fce",
        "23fd9085-5085-4569-ac2a-5ed9c7f17f84",
        "30976176-3660-4ce6-8834-c40501926ab6",
        "2d98d7e3-cbcf-4840-9164-f60afd067833",
        "bba7b302-bdb7-414d-9c4c-39b4acf6683a",
        "5561a03b-4190-499f-93cf-ea3678f64f76",
        "e387047d-82d6-47ca-bcb5-54a07ffd2f77",
        "acd40e44-0a02-429a-bae2-c27350ed272c",
        "a00cfa00-9dff-43bc-95c0-280b813db23b",
        "7de40424-8882-41b2-8e6c-a295e7b29234",
        "b5c7cd93-606e-4160-a6f3-c68e12399edf",
        "106a8026-f055-4536-901f-46ea5edab1fb",
        "3d50dd2c-e8e0-4319-8b2f-298783892050",
        "0c18509b-5432-4581-80dd-064d2db020f8",
        "1b3ec7c7-870a-4c6d-b0c3-67a42d22ed76",
        "424ee551-8303-4522-8b24-b8737e963b14",
        "84fbb6e5-12c9-4722-bf7a-7adbb5e9c434",
        "fb5e0da9-3330-4b14-8b53-640f646a0fbb"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "652cea2d-71fd-4824-91cd-ef3df5faaeac",
      "english": "Good Night",
      "arabic": " \u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "children": [
        "50d45e44-65e8-427b-880e-8182932996b7",
        "3f2d3b3e-0ab9-4873-a5a2-aaaa5a0cdd24",
        "8e915aa2-15a9-4459-a2d1-728f977032a7",
        "f22db8c2-6af3-42f1-80d6-948c24f2ea2f",
        "5fb008fc-eb9b-4ebd-b06b-a1646cc25dcc",
        "a330a611-7dbb-4d3f-875f-84634b23e50b",
        "05f61640-4110-45fa-be8b-bb8272db77c6",
        "995d3715-ae13-431a-a82e-0e5154471b78",
        "c636b212-b859-4d32-b032-afe97187c395",
        "4bbcbd60-c2d9-47c6-a054-0a175d263144",
        "5bd578f6-7daf-4f92-9c79-aba077e71273",
        "f516a23d-9a1c-41d6-9d44-756da63ca3a4",
        "6bf3b0b4-a216-4e10-9044-e249413dbe9e",
        "8e915aa2-15a9-4459-a2d1-728f977032a7",
        "f22db8c2-6af3-42f1-80d6-948c24f2ea2f",
        "5fb008fc-eb9b-4ebd-b06b-a1646cc25dcc",
        "45da35bb-4cc7-4dc2-9393-e1fde457d62a",
        "eb584e2a-a18b-4733-a953-300f1e66685b",
        "31547973-8307-41f6-97e3-8e509ed50dc7",
        "7cd97924-c327-438b-909c-b9d646f9ee7b",
        "52b9a279-cbb2-4b65-a6a9-4cef3d36213d",
        "238e5f71-3a72-4502-a468-cce9d2758b35",
        "dd4fa3d9-7b13-48fa-98e5-09917f18b43b",
        "3b0ffe4d-9f9a-4676-a677-7eca38d9e8db",
        "245a6bb9-c9f7-4449-9894-fffa3711f011",
        "28811695-219e-4986-b523-79e5baed5d09",
        "f35819d3-d31a-426c-8111-446f1193e1cc",
        "48708fcb-212f-4ba2-8b7f-f7853a4479dd",
        "58c7441a-dcba-4c00-baa6-8d92d10ae9f8",
        "f13ee141-f4db-456d-b3e6-ced80230b633",
        "0d13baf8-d693-4224-8e09-b81b319262a9",
        "cbd2f21e-ea6b-44c5-8bb2-0af51dda46d5",
        "3d92e716-a927-4bd0-90d4-4898de247336",
        "ca607f9f-97eb-4f4d-b72a-8760d4ac2550",
        "be69f30d-4305-4d16-8361-ec8f80c7f2bc",
        "1bc67e90-94e3-4682-b4ca-4a7285c82edb",
        "19559c82-f884-4a53-adb2-04b18ade4839",
        "b1039f08-6b8e-4340-a127-cb5252d063a8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "9e5c207a-cbdd-4ded-8ca8-c98b1a699b9f",
      "english": "I'm good, how are you?",
      "arabic": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c \u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "children": [
        "caeef585-e0de-46a6-9b49-8e04d5c39384",
        "12e43bcf-53e5-46cd-b915-79c360541118",
        "a7745e5a-0b59-47c9-9f62-bad69ab673c0",
        "4b325b2e-0619-4f85-95cf-7bae7136cd70",
        "6da2c303-a1a7-4f16-89cc-3ccfa615b481",
        "c9e33926-cde9-46f9-a2c7-35aabc371bd1",
        "e2290930-2439-400e-ad37-fc41b244b746",
        "62ddf8f4-524f-40d9-9983-6eaa86a005d4",
        "05ad2b72-31a7-4242-a5dc-8e5e0e6e698a",
        "6f81e444-67b1-45e2-9d95-121c8894994d",
        "ae6f3822-1e8a-4ae3-8eaa-a339b692fccb",
        "33fce108-8e9c-4ca0-a4a4-d459d0566ce7",
        "4aaccfe3-4d20-4ea7-9eb8-dc868c019ee7",
        "19c1f66c-09fd-4adb-ab6c-4fcb73de61b9",
        "e8751c8e-e7b4-46fe-820b-80a5c7ba489a",
        "486e467d-aec9-4ef6-aa8a-5bc65a437589",
        "900287f7-2231-4cd5-b5af-59968546f370",
        "16bd9584-6e9f-4f12-9221-40486793c5c9",
        "36ebfbae-778f-4ba5-9e09-ecb9431ce5fc",
        "0ee7fdee-003a-4a52-95e1-cef3ea66a4e3",
        "61d6dd26-6189-41f4-b9d6-9ad3619bae9c",
        "fc8b03ec-9a8c-4b03-8028-cbc5405f75d8",
        "16c9e766-ebe6-4153-8034-bb60ea4f037d",
        "2df8d2ca-bb61-4ec8-92e6-9d8b581eb751",
        "6fa0e6b9-80a7-469e-a23a-e5e11b32d61a",
        "fb172ace-d17e-4893-8b8a-34004dc3ca61",
        "7bafe214-935d-44f0-a9e4-f52f9b5898f0",
        "91149ba9-240c-4a32-9b94-3949704eb782",
        "4b108959-d47f-4af1-8678-bc9d94afc08a",
        "3eed3367-5aee-42e4-bd74-328d1f82bf03",
        "9fbc3081-729a-4695-ada0-0d9612564232",
        "75535b82-8dce-4031-ac4a-8710bfce9b22",
        "5cb1f78b-bc5f-459f-9b45-0faac0ee46b5",
        "3177106b-967d-4edd-8bd2-738efdfb58d9",
        "2071638b-3d44-48a6-b765-ba25f8e42c28",
        "30b76478-46b7-4157-ac9c-075e81c0d1bb",
        "25829079-9271-4480-9581-6411bf960227",
        "cd21b596-f6f0-4425-8a99-f7284b76fef3",
        "f3b69960-be80-459c-a230-fbbb5fcd3e2e",
        "43522e6d-e844-47ba-9950-3baac1fd84c3",
        "7b63537c-706a-4a8e-87d8-3550cc31f182",
        "9953378f-400b-4103-84fd-b12af68b6f2c",
        "d4494d3e-8b58-4da0-8db1-cb7e87459ba1",
        "b0ecca4c-267b-4500-ac53-356e5c9a05a6",
        "8d956674-b623-4977-be76-932231d4b2b4",
        "08490e74-07fa-4c7c-8841-6329949ae4c2",
        "97a87d08-4fc5-40b8-bcd7-7204cbf1289d",
        "fd89cfe3-137b-43fa-9ba4-de1a845ff3b8",
        "2c106a0f-5bbd-4b69-bbce-95d525ff2a48",
        "a5d9bb66-863d-4bef-8aa6-506148a64d91",
        "2854c757-a8ee-4372-b3b0-cf3ab468277c",
        "23da570d-ca01-4c36-8b93-b55b621f4f76",
        "a4adb983-8c12-4b7b-877c-392c4aa55c0c",
        "f05ee086-31b1-4aa1-a9e0-01abf705f32a",
        "5c6ede84-949b-4650-9e30-f43a62b8659b",
        "443d2839-4bd6-4731-b80e-cd7780c3f70e",
        "40463459-ff1a-4f61-9780-ab804419e24d",
        "01d0ef7e-3ca6-49ab-b582-d40778118016",
        "24d1f6f6-20dd-45b5-bb6a-1928aba16d3e",
        "97e49559-6e55-4c07-a8b5-9573d9d41beb",
        "15e16552-6fe4-4cb0-aaaa-cf07c1b9c96e",
        "41effe74-8799-4e54-9fa4-4833dcafcb22",
        "10792ce9-1e93-47b3-9860-4e1b4af2e88c",
        "d00316a8-120b-40ec-9a76-ddd2941b7e37",
        "ec7e90f0-fe04-4c85-9d6d-24afc1a1e35f",
        "8a9fdf9c-d0fe-4a63-bbbb-bda55bea01fc",
        "4f1cda3b-ec76-46a7-b968-fc628582688d",
        "f5a5a9e8-93c1-4e1d-8d2f-90a1567da4dc",
        "22c3b398-bc0b-42dd-b047-3d1a13e02a0b",
        "44a65470-1361-494c-9199-5946f06719c3",
        "2a3e3ec7-4516-4c04-b33a-a4827057dce6",
        "38f18e69-657e-467e-949c-a67bf4582604",
        "579a142e-93b5-48d0-8022-8bc3975578c7",
        "9ce143b5-d7f3-47be-9b63-7a9370cca5d1",
        "6240d690-cb9c-4c55-b1ee-02e5db315568",
        "1d9c042a-aaec-4964-b5fd-8362df13c18d",
        "b0fc75f0-775d-41b1-95a8-86acd2e78ef2",
        "b4ac19ac-c56b-49a5-9af5-17c9c55caa8f",
        "4fcd2278-7796-427a-8962-2ef830d3b42d",
        "1162ce71-ad63-4cb8-8adf-78abb32016ec",
        "102e9d06-2feb-409c-a6d7-5a634eee0ba1",
        "b4c3c716-f29c-4632-bb54-dd6d176c1d51",
        "eeec873a-c8ab-41d6-b6b1-9e5159b485f7",
        "8159f7d2-3f17-474d-8e0c-b9cda3323b47",
        "9ef3d24b-9735-4bbe-a09e-8d939cb717b2",
        "046f5313-26cc-472f-a2d8-a69df17e9333",
        "9a9229c5-06b3-43cd-ad95-575b4722a781",
        "e48a0e03-35fd-4719-b090-57a51f8e9515",
        "77cdb879-9ec5-40b8-be5c-95b253b8763a",
        "6ea8b4ec-0148-4722-bdec-889273783c5f",
        "cf47eaa0-5d88-476f-b73a-d4799b85646e",
        "a143a5cc-bc2f-4428-8928-b1ee839dc29b",
        "bdd60adc-fff7-4493-b55a-d51077f30cbe",
        "e8841759-67d6-4bbd-93da-a0e71015bc14",
        "d6178db0-db44-429d-bffc-d2ec4ecbf178",
        "bbf62729-e169-422b-9558-5a13d63cda3f",
        "b14e3f48-5e9c-4bbf-b042-d3c164cad5f2",
        "df213fb8-2f39-4ac0-9423-e7384bd42fb2",
        "da268918-60b0-4d65-88b8-2cc14130f570",
        "ea4d3491-c628-4679-99bc-0846f70af1c6",
        "02ffe877-878e-4ac2-a42a-b64cce62f14d",
        "365a21c2-18b5-475b-95ff-bf315698503e",
        "fa193992-d066-457e-88e6-740afbc6a18b",
        "cfea3a82-023a-4e57-b10e-4e82717a4f8d"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "27ed0263-790b-4a4f-bdf3-90049a648d9a",
      "english": "Do you live in Cairo?",
      "arabic": " \u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "children": [
        "cd181c71-c570-4818-b22e-08dff3f8af87",
        "9ce143b5-d7f3-47be-9b63-7a9370cca5d1",
        "6240d690-cb9c-4c55-b1ee-02e5db315568",
        "1d9c042a-aaec-4964-b5fd-8362df13c18d",
        "b0fc75f0-775d-41b1-95a8-86acd2e78ef2",
        "b4ac19ac-c56b-49a5-9af5-17c9c55caa8f",
        "4fcd2278-7796-427a-8962-2ef830d3b42d",
        "1162ce71-ad63-4cb8-8adf-78abb32016ec",
        "102e9d06-2feb-409c-a6d7-5a634eee0ba1",
        "b4c3c716-f29c-4632-bb54-dd6d176c1d51",
        "eeec873a-c8ab-41d6-b6b1-9e5159b485f7",
        "8159f7d2-3f17-474d-8e0c-b9cda3323b47",
        "9ef3d24b-9735-4bbe-a09e-8d939cb717b2",
        "046f5313-26cc-472f-a2d8-a69df17e9333",
        "9a9229c5-06b3-43cd-ad95-575b4722a781",
        "e48a0e03-35fd-4719-b090-57a51f8e9515",
        "77cdb879-9ec5-40b8-be5c-95b253b8763a",
        "6ea8b4ec-0148-4722-bdec-889273783c5f",
        "cf47eaa0-5d88-476f-b73a-d4799b85646e",
        "6364fea7-f886-463d-8c8e-19d8bf69ce84",
        "983946d9-6c4a-4306-b56d-f20c081cb87a",
        "1d633edc-a187-4dd0-9da0-1cb99eb64050",
        "c3dbb607-1f19-484b-a926-deee039905be",
        "33134866-a5c9-40d6-8479-809e50c16f08",
        "bce11038-9a2c-427f-837b-dcb547d0ed03",
        "a116a600-a85e-4e10-81a0-50d4b6a33072",
        "b9f86f3e-9844-41eb-be22-4c38739f6838",
        "c5a33e6a-9df6-4fb1-a397-9f8b4eaea842",
        "5a0fe30c-7eb1-419f-bfac-0481e0c5a6a4",
        "c084093c-535f-4422-b0b6-15adb5e0eff0",
        "a3272a07-1451-484e-967f-a2ea9036b55b",
        "cd28a209-aca7-4125-91b0-38bca64c39e5",
        "613a47ce-7eea-4b50-92ac-5bf458aec4cf",
        "d1b20d02-0bc2-4d04-b261-1b3a303c217d",
        "15f09153-d03f-4a67-86f2-1641d95d4708",
        "cbf8f469-1b8b-43e5-9eaa-5ceae5adb7d6",
        "a21f9041-1533-4e30-a5da-f30b7f70dcac",
        "d74ccd5c-4ef9-449e-b48c-79d88df36e8c",
        "c39a5118-de4d-4f46-bb95-a3329478d373",
        "44a82611-d976-40e0-9660-c4dd54c529ce",
        "b387b49d-7456-4814-ace2-7eaa1e690b02",
        "e41ec555-ae2f-4df0-b35d-17faae43631c",
        "60db9373-d7ee-478e-b181-7766f2ed1dfa",
        "7aef05f7-e2d9-40ff-a015-d9d3c1ff35f3",
        "2a83c9e9-e056-4eb7-ac15-f3ce825413d3",
        "b83a5d79-cd9d-4385-96f0-231bad86d867",
        "4e69d602-87a6-4e18-92c5-23bf0a2d7d83",
        "e961ba9a-07e0-4d6d-b08d-8d8c604032a8",
        "ee0ce9fc-e132-410c-895a-15ad3ec3f74b",
        "10a326cb-8ef1-4367-8eef-7806f1a4cce9",
        "f028a584-2785-4883-b6b8-9fc878dd3d97",
        "5aa9319b-eb79-4731-8ee1-3f959074b284",
        "0afd1458-f31c-4484-b8fe-4a71b90f06b8",
        "578f9790-1ca3-417e-a571-8a570d2e23f4",
        "afbc2943-16d8-4602-b3f7-e2999052c8d0",
        "1a89caf3-0a61-4a9f-ac32-3eb9088e9157",
        "82b3ee5d-027d-47df-b454-5291200126e7",
        "81772cd2-b425-484a-9ad5-f6fc50af2a0d",
        "ba38161d-4ad8-455d-a26b-efe53e61f4b0",
        "48a89eea-d3d8-41e8-bb99-b24ac6236c70",
        "334da3d2-0cca-4959-a7b4-d4ee83bc8d29",
        "4e3b8d03-0e32-4fcf-994c-ed4cf7a8ca9d",
        "e480b4e7-f969-42b9-9752-7bcb80b3c36e",
        "06e5049c-6cb8-4067-bef3-9251e4c2cbdb",
        "9fdccc94-d32d-4f89-a948-d42c12de3f4c",
        "ba58d1de-c3c2-432d-85d2-c6c04153de17",
        "08aa4780-675d-4043-a4a6-820941acadd8",
        "010a139a-f6d8-4e37-bfe4-62e462ae7118",
        "f56e446c-4aa9-449a-b29d-8fe00ee56596",
        "1d102163-414e-43a2-8643-c19fe33e574e",
        "cb3581d8-90f1-4fbd-a2e7-04af5cb65cb1",
        "32f7d8db-f44f-46b4-b35f-b386b9b17b28",
        "0429cdee-2e5a-4608-93ea-d9f430a31aa2",
        "4aabdd7a-155b-409d-a434-a0ab75333412",
        "dd968d49-a94a-49b9-8590-b0b1e444522f",
        "b914604d-060c-4e4f-bf09-bc19f4c94e7b",
        "7e7cbdbe-e19b-4903-8459-fd539b4b027e",
        "cd9b4d3c-4489-4bb6-9330-f49cfe5fc637",
        "33769a8e-5871-4303-89ca-86f6b328415e",
        "6f44a67b-9e07-4a29-b201-47c787b9ea7d",
        "1fcd539c-3f94-4400-a7a9-f55756910a56",
        "bdb44474-c72c-4c21-bbb4-091d46ad3a25",
        "2980eb48-5e7f-468a-9e3b-41e33e9757d4",
        "e4ab7bea-7ad3-4f6e-a283-3320cf469c18",
        "d7d51a37-c48c-44d8-8862-0c0b542507af",
        "e0f743d3-8f7c-4b2f-8102-a7501bd279d6",
        "e1a4fa18-90aa-41d2-9d2c-42e1ae753e26",
        "79ea8d3d-4de6-497b-b0df-8ea1343f2172",
        "297fd169-1d81-4c86-afe9-3d8dcef2dfe1",
        "eb73dd2d-20f1-46d0-ad26-64e7b533e7af"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "ca5a7887-b02c-43c8-8a3a-4812ef4e03f7",
      "english": "Does this bus go to ... ?",
      "arabic": " \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u062f\u0647 \u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 ... \u061f",
      "children": [
        "a08c22b1-deee-42ba-86f2-41dabab11d48",
        "0cdbf383-3ae0-4d28-a654-47d69a7c43b4",
        "b462701b-46f5-425b-bd95-358e6f869a20",
        "f7c70058-b3fd-4908-a64c-65789cc4fb24",
        "746b2ab1-2e63-4b7a-9bca-09be42f408f2",
        "4cbe3677-ba99-48c0-abab-dac145e3f084",
        "7263508c-e08a-4214-8e0e-110fc7388bea",
        "e0e71c1d-a52a-4015-b322-c5c191ee3ce2",
        "781e8f21-856a-4967-b2e1-0011162b44c4",
        "9bd51eab-a7bf-4498-acb0-e93c2ec65fbe",
        "69bbd05d-c40a-4ff5-a2a2-cb16181a63ec",
        "f8acbf10-10b4-456d-a263-a6a2c3b79c8f",
        "22a57efa-d859-421b-9702-67e628f69e6b",
        "7eb9d1f1-ea26-43dd-96f8-bb7337d426d0",
        "bd4314f6-2e5f-4aae-992f-0917f7ac1c14",
        "10beaf82-bc66-4cd6-a17e-88cf392acfad",
        "114e4c03-0cd7-403d-9e5d-70ec6cb07133",
        "86e69994-12ae-46be-8129-01d13e8fc28f",
        "72652b86-01e6-4732-a805-523ca2ca42f4",
        "fb508ac2-54de-4dad-9234-5fa3746ca1b5",
        "b0d01cca-ca51-4de6-ad30-6ebf5b4725d1",
        "90345799-ac59-4d08-88c2-0e2ad2edf67e",
        "6134cc0a-6fa5-4e84-89fd-cdbd4de2c203",
        "84e36e3e-9c87-4546-aa89-f67794029e40",
        "1b273ab3-7f59-4eff-b3c9-139d701262b2",
        "be5b1631-4fee-4b58-a575-c31ba7ca82c7",
        "c193b7a9-f540-4922-993a-813359ba01cd",
        "7f120042-18a2-46bd-ab96-fab9455737d0",
        "1ff0f48c-de76-4e84-95a5-21fbb7fd82c0",
        "50a406f0-d5f3-4f01-bcc9-7e2e187e7501",
        "ff03685e-9390-49e2-aa11-691541bb4fcf",
        "72832e26-79c1-46be-8eb1-e0ab23f848d9"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "5ba9f8dc-9ee9-4eaf-87b1-6d81947f9651",
      "english": "Do you want some of this?",
      "arabic": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0645\u0646 \u062f\u0647\u061f",
      "children": [
        "ecb27445-acd7-407c-b252-ab1fdd2ce628",
        "80b37855-5b70-4e93-9bc1-07642755739a",
        "9432e994-ea73-4e5d-8044-049711a049eb",
        "6a9055ec-6feb-422c-89c8-26803606a40d",
        "c1f49b26-e4c2-42e0-98ac-504b2511b573",
        "994b3126-fe7d-49c5-941c-36886aa336bb",
        "3848c9dc-92af-487f-adc3-9e7e25a2b344",
        "2feaf2d9-1082-4f09-b24c-82c15f20100c",
        "e7b1a435-f5ec-4378-9a29-2c824b4fc2d3",
        "ec75dcd4-27d3-40e7-9ed3-fc18ec93ad75",
        "ede40320-59d5-4c32-99f0-c5b282628538",
        "19e90ecb-5850-433c-b118-0f3c38de1583",
        "b71db25b-6075-4cda-ac57-a4e6ec74c7d7",
        "b86dda0a-08ee-4dc2-9cca-4a956123c23d",
        "332fe340-4528-4032-8b22-9ac07538ac2b",
        "1cc1323c-5a20-43e0-81e7-d10312912ad9",
        "b782fb3b-0f0b-4f70-b73d-73b7d56c0231",
        "ad8367b0-c7cd-4834-997b-210e6f6f62d6",
        "170d7653-e599-4430-8c3d-eee29e8e2467",
        "f27c5018-6efb-45a6-a86d-ed506a86925e",
        "ae4be931-a6f6-41bb-9fb9-3e1223bed2c9",
        "742830a6-0904-4eae-9abf-d1b445e984f9",
        "8a73ee9c-3d9d-4864-88b9-35a541044274",
        "e1d7e9dd-87b2-4535-9b5b-2dcf4ae238d3",
        "62e8e2bb-1366-4fcd-b085-a56fafd1fb06",
        "0540819a-ce37-4cbc-b909-4cf8f12d4e8f",
        "c2f83ca8-69d1-46ea-a5e4-3f687a09e75c",
        "51b70a65-cc87-4e0c-8f3e-7e453ea20fe4",
        "6413feb9-f657-4b70-9815-c45d0ffcf8a2",
        "930c0be3-2046-4986-8a14-79f2f0929c4e",
        "83cf9606-918e-44f5-a325-b75e58c600ee",
        "c4ab04a3-b98c-43af-8d7b-cc7ec4aaad5f",
        "feeef7da-d17f-468e-97b4-5d5cd1d7c2b7",
        "22cc3c78-b97e-484b-b3d8-e76dc2259a27",
        "a2f3c9a0-07e1-48d7-bf13-a32ad24978e5",
        "214a3795-10ce-4684-8f38-cd3ac432ac7b",
        "55a764d8-e2e0-4a08-8250-1e7af074dbe5",
        "fa0a66cf-b0f9-4bae-a68c-5a70d7375661"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "922288bf-b83c-4b3e-9e17-3e06ce0bc07f",
      "english": "Do you want to get lunch?",
      "arabic": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646 \u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649\u061f",
      "children": [
        "4d022418-a807-43af-8cdb-2e8e06fb02fb",
        "5ff89cec-9e82-476f-9623-26bac6d533b8",
        "d71096e0-782f-47c2-9da1-d76262a8d1b3",
        "44fa7ca4-d9e5-4b23-ad11-76a549e0984e",
        "1600f4fe-f6d2-421e-a885-1efa83692b35",
        "89808776-3dd4-45af-813d-7d6c7a6fa1b3",
        "792efe35-ea41-4c81-b0de-f5e14350692a",
        "5b5783e5-44e2-4122-a5b2-e041266b6158",
        "7deee251-4b80-4d56-8776-9b3e577ac08f",
        "b3cd29d9-4c97-46d8-8318-5082d7db108c",
        "8489d9ee-dcc1-4dbc-9aad-616fe1c26a1b",
        "ae83dbf2-cc41-4bc9-ba2e-c4ea0daef4d8",
        "9cc0404e-3b20-4170-94de-cd68047c7028",
        "cd89781e-0398-40e8-afd8-57c8128832b6",
        "4e81d227-837b-4cad-a4b1-a07d73b17cc3",
        "447d89cb-f844-4e38-bac2-8de337bd111c",
        "7f631f11-5447-4b02-ba49-c323101dcf33",
        "2afaa1ef-7ab9-409e-bac7-65bbef81c006",
        "dd5aa3d3-13c1-41ae-a4da-7bbe2be34e49",
        "452c0bd4-c745-4e95-a1ba-9f41317a7bc1",
        "95cf3c28-c7dc-454a-938d-2333d269e1c4",
        "86578156-ed8a-43b2-a9e1-630df5aaced7",
        "70d3370a-7832-44d8-8a4a-e50df161177e",
        "8e625b26-99f9-4ce3-9e7e-3f042a5bf935",
        "6c118ac4-5091-4f15-bc46-76e12aad7238"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "1943ba3c-3f2f-4a6e-bfd1-79b9efb2177b",
      "english": "Are you hungry?",
      "arabic": " \u0625\u0646\u062a \u062c\u0648\u0639\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "children": [
        "9de1d84d-cee7-4b0e-ab10-446311405401",
        "5a36d8ca-e99b-4935-a393-f5abb31a3f4d",
        "ed9733e7-cd76-4f01-8eda-069ad9c71382",
        "de138420-177f-43a6-8e69-2341d9061a21",
        "e70cda1f-f233-46ea-b99b-4534cd544281",
        "ebfa3a69-341e-454c-a223-1bbde934318a",
        "4d2ef75d-7f6c-48bd-b915-aa20f5a47090",
        "ad8aded9-a6fb-4ad6-8d35-d6b60d06a925",
        "e7e37446-9bb6-4439-9736-4c231f475fd1",
        "f3409ac7-6532-4112-9ef5-5ea3009e21da",
        "edb19998-7549-44d2-92db-ecef6e7f84b4",
        "3633cfce-b403-4658-a50e-83675bf49526",
        "ae9b3576-5743-4ad8-a91e-f24f06908a17",
        "e3bf2328-9fdb-442b-ad07-f0700cb3320c",
        "aa5cd36b-f7c1-4c52-bd37-cfba410db30f",
        "8a301ada-fd38-422d-81df-ae3e33545dd3",
        "1495b8d6-6a0e-4202-9d78-c68f09031c27",
        "ebfa3a69-341e-454c-a223-1bbde934318a",
        "4d2ef75d-7f6c-48bd-b915-aa20f5a47090",
        "ad8aded9-a6fb-4ad6-8d35-d6b60d06a925",
        "e7e37446-9bb6-4439-9736-4c231f475fd1",
        "f3409ac7-6532-4112-9ef5-5ea3009e21da",
        "edb19998-7549-44d2-92db-ecef6e7f84b4",
        "3633cfce-b403-4658-a50e-83675bf49526",
        "a5e514db-faa0-41df-99ed-13c03c479996",
        "ed345e30-4e24-474c-b7bd-dbeedd01b723",
        "75e70e26-adea-43c2-8f7b-00c6ad879cf4",
        "b85bae47-4b6d-4b5d-831f-39921e58f5a3",
        "fe6a623a-19a0-410a-84b9-9a3d43a07c02",
        "3e183c8a-3c34-4040-94b1-97c03325f6ee",
        "a01e637a-c5e2-46b0-8395-d54b573349c3",
        "64313878-e226-47f7-b52f-49bdb502ea48",
        "9f40fd56-f431-4e15-adfe-8f712cc7e051",
        "8487b728-1e10-4290-88e3-d3869d4c28a3",
        "f4e48430-8632-4e63-85a2-2348db6f502d",
        "bf16d818-e9c6-4ca6-a0e1-003dbdda143e",
        "15ac0f0d-3b95-48d9-92cf-a1e02239b841",
        "0b1a1e22-3d37-482f-b55b-0343bb7c8ee0",
        "d8258cbd-8cc7-4aa3-a9c0-9cb2c9ec55c9",
        "8b6b104e-fca3-4bbb-8a2a-b61d779149b7",
        "a13b542a-8f4b-4838-be80-234c92a23a25",
        "dad80518-b77b-48af-804f-bd16000e78ba",
        "77c12e73-997f-494d-aaab-7a0d89774eae",
        "53d1d681-4450-4d7d-8f11-d3423161bef0",
        "33c0ad66-45fd-4466-833e-0add5390330e",
        "e2a0e54a-d893-4ae5-89d0-903d23859068",
        "c872433b-9873-436f-9405-07cdc1de00bf",
        "f00d3fc3-2d87-41e4-add7-ae7bd7462695",
        "bf5d0a21-17f7-434b-8490-126ae26e5e4b",
        "d77d72a6-67be-41f1-8b58-84ff8f2a3165",
        "f25fde92-a323-475a-8004-8da302ce5cc3",
        "af9a310e-2cb9-4ff0-9d63-e9c690c9f3b3",
        "04f11498-6acf-4c0c-bddf-8893ae6c9a26",
        "fa250786-8506-4d75-9a0d-6a9193d66b4b"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
